German O
league O
, O
Bundesliga O
say O
dem O
go O
restart O
matches O
for O
16 B-DATE
May I-DATE
and O
for O
South B-LOC
Korea I-LOC
live O
league O
football O
games O
don O
already O
start O
. O

Bjornsson B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
2 O
. O
05m O
tall O
( O
6ft O
9in O
) O
, O
bin O
win O
di O
World O
Strongest O
Man O
competition O
for O
2018 B-DATE
. O

Aside O
Ighalo B-PER
, O
four O
other O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
players O
including O
: O
Paul B-PER
Pogba I-PER
, O
Davide B-PER
de I-PER
Gea I-PER
, O
Anthony B-PER
Martial I-PER
and O
Luke B-PER
Shaw I-PER
make O
di O
18 O
- O
man O
list O
. O

Dem O
bin O
suspend O
football O
unti O
further O
notice O
for O
France B-LOC
on O
13 B-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

Dis O
screen O
inside O
di O
stadium O
for O
RB B-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG
tell O
pipo O
to O
wash O
dia O
hands O
. O

Add O
to O
empty O
stadium O
, O
some O
goals O
na O
social O
- O
distancing O
alias O
dey O
your O
lane O
dem O
use O
celebrate O
. O

Football O
fans O
dey O
use O
Liverpool B-ORG
do O
yeye O
for O
social O
media O
with O
funny O
- O
funny O
comments O
and O
memes O
afta O
dem O
crash O
out O
for O
Champions O
League O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Dem O
don O
confam O
di O
condition O
of O
both O
of O
dem O
. O

Di O
players O
bin O
dey O
travel O
from O
Enugu B-LOC
, O
east B-LOC
of I-LOC
di I-LOC
kontri I-LOC
to O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
south B-LOC
west I-LOC
of I-LOC
di I-LOC
kontri I-LOC
sake O
of O
di O
break O
wey O
dem O
get O
for O
di O
Nigerian O
league O
on O
Friday B-DATE
20 I-DATE
March I-DATE
, I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
sake O
of O
coronavirus O
pandemic O
. O

Di O
fight O
wey O
many O
sabi O
pipo O
say O
no O
two O
sweet O
to O
watch O
, O
bin O
happun O
for O
di O
T B-LOC
- I-LOC
Mobile I-LOC
Arena I-LOC
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
, O
American O
early O
mor O
mor O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

British O
world O
champion O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
go O
fight O
Kubrat B-PER
Pulev I-PER
for O
Tottenham B-LOC
Hotspur I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
20 I-DATE
June I-DATE
. O

But O
Wilder B-PER
wey O
be O
American O
do O
use O
di O
rematch O
clause O
, O
wey O
mean O
say O
Fury B-PER
vs O
Wilder B-PER
part O
three O
go O
happun O
before O
Fury B-PER
and O
Joshua B-PER
go O
fight O
. O

Di O
family O
of O
di O
football O
star O
Kazeem B-PER
Tiamiyu I-PER
wey O
die O
for O
Sagamu B-LOC
- O
Ogun B-LOC
state I-LOC
South I-LOC
West I-LOC
Nigeria I-LOC
, O
don O
tok O
about O
wetin O
dem O
remember O
am O
for O
, O
and O
how O
di O
loss O
go O
forever O
affect O
dem O
. O

"""" O
Fury B-PER
no O
wound O
me O
at O
all O
, O
but O
di O
simple O
fact O
be O
say O
my O
uniform O
too O
heavy O
for O
me O
, O
"""" O
Wilder B-PER
told O
Yahoo B-ORG
. O

Wilder B-PER
dey O
start O
as O
favourite O
according O
to O
betting O
pipo O
before O
di O
fighters O
go O
waka O
enta O
di O
ring O
around O
05 B-DATE
: I-DATE
00 I-DATE
GMT I-DATE
on O
Sunday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
. O

I O
believe O
say O
Fury B-PER
go O
survive O
some O
difficult O
moment O
and O
then O
win O
on O
points O
. O

CAF B-ORG
komot O
release O
on O
coronavirus O
say O
dia O
team O
of O
doctors O
di O
check O
de O
situation O
for O
continent O
. O

Eight O
major O
football O
kontris O
for O
Africa B-LOC
don O
already O
get O
de O
virus O
: O
Egypt B-LOC
, O
Algeria B-LOC
, O
Tunisia B-LOC
, O
Morocco B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
Senegal B-LOC
, O
Cameroon B-LOC
and O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

Just O
now O
CAF B-ORG
medical O
teams O
di O
watch O
, O
di O
report O
for O
executive O
committee O
and O
if O
de O
situation O
wowo O
, O
CAF B-ORG
for O
decide O
make O
de O
play O
matches O
wit O
no O
fans O
, O
postpone O
or O
cancel O
. O

Di O
king O
don O
return O
to O
di O
top O
of O
di O
throne' O
Dis O
na O
wetin O
Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
tok O
afta O
im O
beat O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
hands O
down O
to O
become O
WBC O
world O
heavyweight O
champion O
for O
dia O
rematch O
wey O
happun O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
tok O
. O

NFF B-ORG
announce O
dis O
appointment O
for O
inside O
statement O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

I O
no O
care O
how O
much O
be O
di O
pay O
- O
cut O
, O
I O
know O
dat O
, O
make O
e O
just O
happun' O
. O
"""" O

Senegal B-LOC
and O
Liverpool B-ORG
forward O
Mane B-PER
beat O
both O
Egypt B-LOC
player O
Mohammed B-PER
Salah I-PER
and O
Algeria B-LOC
winger O
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
to O
win O
di O
award O
wey O
dem O
do O
for O
Egypt B-LOC
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

Mohamed B-PER
Salah I-PER
( O
Egypt B-LOC
& O
Liverpool B-ORG
) O
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
( O
Algeria B-LOC
& O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
) O
Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
( O
Senegal B-LOC
& O
Liverpool B-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Ajara B-PER
Nchout I-PER
( O
Cameroon B-LOC
& O
Valerenga B-ORG
) O
Asisat B-PER
Oshoala I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Barcelona B-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Thembi B-PER
Kgatlana I-PER
( O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
& O
Beijing B-ORG
Phoenix I-ORG
FC I-ORG
) O
Anice B-PER
Badri I-PER
( O
Tunisia B-LOC
& O
Esperance B-ORG
) O
Tarek B-PER
Hamed I-PER
( O
Egypt B-LOC
& O
Zamalek B-ORG
) O
Youcef B-PER
Belaïli I-PER
( O
Algeria B-LOC
& O
Esperance B-ORG
/ O
Ahli B-ORG
Jeddah I-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Achraf B-PER
Hakimi I-PER
( O
Morocco B-LOC
& O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Samuel B-PER
Chukwueze I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Villarreal B-ORG
) O
Victor B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Lille B-ORG
) O
Aliou B-PER
Cisse I-PER
( O
Senegal B-LOC
- O
Senegal B-LOC
) O
Djamel B-PER

Im O
help O
Senegal B-LOC
to O
reach O
dia O
first O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
final O
for O
over O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
dis O
year O
and O
many O
pipo O
regard O
am O
as O
one O
of O
di O
best O
centre O
- O
backs O
for O
modern O
day O
football O
. O

Mohamed B-PER
Salah I-PER
don O
net O
more O
than O
202 O
goals O
for O
club O
and O
kontri O
dis O
decade O
. O

Arguably O
di O
greatest O
African O
Player O
of O
all O
time O
, O
Samuel B-PER
Eto'o I-PER
win O
e O
second O
treble O
for O
di O
start O
of O
di O
decade O
with O
Inter B-ORG
Milan I-ORG
under O
Jose B-PER
Mourinho I-PER
. O

Senaya B-PER
remember O
Togo B-LOC
media O
officer O
, O
Stanislas B-PER
Ocloo I-PER
, O
bin O
stand O
to O
video O
dia O
arrival O
for O
Angola B-LOC
at O
di O
moment O
of O
di O
attack O
. O

I O
say O
: O
'Dem O
don O
hit O
me O
, O
help O
me O
, O
help O
me O
, O
I O
want O
see O
my O
daughter O
, O
my O
son O
. O

Covington B-PER
get O
four O
career O
win O
by O
submission O
and O
three O
knockout O
victory O
. O

Oda O
Boxing O
Day O
matches O
see O
Chelsea B-ORG
surprisingly O
lose O
2 O
- O
0 O
to O
Southampton B-ORG
for O
Stamford B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
while O
Tottenham B-ORG
come O
from O
behind O
to O
beat O
Brighton B-ORG
2 O
- O
1 O
. O

Wilder B-PER
, O
wey O
im O
WBC O
belt O
go O
dey O
on O
di O
line O
when O
they O
jam O
for O
MGM B-LOC
Grand I-LOC
, O
tweet O
say O
: O
"""" O
kweshion O
no O
go O
dey O
again O
"""" O
and O
"""" O
I O
go O
finish O
wetin O
I O
start O
"""" O
. O

Aboudi B-PER
, O
striker O
for O
national O
team O
, O
football O
for O
yi O
na O
gift O
, O
and O
as O
player O
weh O
e O
start O
for O
young O
age O
di O
play O
wit O
boys O
dem O
, O
say O
na O
e O
own O
small O
contribution O
for O
komot O
women O
football O
from O
darkness O
. O

Liverpool B-ORG
midfielder O
James B-PER
Milner I-PER
no O
dey O
hide O
am O
say O
im O
no O
like O
VAR O
at O
all O
. O

Many O
fans O
don O
enta O
social O
media O
to O
show O
dia O
frustration O
wit O
VAR O
, O
especially O
wen O
decision O
no O
favour O
dia O
team O
. O

Olakunle B-PER
Olusegun I-PER
na O
im O
score O
di O
only O
goal O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
wey O
be O
five O
time O
champions O
of O
di O
tournament O
. O

Ali B-PER
collect O
im O
title O
back O
to O
become O
di O
first O
fighter O
to O
win O
world O
heavyweight O
boxing O
title O
three O
times O
. O

I O
ready O
for O
watever O
go O
come O
my O
way O
. O
. O
. O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
na O
special O
place O
wia O
I O
go O
make O
history O
"""" O
Na O
wetin O
Ruiz B-PER
Jr I-PER
tok O
. O

Di O
American O
bin O
struggle O
for O
di O
fight O
as O
Ruiz B-PER
start O
strong O
for O
dia O
rematch O
fight O
wey O
happun O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

On O
12 B-DATE
June I-DATE
2019 I-DATE
, O
President O
Muhammadu B-PER
Buhari I-PER
officially O
add O
'Moshood B-PER
Abiola' I-PER
to O
di O
name O
'National B-LOC
Stadium' I-LOC
to O
take O
honour O
di O
late O
political O
big O
man O
and O
former O
presidential O
candidate O
wey O
pipo O
believe O
say O
win O
di O
1993 B-DATE
elections O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Super B-ORG
Falcons I-ORG
don O
troway O
dia O
chance O
to O
go O
Tokyo B-LOC
2020 B-DATE
Olympic O
Games O
afta O
Cote B-LOC
d' I-LOC
Ivoire I-LOC
waya O
dem O
1 O
- O
1 O
ontop O
home O
soil O
for O
second O
leg O
qualifier O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Catalonia B-LOC
- O
wey O
Barcelona B-ORG
dey O
based O
- O
na O
semi O
- O
autonomous O
region O
for O
north B-LOC
- I-LOC
east I-LOC
Spain I-LOC
and O
inside O
referendum O
wey O
dem O
do O
on O
1 B-DATE
October I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
, O
around O
90 O
% O
of O
Catalan O
votes O
support O
say O
make O
dem O
dey O
independent O
. O

For O
dia O
first O
World O
Cup O
for O
dis O
category O
, O
Cameroon B-LOC
komot O
for O
first O
round O
but O
deh O
no O
bin O
win O
de O
team O
. O

Shelly B-PER
- I-PER
Ann I-PER
Fraser I-PER
Pryce I-PER
win O
gold O
for O
di O
17th O
IAAF B-ORG
World O
Athletics O
Championships O
for O
Doha B-LOC
to O
become O
di O
first O
mama O
to O
win O
100m O
title O
since O
1995 B-DATE
. O

Di O
Jamaican O
run O
her O
fastest O
race O
in O
six B-DATE
years I-DATE
wit O
time O
of O
10 B-DATE
. I-DATE
71 I-DATE
seconds I-DATE
to O
win O
her O
eight O
world O
title O
. O

"""" O
We O
dey O
look O
at O
how O
woman O
go O
fit O
fight O
as O
part O
of O
di O
undercard O
, O
"""" O
im O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
5 O
Live O
Boxing O
. O

Di O
International B-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
( O
ILO B-ORG
) O
say O
work O
no O
sure O
again O
for O
about O
1 O
. O
6 O
billion O
workers O
on O
top O
say O
430 O
million O
businesses O
dey O
in O
big O
trouble O
. O

Pipo O
wey O
dey O
stay O
for O
wia O
dem O
plenti O
for O
dia O
fit O
spread O
coronavirus O
faster O
so O
di O
wahala O
now O
be O
say O
as O
dem O
lockdown O
dey O
end O
how O
dem O
go O
do O
normal O
life O
safely O
. O

Iran B-LOC
announce O
say O
dem O
go O
open O
mosques O
for O
parts O
of O
di O
kontri O
health O
authorities O
say O
dey O
free O
of O
coronavirus O
but O
say O
make O
dme O
do O
social O
distancing O
when O
dem O
go O
to O
pray O
. O

Dis O
na O
one O
of O
di O
biggest O
events O
of O
di O
year O
, O
e O
dey O
mark O
di O
birth O
of O
di O
founder O
of O
di O
nation O
. O

But O
dem O
never O
see O
am O
since O
. O

E O
dey O
important O
to O
note O
say O
nobody O
don O
deny O
say O
Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
undergo O
heart O
surgery O
. O

Evritin O
look O
great O
from O
di O
outside O
: O
smiling O
faces O
, O
friends O
, O
plenti O
moni O
, O
happiness O
and O
confidence O
. O

My O
parents O
tell O
me O
say O
I O
go O
need O
comot O
for O
house O
immediately O
I O
start O
to O
dey O
date O
anyone O
. O

I O
be O
dey O
feel O
small O
, O
weak O
and O
I O
no O
fit O
escape O
. O

Afta O
dat O
I O
go O
dey O
waka O
di O
town O
upandan O
. O

You O
no O
dey O
see O
di O
way O
out O
and O
you O
no O
dey O
hear O
from O
anyone O
. O

But O
on O
top O
one O
or O
two O
digging O
dem O
find O
dia O
identity O
and O
like O
day O
, O
Sita B-PER
turn O
di O
face O
of O
coronavirus O
for O
Indonesia B-LOC
. O

Na O
when O
Tyasutami B-PER
insist O
say O
make O
dem O
do O
her O
Covid O
- O
19 O
test O
and O
dem O
come O
transfer O
dem O
go O
Sulianti B-ORG
Saroso I-ORG
, O
Jakarta's B-LOC
infectious O
disease O
hospital O
, O
for O
di O
test O
. O

Bollywood B-ORG
actor O
Irrfan B-PER
Khan I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
popular O
around O
di O
world O
for O
di O
role O
wey O
im O
play O
for O
Slumdog O
Millionaire O
and O
Jurassic O
World O
don O
die O
at O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
53 I-DATE
. O

Dem O
must O
also O
submit O
di O
names O
and O
phone O
numbers O
of O
every O
pesin O
wey O
attend O
di O
party O
. O

Di O
actor O
write O
say O
"""" O
I O
feel O
ok O
, O
I O
no O
get O
symptoms O
so O
far O
but O
i O
don O
isolate O
mysef O
since O
I O
found O
out O
about O
my O
possible O
exposure O
to O
di O
virus O
. O
. O
. O
"""" O
Model O
and O
now O
actress O
, O
Olga B-PER
Kurylenko I-PER
, O
wey O
don O
act O
for O
films O
like O
'Quantum O
of O
Solace' O
and O
'Oblivion' O
also O
reveal O
for O
Instagram O
say O
she O
dey O
quarantined O
for O
house O
afta O
she O
test O
positive O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
. O

She O
say O
she O
go O
"""" O
like O
make O
di O
executive O
give O
us O
criteria O
wey O
dem O
tak O
choose O
our O
patron O
. O

He O
say O
wetin O
pipo O
dey O
tok O
about O
"""" O
no O
count O
"""" O
. O

Angelique B-PER
Kidjo I-PER
from O
Benin B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
na O
anoda O
pesin O
wey O
also O
dey O
dis O
same O
award O
category O
wit O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
. O

Di O
72 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
star O
wey O
still O
be O
one O
of O
di O
most O
in O
demand O
live O
musicians O
for O
world O
receive O
plenti O
sympathy O
for O
social O
media O
from O
im O
fans O
. O

Di O
tour O
promoters O
for O
im O
next O
show O
for O
Auckland B-LOC
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
and O
Thursday B-DATE
go O
hold O
as O
dem O
plan O
am O
. O

Di O
25 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
pop O
star O
don O
tok O
about O
im O
drug O
abuse O
and O
abusing O
im O
relationship O
before O
, O
but O
dis O
latest O
video O
na O
di O
first O
time O
e O
dey O
tok O
about O
am O
for O
camera O
. O

Di O
mata O
make O
pipo O
start O
to O
dey O
bring O
dia O
own O
reasoning O
on O
top O
wetin O
fit O
don O
cause O
authorities O
to O
remove O
di O
movie O
as O
tori O
bin O
start O
to O
dey O
trend O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
banned O
. O

( O
Rest O
in O
peace O
, O
fada O
, O
your O
race O
don O
complete O
. O
) O

Dem O
born O
Joseph B-PER
Shabalala I-PER
for O
1941 B-DATE
and O
e O
be O
di O
eldest O
of O
eight O
children O
wey O
dey O
live O
for O
one O
farm O
inside O
Tugela B-LOC
, O
near O
di O
town O
of O
Ladysmith B-LOC
inside O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

Dis O
33 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
MC O
from O
Bayelsa B-LOC
State I-LOC
say O
di O
only O
tins O
wey O
im O
need O
for O
im O
relationship O
na O
quality O
time O
and O
personal O
touchy O
- O
touchy O
. O

Dem O
born O
Erivo B-PER
to O
Nigerian O
parents O
for O
Stockwell B-LOC
, O
London B-LOC
for O
1987 B-DATE
. O

TZ B-LOC
] O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
BlaqBonez B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Falz B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
KHALIGRAPH B-PER
Jones I-PER
( O
KE B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Kwesta B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Medikal B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Shinski B-PER
( O
KE B-LOC
) O
Sarkodie B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Reminisce B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Ricky B-PER
Rick I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Zakwe B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Black B-PER
Motion I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Blaq B-PER
diamond I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
DopeNation B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Ethic B-PER
( O
KE B-LOC
) O
Show B-PER
Dem I-PER
Camp I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Toofan B-PER
( O
TG B-LOC
) O
Cracker B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Prince B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Jay B-PER
Synth I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Kel B-PER
P I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
MOG B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Ozedikus B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Olympics O
go O
start O
for O
July B-DATE
and O
end O
for O
August B-DATE
. O

Dis O
go O
be O
test O
for O
di O
local O
organising O
committee O
and O
preparation O
to O
host O
di O
African O
Nations O
Cup O
for O
2021 B-DATE
. O

Di O
National B-ORG
Council I-ORG
for I-ORG
Art I-ORG
and I-ORG
Culture I-ORG
( O
NCAC B-ORG
) O
on O
Friday B-DATE
defend O
di O
reason O
why O
dem O
close O
di O
Art B-LOC
and I-LOC
Craft I-LOC
Village I-LOC
( O
AVC B-LOC
) O
. O

Di O
case O
na O
for O
di O
sealing O
of O
di O
Arts B-LOC
and I-LOC
Craft I-LOC
village I-LOC
for O
Abuja B-LOC
. O

Akon B-PER
bin O
first O
announce O
im O
plans O
for O
di O
"""" O
crypto O
city O
"""" O
for O
2018 B-DATE
for O
di O
Cannes B-LOC
Lion O
Festival O
for O
France B-LOC
, O
wen O
im O
launch O
di O
crypto O
- O
currency O
wey O
di O
city O
go O
dey O
use O
, O
AKoin O
. O

Di O
day O
also O
get O
religious O
connections O
and O
dem O
dey O
celebrate O
am O
as O
Saint B-DATE
Stephen's I-DATE
Day I-DATE
for O
Ireland B-LOC
and O
DI O
Catalonia B-LOC
region I-LOC
of O
Spain B-LOC
. O

Na O
also O
day O
to O
continue O
all O
di O
chopping O
because O
many O
pipo O
dey O
prepare O
so O
much O
food O
for O
Christmas B-DATE
wey O
dem O
go O
end O
up O
eating O
throughout O
di O
next B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

But O
Bumble O
don O
tok O
say O
dem O
don O
now O
unblock O
Stone B-PER
account O
so O
she O
go O
fit O
go O
"""" O
back O
to O
Bumbling O
"""" O
. O

Na O
since O
2014 B-DATE
, O
she O
don O
tok O
say O
she O
dey O
available O
for O
dating O
and O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
she O
say O
she O
like O
for O
her O
men O
to O
dey O
tall O
. O

Plenti O
pipo O
wey O
go O
di O
event O
post O
about O
di O
tins O
dem O
eye O
see O
for O
di O
show O
. O

Tamara B-PER
na O
di O
daughter O
of O
former O
Formula O
1 O
oga O
Bernie B-PER
Ecclestone I-PER
. O

According O
to O
tori O
pipo O
The B-ORG
Sun I-ORG
, O
rings O
, O
earrings O
, O
one O
Cartier B-PER
bangle O
wey O
reach O
£ O
80 O
, O
000 O
, O
wey O
her O
papa O
give O
her O
as O
wedding O
present O
dey O
among O
wetin O
dem O
tiff O
. O

Sheeran B-PER
also O
don O
win O
four O
Grammy O
Awards O
and O
e O
dey O
very O
popular O
with O
two O
of O
im O
ogbonge O
song O
wey O
be O
"""" O
Shape O
of O
You O
"""" O
and O
"""" O
Thinking O
Out O
Loud O
. O
"""" O

while O
ogbonge O
Congo O
musician O
, O
Awilo B-PER
Longomba I-PER
receive O
Special O
Recognition O
Award O
. O

House O
of O
Dragon O
go O
show O
wetin O
happun O
300 B-DATE
years I-DATE
before O
di O
tins O
wey O
shele O
for O
di O
original O
series O
, O
wey O
end O
afta O
eight O
seasons O
early O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

High O
Society O
na O
popular O
musical O
feem O
wey O
dem O
do O
for O
1957 B-DATE
and O
na O
Grace B-PER
Kelly I-PER
last O
work O
before O
she O
become O
princess O
of O
Monaco B-LOC
. O

Tori O
pipo O
The B-ORG
Wrap I-ORG
tok O
say O
di O
Academy O
tell O
voters O
say O
dem O
don O
disqualify O
di O
feem O
for O
email O
wey O
dem O
send O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Last B-DATE
month I-DATE
, O
di O
Academy O
announce O
say O
93 O
kontris O
submit O
dia O
films O
for O
di O
category O
and O
ten O
of O
di O
films O
come O
from O
Africa B-LOC
. O

Genevieve B-PER
Nnaji I-PER
tok O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
say O
di O
movie O
represent O
how O
we O
dey O
speak O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
how O
English O
be O
di O
bridge O
between O
all O
di O
languages O
for O
di O
kontri O
. O

For O
di O
15th B-DATE
year I-DATE
of O
di O
awards O
, O
actress O
and O
producer O
, O
Kemi B-PER
Lala I-PER
Akindoju I-PER
, O
Lorenzo B-PER
Menakaya I-PER
and O
comedian O
, O
Funnybone B-PER
na O
im O
host O
di O
AMAAs O
. O

Nigerians O
don O
arrange O
demselves O
for O
social O
media O
and O
real O
world O
dey O
chill O
to O
see O
wetin O
go O
happun O
for O
di O
Headies O
2019 B-DATE
. O

Although O
e O
no O
be O
new O
tin O
for O
di O
Headies O
to O
use O
pipo O
wey O
no O
dey O
di O
industry O
to O
present O
awards O
. O

Di O
musician O
win O
Best O
Grime O
Act O
for O
di O
2014 B-DATE
and O
2015 B-DATE
MOBO O
Awards O
. O

British O
born O
Nigeria B-LOC
actor O
27 B-DATE
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
John B-PER
Boyega I-PER
, O
worth O
£ O
6 O
. O
6m O
pounds O
to O
make O
number O
21 O
for O
di O
list O
. O

Pipo O
like O
Bernardine B-PER
Evaristo I-PER
wey O
win O
di O
Booker O
Prize O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
and O
Oyinkan B-PER
Braithwaite I-PER
, O
wey O
get O
one O
of O
di O
best O
selling O
books O
of O
di O
year O
. O

Music O
na O
correct O
part O
of O
di O
festival O
and O
some O
correct O
artists O
go O
perform O
for O
di O
event O
like O
Temmie B-PER
Ovwasa I-PER
from O
YBNL B-ORG
and O
Ibejii B-PER
. O

"""" O
Nor O
worry O
, O
everytin O
dey O
OK O
, O
no O
be O
your O
fault O
, O
"""" O
she O
tok O
, O
she O
also O
add O
say O
: O
"""" O
You O
fit O
promise O
me O
something O
? O

In O
fact O
, O
one O
fan O
open O
GoFundme B-ORG
page O
for O
am O
, O
as O
means O
to O
get O
di O
money O
wey O
she O
suppose O
win O
. O

Some O
even O
tok O
say O
dem O
don O
dey O
wait O
for O
am O
to O
tok O
sumtin O
wey O
go O
make O
dem O
find O
fault O
for O
her O
side O
. O

For O
tweet O
wey O
she O
don O
delete O
, O
she O
tok O
say O
"""" O
Marvel B-ORG
and O
DC B-ORG
are O
killing O
it O
in O
inclusion O
and O
women O
but O
wia O
di O
Latinos O
dem O
? O
! O

