On O
di O
first O
day O
, O
di O
number O
one O
lightweight O
fighter O
Tony B-PER
Ferguson I-PER
go O
face O
number O
four O
Justin B-PER
Gaethje I-PER
, O
for O
di O
UFC B-ORG
banterweight O
Championship O
wia O
Henry B-PER
Cejudo I-PER
dey O
look O
to O
flog O
multiple O
- O
time O
title O
holder O
Dominick B-PER
Cruz I-PER
. O

Di O
return O
of O
German O
football O
Bundesliga O
competition O
dey O
currently O
under O
discussion O
for O
one O
news O
conference O
wey O
di O
governing O
body O
dey O
hold O
. O

Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
team O
dey O
train O
for O
dia O
house O
as O
football O
dey O
suspended O
sake O
of O
coronavirus O
pandemic O
. O

"""" O
Di O
nutritionist O
put O
di O
boys O
for O
one O
Instagram O
page O
wia O
dem O
go O
take O
cooking O
lessons O
, O
so O
a O
lot O
of O
dem O
don O
start O
to O
dey O
develop O
new O
skill O
- O
and O
one O
or O
two O
of O
dem O
don O
get O
injury O
. O
"""" O

Two O
rival O
clubs O
Dortmund B-ORG
and O
Schalke B-ORG
go O
jam O
inside O
one O
of O
di O
six O
Saturday B-DATE
matches O
wey O
dem O
go O
play O
for O
stadium O
wey O
no O
get O
fans O
inside O
. O

Popular O
cable O
satellite O
broadcaster O
DsTV B-ORG
, O
no O
get O
right O
to O
Bundesliga O
live O
matches O
for O
di O
2019 B-DATE
/ I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
season O
so O
na O
pipo O
wey O
get O
StarTimes B-ORG
dey O
in O
luck O
because O
na O
dem O
get O
broadcast O
rights O
for O
Sub B-LOC
- I-LOC
Saharan I-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

If O
no O
be O
for O
di O
break O
wey O
Coronavirus O
cause O
. O

Germany B-LOC
top O
football O
league O
- O
Bundesliga O
- O
don O
confam O
say O
football O
action O
go O
return O
on O
16 B-DATE
May I-DATE
, O
as O
dem O
go O
become O
di O
first O
major O
football O
league O
to O
restart O
afta O
di O
coronavirus O
lockdown O
. O

Conditions O
Di O
Premier O
League O
, O
wey O
be O
di O
league O
wey O
football O
fans O
dey O
watch O
pass O
for O
di O
world O
no O
go O
resume O
anytime O
before O
1 B-DATE
June I-DATE
, O
afta O
di O
British O
goment O
on O
Monday B-DATE
comot O
to O
say O
no O
sport O
event O
fit O
hold O
in O
di O
kontri O
before O
dis O
date O
. O

Dis O
don O
vex O
some O
clubs O
wey O
dey O
bottom O
and O
di O
mata O
don O
even O
turn O
to O
court O
mata O
. O

So O
maybe O
dem O
go O
soon O
announce O
dia O
own O
date O
. O

He O
lift O
di O
barbell O
for O
two B-DATE
seconds I-DATE
, O
before O
im O
drop O
drop O
di O
weights O
. O

But O
I O
also O
get O
plenti O
support O
. O
"""" O

Ighalo B-PER
wey O
join O
United B-ORG
on O
loan O
from O
China B-LOC
club O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
dey O
15th O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Sunday B-ORG
Times I-ORG
Rich O
List O
. O

Top O
of O
di O
list O
of O
sports O
stars O
wey O
dey O
30 B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
below O
na O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
player O
, O
Gareth B-PER
Bale I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
valued O
at O
£ O
114m O
. O

Di O
Ligue O
1 O
and O
Ligue O
2 O
seasons O
no O
go O
resume O
afta O
France B-LOC
don O
ban O
all O
sporting O
events O
, O
plus O
di O
one O
wey O
dem O
wan O
do O
behind O
closed O
doors O
, O
until O
September B-DATE
. O

Di O
top O
five O
sides O
for O
Ligue O
2 O
dey O
separated O
by O
just O
four O
points O
, O
with O
Lorient B-ORG
and O
Lens B-ORG
currently O
dey O
occupy O
di O
automatic O
promotion O
spots O
. O

Di O
head O
of O
di O
Dutch B-ORG
FA I-ORG
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
say O
im O
tink O
say O
e O
dey O
"""" O
very O
doubtful O
"""" O
say O
Premier O
League O
go O
fit O
complete O
di O
2019 B-DATE
- I-DATE
20 I-DATE
campaign O
. O

But O
di O
first O
match O
go O
be O
Köln B-ORG
vs O
Mainz B-ORG
by O
2 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30pm I-DATE
Sunday I-DATE
. O

Add O
to O
empty O
stadium O
, O
some O
goals O
na O
social O
- O
distancing O
alias O
dey O
your O
lane O
dem O
use O
celebrate O
. O

Police O
make O
sure O
say O
fans O
no O
gada O
outside O
. O

Discussions O
go O
cover O
all O
domestic O
and O
European O
competitions O
, O
including O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
. O

For O
Italy B-LOC
, O
Serie O
A O
dey O
suspended O
until O
3 B-DATE
April I-DATE
, O
and O
di O
kontri O
dey O
on O
lockdown O
. O

For O
extra O
time O
Roberto B-PER
Firmino I-PER
score O
to O
make O
am O
2 O
- O
0 O
but O
di O
lead O
no O
last O
long O
. O

Already O
dis O
season O
dem O
don O
win O
di O
Uefa B-ORG
Super O
Cup O
and O
di O
Club O
World O
Cup O
title O
. O

Japan's B-LOC
Prime O
Minister O
Shinzo B-PER
Abe I-PER
say O
di O
International B-ORG
Olympic I-ORG
Committee I-ORG
don O
agree O
to O
di O
delay O
. O

Prime O
Minister O
Abe B-PER
add O
: O
"""" O
Dis O
go O
make O
am O
possible O
for O
athletes O
to O
play O
in O
di O
best O
condition O
, O
and O
will O
make O
di O
event O
a O
safe O
and O
secure O
place O
for O
spectators O
. O
"""" O

Di O
agreement O
come O
as O
di O
British B-ORG
Olympic I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
BOA B-ORG
) O
dey O
meet O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
to O
discuss O
di O
matter O
. O

Di O
Nigeria B-ORG
football I-ORG
federation I-ORG
say O
dem O
dey O
sad O
about O
di O
player O
death O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
international O
striker O
Ifeanyi B-PER
George I-PER
don O
die O
for O
motor O
accident O
at O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
26 I-DATE
. O

George B-PER
, O
wey O
get O
two O
caps O
for O
di O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
, O
dey O
involved O
for O
one O
accident O
wey O
happun O
for O
Benin B-LOC
- I-LOC
Agbor I-LOC
road I-LOC
wen O
im O
dey O
travel O
to O
Lagos B-LOC
on O
Sunday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
. O

Dem O
bin O
postpone O
di O
fight O
on O
top O
di O
coronavirus O
palava O
for O
world O
. O

Dis O
dey O
come O
from O
statement O
from O
Joshua B-PER
promoter O
Matchroom B-ORG
Boxing I-ORG
wey O
tok O
say O
dem O
dey O
work O
on O
new O
date O
for O
di O
fight O
. O

Di O
President O
of O
Gabon B-ORG
football I-ORG
federation I-ORG
Pierre B-PER
Alain I-PER
Mounguengui I-PER
, O
don O
advise O
Pierre B-PER
- I-PER
Emmerick I-PER
Aubamayeng I-PER
to O
comot O
Arsenal B-ORG
because O
im O
no O
go O
win O
anything O
dia O
. O

Aubamayeng B-PER
wey O
be O
Arsenal B-ORG
captain O
don O
build O
reputation O
as O
one O
of O
di O
world O
ogbonge O
forwards O
since O
im O
join O
from O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
for O
January B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
, O
and O
im O
next O
Premier O
League O
goal O
go O
be O
im O
50th O
for O
di O
competition O
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
wan O
say O
Arsenal B-ORG
no O
dey O
ginger O
, O
but O
Arsenal B-ORG
no O
get O
ambitions O
wey O
high O
as O
some O
oda O
clubs O
as O
far O
as O
Europe B-LOC
dey O
concerned O
, O
"""" O
President O
Mounguengui B-PER
tell O
ESPN B-ORG
. O

"""" O
On O
individual O
level O
, O
all O
of O
us O
sabi O
say O
im O
dey O
among O
di O
best O
players O
for O
di O
world O
. O

"""" O
But O
the O
advice O
I O
give O
am O
na O
to O
continue O
to O
work O
and O
to O
attract O
di O
attention O
of O
di O
biggest O
clubs O
and O
di O
most O
ambitious O
clubs O
. O
"""" O

No O
be O
only O
Mounguengui B-PER
get O
dis O
belief O
, O
- O
even O
Arsenal B-ORG
legend O
Ian B-PER
Wright I-PER
tok O
say O
Aubameyang B-PER
fit O
dey O
play O
at O
a O
higher O
level O
. O

"""" O
If O
you O
comot O
di O
goals O
out O
of O
dat O
team O
dendem O
dey O
for O
correct O
trouble O
. O
"""" O

Everton B-ORG
boss O
Carlo B-PER
Ancelotti I-PER
don O
tok O
say O
e O
go O
be O
emotional O
moment O
for O
am O
as O
e O
dey O
face O
Chelsea B-ORG
today B-DATE
for O
Stamford B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
. O

Di O
Italian O
spend O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
for O
Chelsea B-ORG
, O
wia O
im O
win O
di O
Premier O
League O
and O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
Double O
in O
2009 B-DATE
- I-DATE
10 I-DATE
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
very O
happy O
to O
get O
dis O
opportunity O
to O
show O
di O
world O
how O
strong O
I O
dey O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Pulev B-PER
tok O
. O

But O
Wilder B-PER
wey O
be O
American O
do O
use O
di O
rematch O
clause O
, O
wey O
mean O
say O
Fury B-PER
vs O
Wilder B-PER
part O
three O
go O
happun O
before O
Fury B-PER
and O
Joshua B-PER
go O
fight O
. O

Pulev B-PER
, O
na O
former O
European O
heavyweight O
champion O
. O

For O
2015 B-DATE
, O
im O
beat O
Britain B-LOC
Hughie B-PER
Fury I-PER
on O
points O
for O
IBF O
final O
eliminator O
for O
Bulgaria B-LOC
for O
October B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
, O
im O
first O
fight O
since O
im O
pull O
out O
of O
im O
original O
meeting O
with O
Joshua B-PER
. O

Tiamiyu B-PER
Fasasi I-PER
, O
wey O
bi O
Kazeem B-PER
papa O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Yoruba I-ORG
say O
e O
never O
reach O
like O
two B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
wen O
im O
pikin O
tell O
am O
say O
im O
get O
invitation O
to O
go O
play O
[ O
football O
] O
trial O
for O
Sweden B-LOC
. O

E O
say O
na O
on O
Friday B-DATE
, I-DATE
21 I-DATE
February I-DATE
Kazeem B-PER
say O
im O
dey O
go O
meet O
with O
im O
manager O
- O
wey O
arrive O
for O
Sagamu B-LOC
- O
ontop O
di O
Sweden B-LOC
mata O
. O

Kazeem B-PER
mama O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
how O
e O
don O
promise O
her O
better O
life O
as O
thank O
you O
for O
all O
di O
wahala O
she O
suffer O
ontop O
dem O
. O

If O
na O
N1000 O
dey O
Kazeem B-PER
account O
and O
pesin O
ask O
am O
for O
N900 O
, O
e O
go O
give O
am O
, O
"""" O
na O
im O
Selimotu B-PER
Tiamiyu I-PER
tok O
about O
her O
son O
. O

Tori O
break O
ontop O
social O
media O
afta O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
football O
club O
release O
statement O
say O
SARS B-ORG
Police O
harass O
dia O
player O
Kazeem B-PER
wey O
lead O
to O
im O
death O
for O
Sagamu B-LOC
, O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
22 I-DATE
February I-DATE
. O

Im O
tell O
Spanish O
tori O
pipo O
AS O
: O
"""" O
Right O
now O
I O
dey O
City B-ORG
and O
I O
dey O
really O
happy O
. O

Dem O
ask O
am O
weda O
im O
go O
like O
play O
for O
Real B-ORG
, O
im O
tok O
say O
: O
"""" O
How O
I O
go O
carry O
answer O
dis O
one O
? O

Di O
camera O
dey O
live O
or O
e O
just O
dey O
take O
pictures O
? O
"""" O

Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
manager O
Pep B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
say O
im O
players O
dey O
"""" O
free O
to O
tok O
as O
e O
be O
. O

We O
no O
dey O
here O
to O
tell O
them O
wetin O
dem O
need O
to O
tok O
"""" O
. O

Sterling B-PER
don O
score O
11 O
goals O
dis O
season O
. O

Fury B-PER
from O
Britain B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

Wilder B-PER
say O
di O
costume O
, O
wey O
dem O
sew O
plenty O
tins O
ontop O
am O
, O
also O
come O
wit O
mask O
and O
crown O
, O
weigh O
at O
least O
18 O
. O
1kg O
and O
na O
tribute O
to O
Black B-DATE
History I-DATE
Month I-DATE
. O

Fury B-PER
on O
di O
oda O
hand O
no O
use O
im O
leg O
waka O
enta O
ring O
as O
im O
sidon O
ontop O
throne O
wey O
four O
pipo O
carri O
. O

Although O
dem O
carri O
Wilder B-PER
go O
hospital O
after O
di O
fight O
, O
e O
say O
im O
no O
get O
concussion O
, O
say O
im O
ear O
drum O
no O
bust O
or O
im O
jaw O
break O
, O
like O
di O
way O
pipo O
dey O
tok O
. O

Former O
Brazil B-LOC
forward O
Ronaldinho B-PER
dey O
police O
custody O
for O
Paraguay B-LOC
ontop O
accuse O
say O
im O
use O
fake O
passport O
enta O
di O
kontri O
, O
according O
to O
authorities O
. O

Paraguay B-LOC
interior O
minister O
bin O
tell O
ESPN B-ORG
Brazil I-ORG
say O
dem O
never O
arrest O
di O
two O
of O
dem O
but O
dem O
dey O
under O
investigation O
. O

Minister O
Euclides B-PER
Acevedo I-PER
also O
confam O
say O
di O
brothers O
don O
deny O
di O
accuse O
and O
dem O
dey O
co O
- O
operate O
wit O
authorities O
. O

Di O
39 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
win O
World O
Player O
Of O
The O
Year O
two O
times O
( O
2004 B-DATE
and O
2005 B-DATE
) O
and O
im O
win O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2002 B-DATE
wit O
fellow O
superstar O
strikers O
Ronaldo B-PER
and O
Rivaldo B-PER
. O

Report O
bin O
say O
she O
jump O
comot O
from O
car O
dey O
shout O
: O
"""" O
E O
pour O
me O
petrol O
"""" O
. O

"""" O
Dis O
na O
horrific O
scene O
, O
"""" O
Det O
Insp O
Mark B-PER
Thompson I-PER
tel O
tori O
pipo O
: O
"""" O
We O
still O
dey O
investigate O
di O
mata O
, O
but O
wen O
police O
reach O
di O
crime O
scene O
di O
car O
dey O
burn O
. O

Police O
find O
Rowan B-PER
Baxter I-PER
, O
42 B-DATE
, O
and O
im O
three O
pikin O
- O
age B-DATE
three I-DATE
, O
four B-DATE
and O
six B-DATE
- O
wey O
don O
die O
inside O
di O
car O
. O

She O
bin O
dey O
critical O
condition O
wen O
dem O
cari O
her O
go O
Royal B-ORG
Brisbane I-ORG
and I-ORG
Women's I-ORG
Hospital I-ORG
, O
police O
tok O
. O

But O
dem O
confam O
am O
say O
she O
later O
die O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
and O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
go O
face O
each O
oda O
again O
for O
early O
mor O
- O
mor O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
, O
almost O
15 B-DATE
months I-DATE
afta O
dia O
last O
fight O
end O
for O
draw O
for O
Los B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC
. O

If O
Fury B-PER
win O
am O
e O
mean O
say O
all O
four O
heavyweight O
belts O
go O
dey O
shared O
between O
two O
British O
fighters O
- O
him O
and O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
, O
go O
hold O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBA O
and O
WBO O
titles O
. O

Dis O
na O
everything O
you O
need O
to O
know O
about O
di O
fight O
. O

Na O
few O
tickets O
remain O
for O
di O
fight O
wey O
go O
happun O
for O
MGM B-LOC
Grand I-LOC
Garden I-LOC
Arena I-LOC
, O
di O
ticket O
prize O
na O
from O
$ O
425 O
( O
£ O
330 O
) O
for O
open O
market O
to O
$ O
10 O
, O
000 O
( O
£ O
7 O
, O
754 O
) O
for O
black O
market O
. O

In O
terms O
of O
money O
for O
di O
two O
men O
dia O
money O
fit O
reach O
eight O
- O
figure O
for O
dat O
night B-DATE
alone O
. O

Im O
5 O
Live O
Boxing O
sidekick O
Steve B-PER
Bunce I-PER
add O
say O
: O
"""" O
Two O
men O
wey O
dey O
unbeaten O
, O
elite O
versus O
elite O
. O

Make O
wey O
no O
forget O
say O
we O
dey O
see O
something O
wey O
we O
no O
dey O
every O
day O
. O

I O
know O
when O
im O
go O
catch O
Fury B-PER
but O
I O
feel O
say O
im O
go O
catch O
am O
. O
"""" O

Bunce B-PER
respond O
: O
"""" O
I O
feel O
say O
we O
go O
see O
Wilder B-PER
box O
small O
and O
Fury B-PER
go O
dey O
more O
aggressive O
. O

Wilder B-PER
neva O
too O
change O
, O
so O
di O
result O
of O
dis O
fight O
go O
depend O
on O
di O
success O
of O
failure O
of O
di O
changes O
Fury B-PER
don O
make O
. O

SugarHill B-PER
Steward I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
policeman O
before O
, O
dey O
call O
imself O
"""" O
di O
knockout O
architect O
"""" O
, O
afta O
im O
learn O
how O
to O
box O
for O
di O
legendary O
Detroit B-ORG
Kronk I-ORG
Gym I-ORG
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
go O
host O
CHAN O
2020 B-DATE
from O
4 B-DATE
- I-DATE
25 I-DATE
April I-DATE
and O
na O
one O
of O
de O
kontris O
for O
announce O
say O
two O
pipo O
don O
test O
positive O
for O
coronavirus O
recently O
. O

Eight O
major O
football O
kontris O
for O
Africa B-LOC
don O
already O
get O
de O
virus O
: O
Egypt B-LOC
, O
Algeria B-LOC
, O
Tunisia B-LOC
, O
Morocco B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
Senegal B-LOC
, O
Cameroon B-LOC
and O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

Di O
incident O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
for O
di O
stadium O
car O
park O
. O

While O
di O
injured O
Terville B-ORG
player O
chop O
six B-DATE
months I-DATE
suspension O
. O

Dis O
don O
end O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
five B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
reign O
as O
WBC O
heavyweight O
world O
champion O
. O

"""" O
Di O
best O
man O
na O
im O
win O
dis O
night B-DATE
. O

E O
give O
shout O
out O
to O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
and O
also O
call O
am O
'Warrior O
. O

Fury B-PER
later O
tell O
tori O
pipo O
say O
im O
dey O
"""" O
expect O
Wilder B-PER
to O
ask O
for O
di O
third O
fight O
. O

Haye B-PER
tell O
BT B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
Box I-ORG
Office I-ORG
. O

Oda O
pipo O
for O
twitter B-ORG
no O
fit O
hide O
dia O
surprise O
and O
joy O
. O

Ighalo B-PER
, O
30 B-DATE
, O
dey O
expected O
to O
travel O
with O
di O
squad O
for O
Monday B-DATE
game O
against O
Chelsea B-ORG
. O

Ighalo B-PER
join O
United B-ORG
on O
loan O
for O
di O
rest O
of O
di O
season O
from O
China B-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
club O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
. O

NFF B-ORG
announce O
dis O
appointment O
for O
inside O
statement O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Yobo B-PER
wey O
play O
100 O
matches O
for O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
also O
play O
for O
Everton B-ORG
, O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
, O
Marseille B-ORG
, O
Standard B-ORG
Liege I-ORG
and O
Norwich B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

Turkey B-LOC
club O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
don O
condemn O
racial O
abuse O
wey O
former O
Nigeria B-LOC
captain O
John B-PER
Mikel I-PER
Obi I-PER
receive O
for O
dia O
win O
over O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

Di O
club O
say O
dem O
don O
file O
"""" O
criminal O
complain O
"""" O
against O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
responsible O
. O

"""" O
Racism O
na O
shelter O
for O
di O
helpless O
and O
ignorant O
, O
"""" O
na O
so O
Trabzonsport B-ORG
tok O
for O
statement O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

Dem O
don O
kick O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
comot O
from O
Champions O
League O
until O
2022 B-DATE
. O

Guardiola B-PER
feel O
say O
dem O
disappoint O
am O
by O
dis O
decision O
? O

E O
no O
dey O
possible O
to O
say O
. O

As O
e O
be O
so O
, O
e O
hard O
to O
imagine O
say O
im O
go O
stay O
with O
all O
di O
rumours O
wey O
dey O
fly O
upandan O
say O
Juventus B-ORG
want O
am O
. O

Wetin O
go O
determine O
di O
future O
of O
Guardiola B-PER
for O
Man B-ORG
City I-ORG
na O
if O
di O
club O
dey O
succesful O
for O
dia O
appeal O
against O
UEFA B-ORG
. O

Striker O
Sergio B-PER
Aguero I-PER
dey O
top O
of O
dat O
list O
. O

And O
what O
about O
di O
stars O
wey O
dia O
contract O
dey O
go O
pass O
2022 B-DATE
, O
like O
Kevin B-PER
de I-PER
Bruyne I-PER
, O
Ederson B-PER
, O
Bernardo B-PER
Silva I-PER
, O
Raheem B-PER
Sterling I-PER
, O
Bernardo B-PER
Silva I-PER
and O
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
? O

If O
Guardiola B-PER
leave O
, O
e O
go O
easy O
to O
see O
plenti O
players O
follow O
am O
waka O
, O
and O
e O
fit O
make O
Man B-ORG
City I-ORG
begin O
build O
im O
team O
from O
di O
scratch O
. O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
brand O
new O
player O
, O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
say O
im O
dey O
so O
desperate O
to O
play O
for O
di O
club O
sotey O
im O
agree O
to O
half O
im O
salary O
to O
make O
di O
deal O
happun O
and O
im O
no O
sleep O
di O
night B-DATE
di O
agreement O
take O
place O
. O

I O
want O
to O
come O
here' O
, O
"""" O
Ighalo B-PER
add O
. O

"""" O
I O
come O
reply O
say O
: O
'I O
no O
care O
oh O
. O

Ighalo B-PER
say O
e O
don O
tey O
wey O
im O
na O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
fan O
, O
na O
since O
wen O
im O
be O
small O
boy O
and O
e O
dey O
happy O
say O
im O
dream O
to O
play O
for O
di O
Old B-LOC
Trafford I-LOC
club O
don O
come O
through O
. O

"""" O
I O
call O
my O
mama O
and O
she O
dey O
happy O
, O
she O
even O
cry O
"""" O
e O
tok O
. O

Di O
Nigerian O
striker O
fly O
from O
China B-LOC
come O
Manchester B-LOC
last B-DATE
weekend I-DATE
afta O
di O
club O
sign O
am O
on O
loan O
from O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
. O

United B-ORG
manager O
Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
tell O
MUTV B-ORG
say O
"""" O
Im O
for O
like O
come O
with O
di O
players O
so O
dat O
im O
go O
get O
to O
know O
dem O
, O
"""" O
. O

"""" O
But O
di O
risk O
[ O
of O
border O
restrictions O
wey O
don O
tight O
now O
] O
sake O
of O
di O
coronavirus O
we O
know O
want O
take O
chances O
. O
"""" O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
two O
clubs O
don O
dey O
negotiate O
throughout O
di O
transfer O
window O
until O
Tuesday B-DATE
wey O
dem O
get O
breakthrough O
afta O
reports O
begin O
fly O
up O
and O
down O
say O
Barcelona B-ORG
sef O
dey O
interested O
. O

"""" O
Belle O
dey O
sweet O
me O
well O
- O
well O
say O
we O
don O
agree O
[ O
deal O
] O
with O
Sporting B-ORG
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
United B-ORG
manager O
Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
tok O
. O

Di O
negotiation O
between O
di O
club O
dey O
good O
and O
we O
know O
say O
from O
time O
, O
dis O
two O
clubs O
don O
dey O
good O
to O
each O
oda O
. O

Fernandes B-PER
join O
Sporting B-ORG
from O
Sampdoria B-ORG
for O
£ O
7 O
. O
2m O
for O
2017 B-DATE
but O
before O
den O
, O
im O
no O
really O
dey O
popular O
for O
im O
homeland O
. O
"""" O

Fernandes B-PER
na O
di O
shinning O
light O
for O
Sporting B-ORG
, O
even O
though O
im O
bin O
struggle O
and O
e O
help O
Portugal B-LOC
to O
win O
Nation O
League O
for O
June B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
- O
di O
big O
question O
now O
na O
whether O
im O
fit O
deliver O
for O
United B-ORG
? O

Di O
pressure O
go O
increase O
, O
im O
opponents O
go O
dey O
stronger O
and O
im O
team O
- O
mates O
go O
dey O
better O
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
think O
say O
I O
fit O
say O
im O
don O
prove O
im O
self O
for O
di O
big O
European O
league O
yet O
but O
dat O
na O
di O
challenge O
. O

For O
Italy B-LOC
, O
im O
do O
well O
. O

Di O
wife O
of O
late O
Kobe B-PER
Bryant I-PER
, O
Vanessa B-PER
share O
foto O
of O
her O
daughter O
Gianna B-PER
"""" I-PER
Gigi I-PER
"""" I-PER
Bryant I-PER
, O
for O
social O
media O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

Dis O
her O
post O
dey O
come O
afta O
fans O
and O
celebs O
honour O
Kobe B-PER
for O
LA B-ORG
Lakers I-ORG
first O
basketball O
game O
for O
staple O
centre O
against O
Portland B-ORG
Trail I-ORG
Blazers I-ORG
. O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
manager O
Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
say O
"""" O
Odion B-PER
na O
experienced O
player O
, O
"""" O
"""" O
Im O
go O
come O
, O
come O
give O
us O
different O
option O
to O
type O
of O
strikers O
wey O
we O
get O
for O
di O
short O
time O
wey O
im O
go O
stay O
with O
us O
. O

Ighalo B-PER
move O
go O
Chinese B-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
for O
2017 B-DATE
, O
first O
with O
Changchun B-ORG
Yatai I-ORG
. O

David B-PER
Barmasai I-PER
from O
Kenya B-LOC
don O
win O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Lagos B-LOC
City O
Marathon O
. O

Oga O
Tumo B-PER
use O
two B-DATE
hour I-DATE
10 I-DATE
mins I-DATE
take O
finish O
di O
42km O
race O
wey O
start O
from O
National O
Stadium O
Surulere B-LOC
and O
end O
for O
Eko B-LOC
Atlantic I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
8 I-DATE
February I-DATE
Im O
fellow O
kontri O
woman O
Sharon B-PER
Cherop I-PER
carry O
first O
for O
female O
category O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
fourth O
edition O
of O
di O
marathon O
wey O
start O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
commercial O
capital O
city O
for O
2016 B-DATE
. O

Pellegrini B-PER
lose O
im O
West B-ORG
Ham I-ORG
job O
18 B-DATE
months I-DATE
afta O
dem O
employ O
am O
for O
2018 B-DATE
on O
three B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
deal O
, O
and O
dem O
tell O
am O
about O
im O
sack O
small O
time O
afta O
e O
do O
post O
- O
match O
interview O
finish O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

Na O
just O
40 B-DATE
seconds I-DATE
McGregor B-PER
use O
defeat O
am O
. O

I O
set O
new O
record O
. O

Di O
last O
time O
im O
win O
inside O
UFC B-ORG
octagon O
ring O
na O
wen O
e O
get O
im O
second O
UFC B-ORG
world O
title O
for O
November B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
, O
and O
afta O
undefeated O
UFC B-ORG
lightweight O
champion O
Khabib B-PER
Nurmagomedov I-PER
defeat O
am O
for O
UFC B-ORG
229 O
for O
October B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
. O

God O
willing O
, O
I O
come O
out O
with O
no O
injury O
. O

For O
di O
women O
category O
, O
Asisat B-PER
Oshoala I-PER
beat O
Ajara B-PER
Nchout I-PER
from O
Cameroon B-LOC
and O
Thembi B-PER
Kgatlana I-PER
from O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
to O
win O
her O
fourth O
African O
Women's O
Player O
of O
the O
Year O
. O

As O
2019 B-DATE
don O
end O
, O
Former O
Chelsea B-ORG
and O
Ghana B-LOC
star O
Michael B-PER
Essien I-PER
don O
choose O
im O
best O
11 O
African O
players O
from O
2010 B-DATE
to O
2019 B-DATE
. O

We O
ask O
Essien B-PER
who O
be O
im O
top O
players O
from O
di O
last O
decade O
. O

For O
club O
level O
, O
he O
was O
one O
of O
di O
first O
signings O
by O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
owners O
Sheikh B-PER
Mansour I-PER
which O
serve O
as O
star O
attraction O
for O
other O
big O
name O
players O
to O
arrive O
. O

Unfortunately O
for O
Assou B-PER
- I-PER
Ekotto I-PER
, O
knee O
surgery O
mean O
say O
im O
career O
go O
pay O
di O
price O
but O
e O
be O
pesin O
wey O
pass O
expectations O
and O
become O
di O
best O
African O
left O
- O
back O
for O
Premier O
League O
. O

Im O
help O
Senegal B-LOC
to O
reach O
dia O
first O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
final O
for O
over O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
dis O
year O
and O
many O
pipo O
regard O
am O
as O
one O
of O
di O
best O
centre O
- O
backs O
for O
modern O
day O
football O
. O

Di O
only O
reason O
e O
still O
dey O
Napoli B-ORG
na O
say O
di O
club O
owner O
turn O
down O
many O
offers O
from O
top O
European O
outfits O
so O
far O
. O

Essien B-PER
prowess O
begin O
to O
die O
down O
just O
for O
di O
turn O
of O
di O
decade O
with O
injuries O
taking O
dia O
toll O
but O
e O
bin O
still O
dey O
important O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
as O
dem O
qualify O
for O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
- O
e O
insists O
say O
im O
deserve O
place O
for O
e O
team O
of O
di O
decade O
! O

Yaya B-PER
don O
win O
di O
Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
African I-ORG
Football I-ORG
( O
Caf B-ORG
) O
African O
Player O
of O
the O
Year O
award O
four O
times O
in O
di O
last O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

E O
also O
score O
79 O
goals O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
di O
most O
by O
any O
midfielder O
for O
di O
club O
during O
dat O
period O
. O

E O
don O
score O
73 O
goals O
to O
help O
Jurgen B-PER
Klopp I-PER
men O
and O
bin O
dey O
instrumental O
in O
helping O
dem O
reach O
two O
European O
Champions O
League O
finals O
, O
winning O
di O
last O
edition O
. O

Mohamed B-PER
Salah I-PER
don O
net O
more O
than O
202 O
goals O
for O
club O
and O
kontri O
dis O
decade O
. O

For O
di O
year O
2012 B-DATE
, O
Didier B-PER
Drogba I-PER
cement O
e O
legendary O
status O
for O
European O
football O
as O
im O
score O
di O
equaliser O
and O
di O
winning O
penalty O
as O
Chelsea B-ORG
lift O
di O
European O
Champions O
League O
for O
di O
first O
time O
ever O
. O

Those O
feats O
see O
am O
win O
di O
fourth O
of O
e O
Caf B-ORG
African O
Player O
of O
the O
Year O
awards O
for O
2010 B-DATE
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
go O
fit O
continue O
to O
play O
like O
dat O
"""" O
dis O
na O
wetin O
Seven O
time O
champion O
Serena B-PER
Williams I-PER
tok O
afta O
she O
crash O
comot O
from O
Australian O
Open O
on O
Friday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
and O
lose O
6 O
- O
4 O
6 O
- O
7 O
( O
2 O
- O
7 O
) O
7 O
- O
5 O
to O
Wang B-PER
Qiang I-PER
from O
China B-LOC
for O
third O
round O
. O

Di O
last O
time O
wey O
38 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
Serena B-PER
win O
grand O
slam O
na O
2017 B-DATE
when O
she O
beat O
her O
sister O
for O
Australian O
Open O
final O
to O
win O
her O
23rd O
title O
and O
na O
di O
same B-DATE
year I-DATE
she O
born O
her O
daughter O
too O
. O

Leicester B-ORG
manage O
to O
match O
brake O
for O
di O
ginger O
wey O
Brentford B-ORG
carri O
come O
for O
second O
half O
of O
dem O
two O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
fourth O
round O
match O
. O

Di O
oda O
team O
worry O
us O
well O
well O
. O

Fear O
catch O
me O
small O
because O
dem O
just O
dey O
come O
dey O
come O
. O

Dem O
find O
levels O
of O
di O
hormone O
cortisol O
wey O
bin O
go O
up O
for O
dia O
bodi O
during O
di O
7 O
- O
1 O
home O
defeat O
for O
di O
semi O
- O
final O
. O

High O
levels O
of O
cortisol O
wey O
don O
tey O
for O
bodi O
fit O
: O
Cortisol O
wey O
don O
raise O
fit O
also O
give O
pipo O
di O
feeling O
say O
bad O
tin O
wan O
happun O
, O
say O
dia O
life O
dey O
in O
danger O
and O
dem O
dey O
under O
attack O
. O

Di O
one O
wey O
dey O
stressful O
pass O
na O
di O
semi O
- O
final O
. O

"""" O
Na O
match O
wey O
dem O
waya O
dem O
- O
so O
many O
pipo O
comot O
dey O
cry O
, O
"""" O
Dr O
Newson B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
. O

"""" O
Clubs O
fit O
dey O
do O
heart O
screening O
or O
oda O
health O
measures O
for O
dia O
fans O
wey O
dey O
committed O
because O
na O
dem O
dey O
at O
risk O
to O
experience O
stress O
during O
di O
game O
, O
"""" O
she O
add O
. O

Di O
detail O
bin O
no O
clear O
, O
but O
e O
clear O
say O
sometin O
serious O
don O
happun O
. O

I O
ask O
to O
speak O
to O
someone O
, O
dem O
immediately O
tell O
me O
say O
di O
team O
tok O
- O
tok O
pesin O
na O
dia O
best O
- O
known O
player O
- O
wey O
be O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
star O
Emmanuel B-PER
Adebayor I-PER
. O

10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
afta O
, O
dis O
na O
di O
tori O
from O
team O
members O
wey O
make O
global O
headlines O
and O
wetin O
happun O
afta O
. O

Togo B-LOC
squad O
bin O
dey O
in O
good O
spirits O
days O
before O
di O
2010 B-DATE
Nations O
Cup O
. O

Dis O
decision O
later O
end O
with O
bad O
result O
. O

Looking O
back O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
midfielder O
Junior B-PER
Senaya I-PER
recall O
di O
journey O
, O
and O
di O
moment O
everitin O
change O
. O

Den O
serious O
shooting O
start O
. O
"""" O

Dem O
shoot O
kill O
am O
. O

"""" O
I O
hear O
di O
sound O
of O
di O
machine O
gun O
, O
"""" O
Im O
tok O
, O
"""" O
and O
for O
dat O
very O
moment O
I O
bin O
want O
move O
go O
hide O
, O
e O
bin O
dey O
as O
if O
dem O
nail O
me O
to O
chair O
. O

"""" O
Dat O
na O
wen O
I O
see O
myself O
- O
both O
my O
belle O
and O
my O
back O
begin O
bleed O
. O

Im O
remember O
as O
assistant O
coach O
Amelete B-PER
Abalo I-PER
shout O
say O
dem O
don O
shoot O
am O
- O
di O
54 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- O
na O
one O
of O
di O
pipo O
wey O
die O
for O
di O
attack O
. O

Memories O
of O
how O
long O
e O
last O
dey O
different O
, O
but O
everyone O
agree O
say O
na O
at O
least O
30 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
e O
last O
. O

"""" O
No O
be O
like O
say O
one O
or O
two O
guys O
shoot O
one O
or O
two O
times O
on O
our O
bus O
, O
"""" O
Adebayor B-PER
tell O
me O
afta O
im O
don O
dey O
safe O
place O
for O
di O
team O
hotel O
few O
hours O
afta O
di O
attack O
. O

"""" O
Wen O
I O
come O
out O
, O
I O
see O
all O
di O
players O
, O
and O
everyone O
bin O
dey O
cry O
, O
everyone O
bin O
dey O
tok O
about O
dia O
family O
, O
calling O
pipo O
, O
calling O
dia O
mama O
, O
dey O
cry O
for O
phone O
. O

Officials O
, O
goment O
ministers O
and O
representatives O
of O
di O
Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
African I-ORG
Football I-ORG
fly O
in O
from O
Angola B-LOC
capital O
Luanda B-LOC
, O
wit O
questions O
about O
wetin O
happen O
, O
who O
dey O
responsible O
, O
and O
why O
- O
for O
sometin O
wey O
go O
against O
tournament O
rules O
- O
Togo B-LOC
decide O
to O
drive O
instead O
of O
fly O
. O

Anoda O
question O
lie O
for O
di O
presence O
Angolan O
security O
wey O
travel O
with O
di O
team O
. O

And O
na O
di O
militarised O
escort O
cause O
di O
attack O
? O

None O
of O
dis O
questions O
get O
clear O
answers O
, O
even O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
on O
- O
and O
at O
di O
time O
di O
most O
immediate O
issue O
for O
di O
players O
na O
to O
absorb O
wetin O
don O
happen O
to O
dem O
and O
decide O
wetin O
to O
do O
next O
. O

For O
several O
days O
e O
no O
dey O
clear O
to O
those O
of O
us O
wey O
watch O
from O
di O
outside O
wetin O
go O
happen O
. O

Initially O
tori O
spread O
say O
im O
die O
too O
. O

Since O
den O
e O
don O
face O
eight O
major O
operations O
and O
don O
get O
to O
rebuild O
e O
life O
, O
physically O
and O
emotionally O
. O

I O
go O
back O
to O
school O
, O
take O
exams O
, O
work O
and O
write O
book O
, O
"""" O
im O
tok O
. O

For O
long O
time O
im O
work O
wit O
children O
with O
special O
needs O
, O
as O
e O
help O
dem O
through O
di O
medium O
of O
football O
, O
and O
e O
don O
set O
up O
e O
own O
organisation O
to O
continue O
dat O
work O
. O

Obilale B-PER
lose O
e O
livelihood O
- O
and O
almost O
e O
life O
- O
for O
Cabinda B-LOC
and O
e O
dey O
striking O
say O
im O
tok O
say O
na O
since O
only O
di O
change O
in O
leadership O
for O
di O
Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
African I-ORG
Football I-ORG
for O
2017 B-DATE
, O
wen O
current O
president O
Ahmad B-PER
comot O
Issa B-PER
Hayatou I-PER
, O
na O
im O
e O
don O
get O
any O
meaningful O
contact O
wit O
di O
continental O
governing O
body O
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
legend O
Samuel B-PER
Eto'o I-PER
na O
di O
host O
for O
Hurghada B-LOC
, O
and O
e O
be O
one O
of O
several O
former O
players O
wey O
don O
provide O
steady O
support O
. O

Even O
those O
wey O
e O
no O
affect O
physically O
face O
significant O
challenges O
for O
di O
wake O
of O
di O
attack O
. O

I O
find O
no O
reason O
at O
all O
to O
play O
football O
for O
my O
club O
because O
psychologically O
I O
bin O
dey O
shocked O
. O
"""" O

E O
last O
for O
half B-DATE
an I-DATE
hour I-DATE
, O
maybe O
a O
little O
more O
. O

Additional O
research O
and O
reporting O
by O
Blame B-PER
Ekoue I-PER
for O
Lome B-LOC
and O
Victoire B-PER
Eyoum I-PER
in O
London B-LOC
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Super B-ORG
Falcons I-ORG
captain O
, O
Asisat B-PER
Oshoala I-PER
say O
she O
want O
'create O
her O
own O
history' O
afta O
she O
win O
di O
2019 B-DATE
Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
African I-ORG
Football I-ORG
( O
Caf B-ORG
) O
Women O
Player O
of O
di O
Year O
award O
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

Dis O
award O
wey O
Oshoala B-PER
win O
for O
di O
fourth O
time O
don O
make O
her O
equal O
di O
record O
of O
fellow O
Nigerian O
Perpetua B-PER
Nkwocha I-PER
. O

Oshoala B-PER
, O
wey O
claim O
di O
award O
for O
2014 B-DATE
, O
2016 B-DATE
and O
2017 B-DATE
, O
bin O
dey O
up O
against O
Valerenga B-ORG
and O
Cameroon B-LOC
forward O
Ajara B-PER
Nchout I-PER
plus O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
winner O
Thembi B-PER
Kgatlana I-PER
of O
Beijing B-ORG
BG I-ORG
Phoenix I-ORG
and O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
actually O
tense O
about O
dis O
, O
but O
na O
historical O
night B-DATE
for O
me O
, O
"""" O
she O
tok O
Nkwocha B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
five O
- O
time O
Women O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
winner O
, O
claim O
di O
award O
back O
- O
to O
- O
back O
for O
2004 B-DATE
and O
2005 B-DATE
and O
again O
for O
2010 B-DATE
and O
2011 B-DATE
. O

Toure B-PER
add O
: O
"""" O
Of O
course O
e O
dey O
shocking O
because O
na O
2019 B-DATE
we O
dey O
. O

For O
2020 B-DATE
, O
2025 B-DATE
we O
go O
get O
young O
pikin O
dem O
wey O
don O
grow O
- O
wetin O
we O
go O
come O
do O
? O

Di O
former O
Gunners B-ORG
midfielder O
bin O
dey O
work O
with O
Pep B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
as O
coach O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
im O
join O
dem O
afta O
im O
retire O
as O
player O
for O
2016 B-DATE
. O

Im O
go O
replace O
Unai B-PER
Emery I-PER
wey O
Arsenal B-ORG
sack O
for O
early B-DATE
November I-DATE
but O
dem O
neva O
announce O
im O
coaching O
team O
yet O
. O

"""" O
We O
need O
to O
dey O
compete O
for O
di O
top O
trophies O
for O
di O
game O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Arteta B-PER
tok O
"""" O
Dat O
one O
dey O
very O
clear O
to O
me O
, O
when O
I O
discuss O
with O
di O
[ O
owners O
] O
Stan B-PER
and O
Josh B-PER
Kroenke I-PER
and O
senior O
pipo O
from O
di O
club O
. O
"""" O

Di O
former O
midfielder O
sabi O
speak O
plenty O
language O
dem O
, O
im O
dey O
speak O
Spanish O
, O
Basque O
, O
Catalan O
and O
English O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Im O
also O
dey O
speak O
French O
, O
Italian O
and O
Portuguese O
small O
too O
. O

Kamaru B-PER
kpo O
- O
kpo O
Covington B-PER
patapata O
for O
di O
last O
round O
, O
and O
put O
am O
for O
ground O
two O
times O
with O
two O
big O
punch O
, O
e O
come O
begin O
dey O
punch O
am O
, O
punch O
am O
before O
referee O
Marc B-PER
Goddard I-PER
come O
dey O
force O
to O
shout O
say O
di O
fight O
don O
do O
oh O
! O

But O
di O
truth O
be O
say O
dem O
born O
Kamaru B-PER
Usman I-PER
for O
Benin B-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
for O
May B-DATE
11 I-DATE
, I-DATE
1987 I-DATE
and O
Kamaru B-PER
na O
di O
first O
African O
fighter O
to O
win O
Ultimate B-ORG
Fighting I-ORG
Championship I-ORG
title O
. O

Kamaru B-PER
tok O
say O
na O
im O
responsibility O
to O
teach O
Covington B-PER
lesson O
, O
because O
e O
dey O
tok O
too O
much O
. O

"""" O
E O
don O
too O
make O
mouth O
about O
dis O
fight O
, O
so O
dis O
come O
be O
something O
of O
respect O
. O

Nigerians O
and O
odas O
don O
begin O
dey O
say O
congratulobiaa O
give O
Kamaru B-PER
Usman I-PER
. O

Everton B-ORG
don O
appoint O
Carlo B-PER
Ancelotti I-PER
as O
dai O
manager O
for O
four B-DATE
- I-DATE
and I-DATE
- I-DATE
a I-DATE
- I-DATE
half I-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
deal O
. O

Ancelotti B-PER
wey O
Napoli B-ORG
bin O
sack O
early B-DATE
dis I-DATE
month I-DATE
, O
go O
take O
ova O
from O
Marco B-PER
Silva I-PER
, O
wey O
Everton B-ORG
sack O
for O
6 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

Ancelotti B-PER
don O
win O
15 O
major O
trophies O
during O
im O
career O
and O
im O
na O
one O
of O
only O
three O
managers O
to O
win O
three O
European O
Cups O
/ O
Champions O
Leagues O
- O
along O
with O
Liverpool B-ORG
legend O
Bob B-PER
Paisley I-PER
and O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
boss O
Zinedine B-PER
Zidane I-PER
. O

E O
guide O
Chelsea B-ORG
go O
di O
Premier O
League O
and O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
double O
during O
im O
first O
season O
in O
charge O
for O
2009 B-DATE
- I-DATE
10 I-DATE
but O
dem O
sack O
am O
afta O
e O
fail O
to O
win O
trophy O
for O
di O
following O
campaign O
. O

Everton B-ORG
director O
of O
football O
, O
Marcel B-PER
Brands I-PER
tok O
say O
Ancelotti B-PER
na O
"""" O
one O
of O
di O
finest O
managers O
for O
di O
world O
football O
"""" O
and O
na O
"""" O
proven O
winner O
"""" O
. O

"""" O
Carlo B-PER
na O
di O
perfect O
appointment O
for O
us O
, O
"""" O
e O
add O
. O

Im O
record O
na O
15 O
- O
1 O
. O

Usman B-PER
get O
six O
career O
knockout O
win O
and O
one O
submission O
victory O
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
relaxed O
becos O
I O
know O
wetin O
I O
go O
do O
. O
"""" O

Di O
American O
neva O
lose O
for O
im O
last O
seven O
fight O
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
real O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
Usman B-PER
and O
Covington B-PER
go O
make O
$ O
500 O
, O
000 O
each O
for O
dis O
dia O
fight O
. O

Martial B-PER
score O
two O
goals O
, O
Marcus B-PER
Rashford I-PER
and O
Mason B-PER
Greenwood I-PER
na O
dem O
score O
di O
oda O
goals O
for O
di O
Red B-ORG
Devils I-ORG
. O

Fury B-PER
, O
31 B-DATE
, O
bin O
fight O
draw O
wit O
undefeated O
American O
Wilder B-PER
, O
34 B-DATE
, O
for O
December B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
. O

Fury B-PER
survive O
knockdown O
two O
times O
from O
di O
American O
to O
get O
draw O
during O
di O
Los B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC
fight O
. O

Fury B-PER
defeat O
Germany B-LOC
fighter O
Tom B-PER
Schwarz I-PER
for O
June B-DATE
, O
but O
im O
injure O
im O
eye O
during O
di O
beating O
im O
give O
Swedish O
man O
Otto B-PER
Wallin I-PER
for O
September B-DATE
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
full O
draw O
for O
di O
Champions O
League O
last O
- O
16 O
stage O
. O

Aboudi B-PER
Onguéné I-PER
Gabrielle I-PER
, O
captain O
for O
Cameroon B-LOC
women O
national O
team O
, O
president O
for O
"""" O
Terre B-ORG
Promise' I-ORG
association I-ORG
, O
say O
e O
wan O
komot O
women O
football O
from O
'darkness' O
. O

Di O
Russian O
champion O
for O
2019 B-DATE
with O
CSKA B-ORG
Mosco I-ORG
make O
de O
statement O
for O
'GO7 O
Awards' O
prize O
award O
weh O
e O
organise O
for O
compensate O
de O
pipo O
weh O
deh O
work O
hard O
for O
2018 B-DATE
football O
season O
. O

Na O
de O
first O
prize O
award O
weh O
player O
weh O
e O
still O
bi O
active O
wit O
national O
team O
don O
organise O
for O
encourage O
women O
football O
. O

Since O
den O
, O
Aboudi B-PER
say O
tins O
di O
change O
small O
- O
small O
but O
e O
also O
check O
say O
taim O
don O
reach O
for O
shake O
tins O
for O
women O
football O
. O

One O
of O
de O
winners O
, O
Marian B-PER
Ngo I-PER
- I-PER
ese I-PER
player O
weh O
e O
touch O
pipo O
dia O
heart O
last O
football O
season O
, O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
e O
hard O
work O
pay O
wit O
de O
award O
. O

Celine B-PER
Eko I-PER
president O
for O
women O
football O
league O
, O
say O
Cameroon B-LOC
football O
executive O
committee O
don O
decide O
for O
support O
Aboudi B-PER
for O
dis O
wandaful O
activity O
next B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
for O
organise O
de O
award O
wit O
de O
plyer O
, O
e O
announce O
for O
BBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
. O

As O
Jose B-PER
Mourinho I-PER
dey O
return O
to O
Old B-LOC
Trafford I-LOC
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
almost I-DATE
one I-DATE
year I-DATE
afta O
dem O
chase O
am O
comot O
dia O
, O
one O
mata O
wey O
go O
dey O
pipo O
mind O
na O
which O
kain O
kwanta O
VAR O
go O
cause O
for O
di O
ogbonge O
matches O
. O

VAR O
don O
cause O
controversy O
well O
well O
for O
Premier O
League O
and O
Mourinho B-PER
imsef O
na O
pesin O
wey O
from O
time O
don O
para O
unto O
officials O
decisions O
wey O
im O
feel O
say O
no O
correct O
. O

Although O
we O
no O
get O
data O
to O
support O
dis O
, O
e O
be O
like O
many O
of O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
players O
don O
complain O
well O
well O
about O
am O
. O

For O
November B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
, O
Chelsea B-ORG
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Frank B-PER
Lampard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

Many O
fans O
don O
enta O
social O
media O
to O
show O
dia O
frustration O
wit O
VAR O
, O
especially O
wen O
decision O
no O
favour O
dia O
team O
. O

"""" O
We O
decide O
togeda O
say O
we O
go O
tok O
next B-DATE
week I-DATE
becos O
I O
dey O
inside O
Doha B-LOC
until O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
true O
story O
, O
"""" O
Wenger B-PER
tok O
. O

"""" O
Him O
bein O
dey O
inside O
him O
car O
dey O
go O
for O
di O
game O
against O
Olympiakos B-ORG
. O

Afta O
10 O
games O
of O
di O
Bundesliga O
campaign O
, O
Bayern B-ORG
carri O
fourth O
, O
four O
points O
behind O
leaders O
Borussia B-ORG
Monchengladbach I-ORG
, O
and O
lost O
5 O
- O
1 O
to O
Eintracht B-ORG
Frankfurt I-ORG
in O
Kovac's B-PER
last O
match O
in O
charge O
. O

However O
, O
dem O
get O
a O
perfect O
record O
inside O
di O
Champions O
League O
and O
dia O
2 O
- O
0 O
win O
over O
Olympiakos B-ORG
inside O
Flick B-PER
first O
game O
wey O
dey O
in O
charge O
for O
di O
meantime O
, O
make O
am O
dia O
numebr O
four O
win O
in O
four O
group O
games O
. O

Joshua B-PER
go O
fight O
Ruiz B-PER
again O
for O
rematch O
for O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
. O

Seven B-DATE
months I-DATE
later O
Ali B-PER
defeat O
Spinks B-PER
for O
15 O
rounds O
afta O
all O
di O
judges O
give O
am O
di O
victory O
. O

Evander B-PER
Holyfield I-PER
: O
Holyfield B-PER
lose O
im O
WBA O
, O
IBF O
and O
Lineal O
Heavyweight O
title O
dem O
to O
Michael B-PER
Moorer I-PER
on O
points O
, O
di O
defeat O
surprise O
plenty O
pipo O
. O

Afta O
Moorer B-PER
victory O
to O
Holyfield B-PER
e O
come O
choose O
to O
fight O
45 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
ex O
- O
Heavyweight O
champion O
George B-PER
Foreman I-PER
instead O
but O
im O
lose O
dat O
fight O
. O

Foreman B-PER
win O
di O
fight O
on O
knockout O
afta O
im O
land O
Moorer B-PER
heavy O
blow O
for O
im O
chin O
. O

On O
November B-DATE
11 I-DATE
, I-DATE
1997 I-DATE
, O
Holyfield B-PER
and O
Moorer B-PER
meet O
again O
for O
rematch O
. O

Di O
big O
fight O
wey O
evri O
dey O
wait O
for O
dem O
title O
am O
unification O
rematch O
, O
and O
e O
go O
takes O
place O
on O
Dec B-DATE
. I-DATE
7 I-DATE
for O
Diriyah B-LOC
Arena I-LOC
- O
custom O
- O
built O
15 O
, O
000 O
- O
seater O
venue O
inside O
Diriyah B-LOC
, O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
. O

Di O
American O
bin O
struggle O
for O
di O
fight O
as O
Ruiz B-PER
start O
strong O
for O
dia O
rematch O
fight O
wey O
happun O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

But O
for O
seventh O
round O
, O
Wilder B-PER
right O
hand O
blow O
land O
Ortiz B-PER
for O
ground O
. O

Na O
only O
Tommy B-PER
Burns I-PER
( O
11 O
) O
, O
Vitali B-PER
Klitschko I-PER
( O
11 O
) O
, O
Wladimir B-PER
Klitschko I-PER
( O
18 O
) O
, O
Larry B-PER
Holmes I-PER
( O
20 O
) O
and O
Joe B-PER
Louis I-PER
( O
25 O
) O
don O
manage O
to O
defend O
dia O
heavyweight O
crown O
more O
times O
straight O
without O
defeat O
. O

Im O
im O
win O
by O
decision O
wey O
all O
di O
judges O
gree O
to O
. O

Meanwhile O
plenti O
pipo O
for O
inside O
social O
media O
follow O
to O
jollificate O
with O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
afta O
im O
win O
. O

Minister O
of O
Youths O
and O
Sports O
Development O
, O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
Sunday B-PER
Dare I-PER
, O
say O
Africa B-LOC
richest O
man O
Aliko B-PER
Dangote I-PER
godo O
collabo O
wit O
goment O
to O
repair O
di O
Moshood B-LOC
Abiola I-LOC
National I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
for O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
di O
kontri O
capital O
. O

Local O
tori O
pipo O
, O
The B-ORG
Cable I-ORG
also O
report O
on O
Friday B-DATE
say O
oga O
Dare B-PER
follow O
journalists O
tok O
say O
repair O
work O
go O
start O
in O
one B-DATE
or I-DATE
two I-DATE
weeks I-DATE
time I-DATE
. O

Wen O
Nigeria B-LOC
use O
di O
national O
stadium O
take O
host O
di O
Fifa B-ORG
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
for O
2009 B-DATE
, O
di O
grass O
ontop O
di O
field O
still O
green O
well O
- O
well O
and O
facility O
dey O
work O
. O

"""" O
If O
e O
happun O
to O
anyone O
of O
us O
, O
e O
happun O
to O
all O
of O
us O
, O
"""" O
Abraham B-PER
bin O
tok O
. O

"""" O
If O
e O
happun O
and O
warning O
don O
sound O
comot O
for O
di O
stadium O
, O
and O
e O
come O
happun O
again O
, O
we O
go O
need O
to O
decide O
as O
one O
team O
and O
wit O
di O
staff O
, O
"""" O
Abraham B-PER
bin O
tok O
. O

"""" O
E O
go O
pain O
me O
if O
e O
happun O
say O
na O
true O
. O
. O
. O
Me O
personally O
, O
I O
no O
hear O
di O
chanting O
, O
"""" O
Balakov B-PER
bin O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Afta O
yesterday B-DATE
shame O
wey O
di O
Bulgarian O
National O
Team O
carri O
come O
and O
di O
bad O
result O
from O
our O
football O
, O
I O
don O
order O
di O
end O
of O
any O
relationship O
wit O
BFU B-ORG
, O
including O
financial O
, O
until O
Borislav B-PER
Mihaylov I-PER
comot O
from O
di O
position O
, O
"""" O
hala O
Borissov B-PER

For O
match O
wey O
dem O
play O
for O
Agege B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
Lagos I-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
lose O
based O
on O
di O
away O
goal O
rule O
because O
na O
goalless O
draw O
dem O
play O
for O
first O
leg O
. O

Les B-ORG
Elephantes I-ORG
and O
Super B-ORG
Falcons I-ORG
bin O
play O
0 O
- O
0 O
draw O
for O
Abidjan B-LOC
four B-DATE
days I-DATE
earlier I-DATE
, O
and O
Nigeria B-LOC
be O
di O
favourite O
to O
win O
am O
for O
Agege B-LOC
, O
but O
coach O
Clementine B-PER
Toure I-PER
and O
her O
girls O
decide O
say O
dem O
go O
change O
am O
for O
dem O
. O

Boxer O
Patrick B-PER
Day I-PER
don O
die O
at O
age B-DATE
27 I-DATE
- O
four B-DATE
days I-DATE
afta O
im O
suffer O
brain O
injury O
from O
fight O
against O
Charles B-PER
Conwell I-PER
. O

Di O
American O
enta O
coma O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
afta O
im O
knock O
out O
for O
di O
10th O
round O
of O
im O
super O
welterweight O
bout O
for O
Chicago B-LOC
. O

Na O
how O
he O
inspire O
pipo O
and O
it O
was O
something O
that O
made O
him O
feel O
alive O
. O
"""" O

Day B-PER
win O
17 O
of O
im O
22 O
fights O
, O
with O
four O
defeats O
and O
one O
draw O
. O

Di O
match O
suppose O
happun O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
26 I-DATE
October I-DATE
for O
Barcelona B-ORG
but O
RFEF B-ORG
postpone O
am O
after O
La O
Liga O
say O
dem O
dey O
fear O
say O
gbege O
fit O
happun O
. O

Protests O
don O
dey O
happun O
for O
Barcelona B-ORG
since O
last B-DATE
week I-DATE
afta O
nine O
Catalan O
separatist O
leaders O
get O
jail O
sentence O
earlier B-DATE
dis I-DATE
month I-DATE
. O

"""" O
La O
Liga O
no O
gree O
wit O
di O
competition O
committee O
decision O
to O
select O
18 B-DATE
December I-DATE
- O
afta O
dem O
reach O
agreement O
wit O
Barcelona B-ORG
and O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
, O
even O
though O
Liga O
say O
dem O
no O
want O
am O
- O
as O
di O
date O
wey O
di O
postponed O
Clasico O
go O
now O
happun O
, O
"""" O
La O
Liga O
tok O
for O
statement O
. O

Spain B-ORG
Constitutional I-ORG
Court I-ORG
don O
declare O
di O
referendum O
illegal O
. O

Spain B-ORG
Supreme I-ORG
Court I-ORG
convict O
nine O
separatist O
leaders O
ontop O
dia O
role O
inside O
di O
referendum O
and O
nack O
dem O
jail O
sentences O
of O
between O
nine B-DATE
and I-DATE
13 I-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

Liverpool B-ORG
forward O
Roberto B-PER
Firmino I-PER
na O
im O
score O
Brazil B-LOC
goal O
wen O
im O
chip O
Senegal B-LOC
goalkeeper O
to O
open O
di O
scoring O
afta O
only O
nine B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
. O

Senegal B-LOC
Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
come O
later O
win O
penarity O
wey O
striker O
Famara B-PER
Diedhiou I-PER
convert O
to O
equalise O
for O
Senegal B-LOC
. O

Brazil B-LOC
go O
now O
face O
Nigeria B-LOC
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
on O
Sunday B-DATE
for O
di O
same O
venue O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

Etienne B-PER
Eto'o I-PER
say O
e O
bi O
na O
big O
blow O
for O
know O
say O
dis O
decree O
go O
komot O
dem O
for O
World O
Cup O
, O
and O
wit O
de O
five O
Europe B-LOC
players O
encourage O
we O
selves O
and O
we O
don O
turn O
new O
page O
for O
life O
, O
Eto'o B-PER
e O
pikin O
tok O
. O

Cameroon B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
, O
Fecafoot B-ORG
send O
de O
message O
for O
de O
big O
boss O
sports O
minister O
, O
but O
wen O
final O
list O
komot O
deh O
discover O
say O
players O
weh O
deh O
di O
no O
di O
play O
for O
kontri O
no O
dey O
inside O
. O

Today B-DATE
, O
Fifa B-ORG
confirm O
squad O
list O
de O
24 O
teams O
dem O
weh O
deh O
go O
take O
part O
for O
dis O
competition O
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
dey O
for O
Group O
E O
wit O
Argentina B-LOC
, O
Spain B-LOC
, O
Tajikistan B-LOC
and O
Brazil B-LOC
. O

Joe B-PER
Aribo I-PER
score O
Nigeria B-LOC
first O
goal O
for O
di O
35th B-DATE
minute I-DATE
of O
di O
game O
afta O
im O
collect O
fine O
pass O
from O
Simon B-PER
inside O
di O
penalty O
box O
. O

Top O
star O
Neymar B-PER
play O
only O
12 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
for O
di O
match O
sake O
of O
Injury O
, O
but O
oda O
ogbonge O
stars O
like O
Philipe B-PER
Coutinho I-PER
, O
Gabriel B-PER
Jesus I-PER
, O
Roberto B-PER
Firmino I-PER
and O
veteran O
Dani B-PER
Alves I-PER
show O
wella O
for O
di O
Brazil B-LOC
team O
. O

Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
coach O
, O
Gernot B-PER
Rohr I-PER
plan O
use O
today B-DATE
match O
take O
prepare O
im O
team O
for O
dia O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

For O
di O
Brazilian O
Consulate O
inside O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
our O
reporter O
send O
fotos O
as O
Nigeria B-LOC
fans O
go O
dia O
to O
watch O
di O
match O
and O
support O
dia O
national O
team O
. O

Bonaventure B-PER
score O
im O
first O
goal O
from O
im O
left O
foot O
shot O
from O
di O
centre O
of O
box O
afta O
nine B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
to O
put O
im O
team O
in O
front O
. O

Im O
second O
goal O
na O
from O
mistake O
from O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
midfielder O
Luka B-PER
Modric I-PER
as O
im O
collect O
ball O
from O
im O
hand O
for O
midfield O
run O
go O
score O
. O

Osimhen B-PER
dey O
form O
Victor B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
score O
for O
Lille B-ORG
but O
den O
lose O
2 O
- O
1 O
for O
house O
to O
Chelsea B-ORG
. O

Wednesday B-DATE
Results O
Genk B-ORG
0 O
- O
0 O
Napoli B-ORG
Slavia I-ORG
Prague I-ORG
0 O
- O
2 O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
Liverpool I-ORG
4 O
- O
3 O
RB B-ORG
Salzburg I-ORG
Barcelona I-ORG
2 O
- O
1 O
Inter B-ORG
Milan I-ORG
Lille I-ORG
1 O
- O
2 O
Chelsea B-ORG
Valencia I-ORG
0 O
- O
3 O
Ajax B-ORG
RB I-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG
0 O
- O
2 O
Lyon B-ORG
Zenit I-ORG
St I-ORG
Petersburg I-ORG
3 O
- O
1 O
Benfica B-ORG
Tuesday B-DATE
Results O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
2 O
- O
2 O
Club B-ORG
Brugge I-ORG
Atalanta I-ORG
1 O
- O
2 O
Shakhtar B-ORG
Donetsk I-ORG
Galatasaray I-ORG
0 O
- O
1 O
Paris B-ORG
Saint I-ORG
- I-ORG
Germain I-ORG
Tottenham I-ORG
Hotspur I-ORG
2 O
- O
7 O
Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
Red I-ORG
Star I-ORG
Belgrade I-ORG
3 O
- O
1 O
Olympiacos B-ORG
Manchester I-ORG
City I-ORG
2 O
- O
0 O
Dinamo B-ORG
Zagreb I-ORG
Juventus I-ORG
3 O
- O
0 O
Bayer B-ORG
Leverkusen I-ORG
Lokomotiv I-ORG
Moscow I-ORG
0 O
- O
2 O
Atletico B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG

Pepe B-PER
enter O
as O
substitute O
for O
di O
second O
half O
and O
come O
later O
score O
two O
free O
- O
kicks O
to O
show O
Arsenal B-ORG
fans O
say O
im O
fit O
provide O
di O
pepper O
dia O
season O
need O
. O

Arsenal B-ORG
bin O
dey O
lose O
2 O
- O
1 O
afta O
goals O
from O
Marcus B-PER
Edwards I-PER
and O
Duarte B-PER
da I-PER
Silva I-PER
bin O
give O
Victoria B-ORG
shock O
lead O
for O
Emirates B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
. O

"""" O
Im O
dey O
improve O
and O
tonight O
those O
two O
goals O
dey O
really O
important O
for O
us O
first O
and O
den O
secondly O
for O
am O
. O

Before O
di O
game O
, O
11 O
Norwich B-ORG
players O
suffer O
injury O
wey O
make O
dia O
coach O
Daniel B-PER
Farke I-PER
use O
some O
new O
players O
wey O
never O
play O
dis O
season O
. O

Dem O
been O
don O
go O
19 O
games O
without O
defeat O
before O
Norwich B-ORG
come O
spoil O
dat O
record O
. O

Afta O
she O
win O
she O
say O
; O
"""" O
My O
son O
Zyon B-PER
, O
my O
family O
na O
my O
strength O
. O

You O
fit O
do O
anything O
. O

Na O
about O
who O
you O
be O
and O
why O
you O
start O
"""" O
. O

Fraser B-PER
- I-PER
Pryce I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
32 B-DATE
- I-DATE
years I-DATE
don O
become O
di O
oldest O
woman O
to O
win O
Olympic O
or O
world O
100m O
title O
, O
two B-DATE
years I-DATE
afta O
she O
born O
her O
pikin O
, O
Zyon B-PER
. O

"""" O
For O
pesin O
wey O
no O
well O
, O
to O
come O
comot O
freedom O
from O
dat O
pesin O
life O
, O
dis O
one O
pass O
bad O
, O
e O
dey O
heartbreaking O
and O
sad O
. O

I O
go O
like O
make O
di O
goment O
or O
whoever O
dey O
capable O
to O
help O
me O
bring O
my O
mama O
back O
. O
"""" O

Police O
tok O
- O
tok O
pesin O
for O
Bayelsa B-LOC
state I-LOC
, O
SP O
Butswat B-PER
Asinim I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
investigation O
still O
dey O
go O
on O
and O
dem O
neva O
relax O
for O
di O
mata O
to O
rescue O
Samson B-PER
Siasia I-PER
mama O
. O

"""" O
For O
three B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
I O
never O
get O
work O
and O
wit O
dis O
Fifa B-ORG
ban O
appeal O
and O
to O
come O
get O
my O
sick O
mama O
for O
di O
hands O
of O
kidnappers O
, O
my O
tire O
pass O
tire O
. O
"""" O

Red O
hot O
Lille B-ORG
of O
France B-LOC
striker O
Victor B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
wey O
don O
score O
six O
goals O
for O
French O
league O
go O
dey O
expected O
to O
lead O
di O
line O
again O
. O

Midfielders O
: O
Alexander B-PER
Iwobi I-PER
( O
Everton B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
England B-LOC
) O
; O
Anderson B-PER
Esiti I-PER
( O
PAOK B-ORG
Salonica I-ORG
, O
Greece B-LOC
) O
; O
Oghenekaro B-PER
Etebo I-PER
( O
Stoke B-ORG
City I-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
England B-LOC
) O
; O
Wilfred B-PER
Ndidi I-PER
( O
Leicester B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
England B-LOC
) O
; O
Joseph B-PER
Ayodele I-PER
- I-PER
Aribo I-PER
( O
Glasgow B-ORG
Rangers I-ORG
, O
Scotland B-LOC
) O
; O
Ramon B-PER
Azeez I-PER
( O
Granada B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Spain B-LOC
) O
. O

Forwards O
: O
Victor B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
( O
Lille B-ORG
OSC I-ORG
, O
France B-LOC
) O
; O
Moses B-PER
Simon I-PER
( O
FC B-ORG
Nantes I-ORG
, O
France B-LOC
) O
; O
Samuel B-PER
Chukwueze I-PER
( O
Villarreal B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Spain B-LOC
) O
; O
Samuel B-PER
Kalu I-PER
( O
Girondins B-ORG
Bordeaux I-ORG
, O
France B-LOC
) O
; O
Paul B-PER
Onuachu I-PER
( O
KRC B-ORG
Genk I-ORG
, O
Belgium B-LOC
) O
; O
Emmanuel B-PER
Dennis I-PER
( O
Club B-ORG
Brugge I-ORG
, O
Belgium B-LOC
) O
; O
Peter B-PER
Olayinka I-PER
( O
SK B-ORG
Slavia I-ORG
Prague I-ORG
, O
Czech B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
) O
. O

Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
say O
boxing O
'undercard' O
match O
wey O
women O
go O
fight O
fit O
happun O
on O
di O
day O
of O
im O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
rematch O
wit O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jr I-PER
. O
Joshua B-PER
, O
29 B-DATE
, O
dey O
target O
to O
get O
back O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBA O
and O
WBO O
world O
heavyweight O
titles O
inside O
"""" O
Clash O
on O
di O
Dunes O
"""" O
wey O
go O
happun O
for O
Diriyah B-LOC
on O
7 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

Undercard' O
na O
di O
small O
- O
small O
matches O
wey O
dey O
happun O
before O
di O
main O
boxing O
match O
of O
di O
night B-DATE
, O
to O
take O
totori O
di O
pipo O
wey O
don O
spend O
big O
money O
come O
. O

No O
be O
just O
say O
make O
two O
men O
come O
togeda O
to O
fight O
. O
"""" O

Promoter O
Eddie B-PER
Hearn I-PER
sef O
confam O
to O
BBC B-ORG
say O
tok O
- O
tok O
"""" O
dey O
happun O
now O
"""" O
ontop O
undercard O
match O
for O
women O
. O

Some O
pipo O
don O
criticize O
di O
event O
wen O
di O
tori O
comot O
say O
na O
for O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
e O
go O
happun O
. O

For O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
, O
freedom O
of O
expression O
and O
women O
rights O
get O
k O
- O
leg O
and O
di O
international O
community O
don O
also O
raise O
di O
issue O
of O
death O
penalty O
for O
offence O
wey O
international O
law O
no O
recognise O
to O
be O
crime O
. O

In O
just O
3 B-DATE
days I-DATE
dem O
see O
3 O
, O
000 O
new O
cases O
for O
April B-DATE
and O
come O
put O
back O
di O
lockdown O
to O
1 B-DATE
June I-DATE
. O

Italy B-LOC
, O
for O
example O
, O
dey O
reduce O
dia O
7 B-DATE
- I-DATE
week I-DATE
lockdown O
but O
restaurants O
and O
bars O
dey O
open O
only O
for O
take O
- O
away O
. O

Na O
why O
plenti O
goments O
for O
world O
get O
stimuli O
packages O
for O
workers O
and O
companies O
. O

To O
go O
back O
work O
Pressure O
don O
dey O
goment O
neck O
to O
reduce O
restrictions O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
work O
. O

Bangladesh B-LOC
na O
kontri O
wey O
lobby O
work O
and O
dem O
dey O
start O
exit O
measures O
. O

Bangladesh B-LOC
wey O
be O
di O
second O
largest O
explorer O
of O
clothes O
for O
world O
dem O
don O
dey O
suffer O
on O
top O
cancellation O
of O
orders O
from O
Europe B-LOC
and O
South B-LOC
America I-LOC
. O

Belgium B-LOC
dey O
pressure O
dia O
workers O
on O
safety O
in O
fact O
, O
one O
of O
di O
busiest O
ports O
for O
di O
world O
, O
Antwerp B-LOC
dey O
test O
wristband O
wey O
go O
beep O
if O
pesin O
pass O
di O
2 O
meter O
rule O
for O
social O
distancing O
for O
di O
workers O
. O

Di O
wristband O
sef O
go O
help O
with O
contact O
tracing O
in O
case O
of O
infection O
and O
dem O
also O
dey O
test O
am O
for O
America B-LOC
. O

School O
closures O
na O
im O
almost O
evri O
kontri O
don O
adopt O
for O
dis O
pandemic O
. O

By O
April B-DATE
170 O
of O
di O
193 O
kontris O
for O
UN B-ORG
don O
close O
down O
dia O
schools O
according O
to O
Unesco B-ORG
. O

Some O
kontris O
don O
dey O
reopen O
and O
dey O
look O
for O
strategy O
to O
make O
sure O
say O
di O
students O
and O
staff O
dey O
safe O
. O

While O
scientists O
dey O
fear O
say O
opening O
school O
fit O
make O
children O
dey O
share O
di O
virus O
, O
education O
sabi O
pipo O
say O
e O
dey O
good O
for O
dia O
education O
and O
mental O
health O
. O

Even O
sef O
dem O
cancel O
di O
Buddist B-DATE
New I-DATE
Year I-DATE
for O
South B-LOC
Asia I-LOC
. O

But O
di O
presidential O
office O
for O
Seoul B-LOC
don O
tok O
say O
no O
particular O
signs O
from O
di O
North O
to O
indicate O
say O
di O
36 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
dey O
"""" O
seriously O
sick O
"""" O
. O

Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
recently O
miss O
di O
celebration O
of O
im O
grandpapa O
birthday O
on O
15 B-DATE
April I-DATE
. O

As O
e O
be O
, O
im O
absence O
start O
di O
speculation O
and O
rumour O
, O
none O
of O
which O
dey O
easy O
to O
prove O
. O

We O
know O
say O
im O
chair O
one O
key O
political O
meeting O
di O
day O
before O
, O
from O
state O
media O
despatches O
. O

Im O
dey O
usually O
dey O
for O
dis O
kind O
launch O
dem O
. O

Anonymous O
source O
tell O
tori O
pipo O
Daily B-ORG
NK I-ORG
say O
Kim B-PER
dey O
struggle O
with O
cardiovascular O
problems O
since O
last B-DATE
August I-DATE
"""" O
but O
e O
become O
worse O
afta O
many O
visits O
to O
Mount B-LOC
Paektu I-LOC
"""" O
. O

News O
agencies O
come O
begin O
to O
run O
with O
dat O
claim O
, O
and O
na O
all O
dem O
bin O
get O
until O
some O
reports O
comot O
from O
intelligence O
agencies O
for O
South B-LOC
Korea I-LOC
and O
also O
show O
say O
di O
US B-LOC
too O
dey O
monitor O
di O
claim O
. O

E O
dey O
important O
to O
note O
say O
nobody O
don O
deny O
say O
Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
undergo O
heart O
surgery O
. O

Di O
statement O
from O
South B-LOC
Korea I-LOC
and O
China B-LOC
merely O
deny O
say O
di O
North O
Korean O
leader O
dey O
seriously O
sick O
. O

But O
for O
now O
, O
we O
fit O
only O
watch O
and O
wait O
to O
see O
if O
North B-LOC
Korea I-LOC
react O
to O
dis O
many O
speculation O
about O
their O
leader O
health O
. O

De O
virus O
spread O
catch O
twelve O
out O
of O
sixteen O
regions O
for O
, O
dis O
be O
regional O
breakdown O
of O
how O
Covid O
- O
19 O
spread O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
. O

Dutch O
goment O
don O
issue O
new O
guidance O
to O
single O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
find O
closeness O
during O
di O
pandemic O
, O
with O
advise O
for O
dem O
to O
find O
"""" O
sex O
buddy O
"""" O
. O

Social O
- O
distancing O
measures O
dey O
in O
place O
for O
Netherlands B-LOC
since O
23 B-DATE
March I-DATE
, O
wen O
goment O
impose O
wetin O
dem O
call O
"""" O
intelligent O
"""" O
or O
"""" O
targeted O
"""" O
lockdown O
. O

But O
for O
di O
guidance O
wey O
dem O
publish O
on O
14 B-DATE
May I-DATE
, O
di O
RIVM B-ORG
say O
"""" O
e O
make O
sense O
for O
single O
[ O
pesin O
] O
you O
also O
go O
wan O
get O
physical O
contact O
"""" O
during O
di O
pandemic O
. O

If O
singles O
choose O
to O
engage O
in O
sexual O
contact O
, O
dem O
must O
take O
precautions O
to O
minimise O
di O
risk O
of O
coronavirus O
exposure O
, O
di O
authority O
tok O
. O

Di O
RIVM B-ORG
also O
issue O
advice O
for O
pipo O
wey O
dia O
long O
- O
term O
partners O
suspect O
say O
don O
catch O
di O
coronavirus O
. O

"""" O
Sex O
with O
yourself O
or O
with O
odas O
at O
a O
distance O
dey O
possible O
, O
"""" O
e O
add O
, O
e O
suggest O
"""" O
erotic O
stories O
"""" O
and O
"""" O
masturbating O
togeda O
"""" O
as O
possible O
solutions O
. O

On O
Monday B-DATE
, O
di O
Netherlands B-LOC
begin O
dia O
first O
stage O
of O
five O
- O
phase O
lockdown O
exit O
plan O
. O

43 O
, O
880 O
pipo O
don O
test O
positive O
for O
coronavirus O
for O
di O
kontri O
so O
far O
, O
with O
more O
dan O
5 O
, O
500 O
deaths O
. O

We O
dey O
travel O
half O
di O
world O
togeda O
. O

My O
fear O
na O
to O
avoid O
to O
dey O
alone O
for O
di O
same O
place O
wit O
her O
. O

We O
meet O
wen O
we O
dey O
our O
20s B-DATE
- O
na O
she O
ask O
me O
out O
. O

Inside O
one O
day O
, O
I O
lose O
evritin O
. O

I O
only O
fit O
afford O
relationship O
wen O
I O
bin O
don O
save O
plenty O
moni O
to O
live O
on O
my O
own O
. O

On O
top O
of O
am O
, O
my O
mama O
dey O
shame O
for O
me O
sake O
of O
how O
I O
look O
- O
I O
bin O
get O
very O
low O
self O
- O
esteem O
. O

I O
bin O
need O
to O
go O
overseas O
on O
long O
business O
trip O
. O

I O
dey O
fear O
to O
lose O
Ira B-PER
, O
so O
I O
ask O
am O
to O
follow O
me O
. O

She O
refuse O
, O
but O
she O
join O
me O
las O
- O
las O
. O

Na O
where O
e O
begin O
be O
dat O
. O

I O
don O
dey O
wait O
for O
you O
for O
long O
time O
. O
"""" O

I O
go O
reply O
, O
"""" O
No O
, O
I O
no O
want O
to O
, O
I O
want O
rest O
, O
I O
don O
tired O
. O
"""" O

She O
no O
go O
leave O
any O
marks O
for O
my O
face O
- O
she O
go O
harm O
only O
place O
I O
fit O
cover O
: O
my O
chest O
, O
back O
, O
hands O
. O

Na O
how O
my O
parent O
raised O
me O
be O
dat O
. O

I O
come O
end O
up O
trapped O
. O

So O
, O
I O
con O
get O
urinary O
tract O
infections O
, O
prostatitis O
, O
and O
fever O
. O

Na O
weekend O
worse O
pass O
. O

She O
no O
fit O
go O
anywhere O
without O
me O
- O
I O
be O
play O
toy O
wey O
need O
to O
entertain O
her O
all O
di O
time O
. O

Every O
morning O
, O
I O
need O
wait O
till O
she O
wake O
up O
, O
na O
until O
wen O
she O
wake O
about O
nine B-DATE
or I-DATE
10 I-DATE
o'clock I-DATE
or O
she O
go O
say O
I O
disturb O
her O
sleep O
. O

Wen O
I O
be O
do O
sometin O
wrong O
, O
she O
go O
shout O
for O
me O
and O
even O
beat O
me O
. O

Anytin O
wey O
dey O
happun O
- O
she O
go O
blame O
me O
. O

She O
waka O
pass O
me O
and O
see O
me O
. O

No O
matta O
wetin O
I O
do O
or O
how O
bad O
e O
do O
me O
, O
nothing O
change O
. O

I O
no O
dey O
perfect O
. O

To O
dey O
avoid O
all O
dis O
, O
I O
use O
to O
work O
10 B-DATE
, O
12 B-DATE
, O
14 B-DATE
hours I-DATE
every O
day O
, O
on O
weekends B-DATE
and O
even O
for O
holiday O
time O
. O

You O
no O
go O
see O
di O
way O
out O
and O
you O
no O
go O
hear O
wen O
you O
dey O
situation O
like O
dat O
, O
you O
no O
dey O
know O
wetin O
dey O
happun O
to O
you O
. O

And O
so O
I O
sacrifice O
my O
interests O
and O
myself O
- O
e O
look O
normal O
to O
me O
back O
then O
. O

Tyasutami B-PER
no O
too O
tink O
am O
but O
then O
for O
17 B-DATE
February I-DATE
morning O
she O
wake O
up O
with O
symptoms O
wey O
she O
sef O
gree O
say O
no O
be O
small O
tin O
. O

Na O
so O
dem O
cari O
bodi O
go O
hospital O
, O
wia O
di O
doctor O
say O
di O
mama O
get O
typhus O
, O
wey O
be O
bacterial O
disease O
wey O
lice O
and O
fleas O
dey O
spread O
and O
di O
pikin O
get O
bronchopneumonia O
. O

Dem O
even O
ask O
if O
na O
scam O
say O
she O
come O
fine O
and O
beautiful O
afta O
she O
bin O
sick O
. O

For O
3 B-DATE
March I-DATE
, O
Presido O
Widodo B-PER
sat O
make O
di O
hospitals O
and O
goment O
officials O
respect O
di O
privacy O
of O
di O
patients O
but O
by O
that O
time O
evritin O
don O
scata O
. O

E O
no O
help O
di O
mata O
when O
di O
Indonesia B-LOC
health O
minister O
, O
Terewan B-PER
Agus I-PER
Putranto I-PER
cause O
more O
wahala O
afta O
e O
say O
Sita B-PER
catch O
di O
virus O
from O
her O
Japanese O
close O
friend O
when O
she O
bin O
dey O
dance O
for O
nightclub O
wey O
no O
be O
true O
. O

Dem O
dey O
take O
out O
time O
to O
dey O
support O
families O
wey O
no O
too O
hold O
money O
like O
dem O
, O
and O
sometimes O
advice O
, O
Dem O
even O
donate O
dia O
blood O
to O
find O
treatment O
for O
di O
virus O
. O

WHO B-ORG
Emergencies O
Director O
, O
Dr O
Mike B-PER
Ryan I-PER
wey O
tok O
dis O
one O
for O
one O
virtual O
press O
briefing O
say O
, O
e O
dey O
important O
for O
pipo O
to O
know O
say O
dis O
virus O
fit O
become O
anoda O
common O
virus O
for O
di O
world O
just O
like O
HIV O
. O

Plenti O
Nigerians O
and O
celebs O
shock O
wen O
dem O
wake O
up O
to O
hear O
di O
news O
of O
di O
death O
of O
popular O
video O
vixen O
and O
dancer O
, O
Kodak B-PER
. O

Kaffy B-PER
wey O
be O
dancer O
like O
her O
also O
comment O
. O

One O
of O
Kodak B-PER
friend O
wey O
tok O
to O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
but O
no O
want O
make O
we O
mention O
her O
name O
say O
, O
na O
electric O
shock O
kill O
di O
dancer O
, O
wen O
she O
bin O
go O
charge O
her O
phone O
for O
one O
music O
producer O
office O
. O

She O
bin O
dey O
shoot O
music O
video O
for O
di O
music O
producer O
house O
wen O
di O
incident O
happun O
. O

Allen B-PER
na O
di O
drummer O
, O
musical O
director O
and O
leader O
of O
Fela B-PER
Kuti I-PER
famous O
band O
Africa B-ORG
'70 I-ORG
for O
1960 B-DATE
- I-DATE
70s I-DATE
. O

Allen B-PER
career O
and O
life O
tori O
dey O
documented O
inside O
im O
2013 B-DATE
autobiography O
Tony B-PER
Allen I-PER
: O
Master O
Drummer O
of O
Afrobeat O
. O

Afrobeat O
music O
na O
di O
kind O
music O
wey O
combine O
tins O
from O
West B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
fuji O
music O
and O
highlife O
styles O
with O
American O
funk O
and O
jazz O
. O

Allen B-PER
bin O
first O
meet O
Fela B-PER
for O
1964 B-DATE
, O
and O
dem O
form O
partnership O
wey O
produce O
plenty O
albums O
during O
di O
era O
of O
Africa B-ORG
'70 I-ORG
band O
, O
including O
Gentleman O
and O
Zombie O
. O

Allen B-PER
later O
comot O
di O
band O
for O
1979 B-DATE
, O
afta O
kwanta O
wey O
im O
be O
get O
wit O
di O
band O
leader O
over O
royalty O
money O
. O

"""" O
My O
heart O
dey O
do O
gbim O
- O
gbim O
for O
those O
wey O
bi O
ER O
doctors O
and O
for O
nurses O
wey O
dey O
sleep O
inside O
car O
to O
make O
sure O
say O
dem O
no O
infect O
dia O
families O
or O
dia O
parents O
, O
"""" O
di O
singer O
, O
wey O
im O
real O
name O
na O
Stefani B-PER
Germanotta I-PER
tok O
. O

Two B-DATE
months I-DATE
afta O
im O
tok O
about O
im O
sickness O
for O
public O
, O
im O
write O
open O
letter O
about O
im O
experience O
with O
di O
cancer O
treatment O
, O
im O
tok O
about O
di O
"""" O
intensity O
"""" O
of O
im O
pain O
and O
di O
"""" O
uncertainty O
"""" O
of O
life O
. O

Bollywood B-ORG
stars O
and O
politicians O
don O
begin O
pay O
tribute O
to O
am O
on O
social O
media O
. O

For O
her O
interview O
with O
BBC B-ORG
, O
she O
tok O
say O
she O
gatz O
to O
fight O
pressure O
from O
di O
industry O
to O
fit O
change O
herself O
. O

She O
dey O
conscious O
to O
be O
role O
model O
to O
plenti O
boys O
and O
girls O
wey O
fit O
dey O
deal O
with O
dia O
own O
images O
and O
self O
- O
acceptance O
. O

But O
some O
practical O
considerations O
dey O
too O
: O
"""" O
To O
wear O
make O
- O
up O
dey O
stressful O
! O

You O
go O
dey O
sweat O
. O

"""" O
I O
remember O
one O
time O
wey O
I O
go O
Disney B-ORG
with O
my O
friend O
for O
Orlando B-LOC
during O
summer B-DATE
and O
e O
dey O
hot O
and O
my O
friend O
face O
look O
like O
mud O
! O

Di O
couple O
enta O
gbege O
afta O
one O
viral O
video O
wey O
show O
dem O
dey O
party O
for O
house O
with O
more O
dan O
20 O
pipo O
for O
di O
house O
Di O
couple O
go O
also O
pay O
100 O
, O
000 O
naira O
each O
and O
go O
observe O
di O
isolation O
for O
place O
wia O
nobody O
go O
know O
by O
di O
Lagos B-LOC
state O
goment O
to O
determine O
dia O
Covid O
- O
19 O
status O
. O

E O
write O
say O
; O
"""" O
We O
feel O
a O
bit O
tired O
, O
like O
we O
say O
we O
get O
cold O
, O
and O
some O
body O
ache O
. O

Rita B-PER
experience O
some O
chills O
wey O
come O
and O
later O
go O
. O

British O
actor O
and O
musician O
, O
Idris B-PER
Elba I-PER
tok O
say O
im O
test O
positive O
for O
COVID O
- O
19 O
on O
March B-DATE
16 I-DATE
inside O
one O
video O
wey O
im O
post O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

Di O
actor O
write O
say O
"""" O
I O
feel O
ok O
, O
I O
no O
get O
symptoms O
so O
far O
but O
i O
don O
isolate O
mysef O
since O
I O
found O
out O
about O
my O
possible O
exposure O
to O
di O
virus O
. O
. O
. O
"""" O
Model O
and O
now O
actress O
, O
Olga B-PER
Kurylenko I-PER
, O
wey O
don O
act O
for O
films O
like O
'Quantum O
of O
Solace' O
and O
'Oblivion' O
also O
reveal O
for O
Instagram O
say O
she O
dey O
quarantined O
for O
house O
afta O
she O
test O
positive O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
. O

Take O
care O
of O
yourself O
and O
take O
dis O
mata O
serious O
! O
"""" O

Rachel B-PER
Matthews I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
popular O
for O
her O
role O
in O
'Happy O
Death O
Day' O
and O
also O
voiced O
di O
character O
of O
Honeymaren O
for O
Frozen O
2 O
, O
announce O
for O
her O
Instagram O
Stories O
say O
she O
don O
test O
positive O
for O
COVID O
- O
19 O
. O

Di O
advice O
and O
tips O
include O
make O
pipo O
wear O
protective O
cloth O
, O
greet O
each O
oda O
with O
dia O
elbow O
plus O
songs O
wey O
get O
to O
do O
with O
washing O
of O
hands O
. O

Self O
isolation O
and O
social O
distancing O
na O
some O
of O
di O
ways O
sabi O
pipo O
don O
advise O
say O
go O
help O
to O
prevent O
di O
spread O
of O
Covid O
- O
19 O
wey O
dey O
cause O
palava O
for O
di O
world O
. O

For O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
more O
states O
dey O
order O
dia O
citizens O
to O
close O
shop O
and O
stay O
for O
house O
, O
even O
as O
schools O
across O
di O
kontri O
don O
close O
down O
. O

Marjorie B-PER
Fiedler I-PER
, O
na O
one O
of O
such O
pipo O
wey O
don O
join O
one O
of O
di O
parties O
wey O
happun O
for O
Instagram O
Live O
wey O
feature O
Nigerian O
DJ B-PER
Obi I-PER
. O

She O
tok O
say O
, O
"""" O
DJ B-PER
Obi I-PER
party O
bin O
get O
plenti O
celebs O
with O
oda O
pipo O
join O
and O
dey O
very O
interesting O
. O

We O
dey O
pretend O
say O
we O
dey O
for O
inside O
club O
and O
for O
di O
chat O
we O
, O
go O
dey O
do O
like O
na O
real O
party O
, O
dey O
chyke O
babe O
, O
dey O
bounce O
pipo O
comot O
and O
like O
say O
pesin O
dey O
order O
bottles O
. O
"""" O

Anoda O
pesin O
, O
Moses B-PER
Imodu I-PER
describe O
di O
House O
Party O
App O
say O
, O
"""" O
na O
like O
combination O
of O
Whatsapp O
, O
Snapchat O
an O
Skype O
as O
you O
fit O
video O
chat O
with O
up O
to O
eight O
pipo O
and O
also O
fit O
play O
online O
games O
. O
"""" O

Now O
di O
Senator O
don O
collect O
extra O
appointment O
from O
Emeka B-PER
Rollas I-PER
, O
di O
leader O
of O
Actors B-ORG
Guild I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
as O
di O
Patron O
of O
di O
group O
. O

"""" O
You O
fit O
be O
be O
star O
or O
celebrity O
but O
you O
fit O
no O
be O
member O
of O
our O
joinbodi O
, O
"""" O
Rollas B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
interview O
. O

na O
wetin O
Henshaw B-PER
tok O
put O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
be O
that O
. O

She O
con O
add O
put O
say O
person O
wey O
be O
paron O
go O
be O
person O
wey O
get O
moral O
and O
no O
be O
person O
wey O
dey O
slap O
women O
. O

"""" O
Wetin O
pipo O
suppose O
dey O
ask O
na O
if O
im O
come O
out O
to O
beg O
for O
wetin O
im O
do O
. O

Di O
woman O
wey O
im O
slap O
, O
did O
she O
say O
she O
no O
accept O
di O
beg O
? O
, O
~ O
na O
the O
questions O
wey O
Rollas B-PER
ask O
on O
top O
interview O
for O
Plustv B-ORG
Africa I-ORG
be O
this O
. O

Di O
president O
throw O
side O
yab O
for O
Henshaw B-PER
and O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
against O
di O
appointment O
, O
im O
say O
many O
of O
dem O
no O
go O
even O
fit O
pass O
morality O
test O
. O

Pesin O
for O
im O
family O
, O
say O
im O
"""" O
die O
peacefully O
for O
im O
house O
from O
natural O
causes O
"""" O
. O

Rogers B-PER
win O
three O
Grammy O
awards O
and O
dey O
popular O
for O
songs O
like O
Tyhe O
Gambler O
, O
Lucile O
, O
Cowartd O
of O
the O
County O
among O
plenti O
odas O
wey O
make O
im O
career O
last O
ova O
sixty B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

Kenny B-PER
Rogers I-PER
don O
also O
follow O
act O
for O
plenti O
feem O
and O
TV O
shows O
wey O
include O
di O
1982 B-DATE
feem O
Six O
Pack O
. O

Di O
feem O
wey O
be O
di O
follow O
- O
up O
to O
di O
1992 B-DATE
classic O
of O
di O
same O
name O
na O
di O
first O
time O
Ramsey B-PER
Nouah I-PER
wey O
follow O
win O
di O
Best O
Director O
award O
for O
im O
work O
, O
go O
direct O
a O
movie O
. O

Di O
feem O
follow O
win O
for O
Best O
Sound O
Editor O
, O
Best O
Cinematographer O
, O
Best O
Soundtrack O
, O
Best O
Writers O
, O
Best O
Movie O
for O
West B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
Best O
Overall O
Movie O
. O

Di O
movie O
follow O
di O
life O
of O
man O
wey O
neva O
find O
work O
afta O
five B-DATE
years I-DATE
wey O
im O
don O
graduate O
and O
find O
imself O
for O
situation O
to O
make O
quick O
money O
with O
jazz O
. O

You O
fit O
find O
oda O
winners O
of O
di O
night O
here O
: O

Di O
film O
wey O
she O
do O
for O
2016 B-DATE
na O
true O
life O
story O
of O
Phiona B-PER
Mutesi I-PER
, O
wey O
begin O
play O
chess O
for O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
nine I-DATE
even O
though O
say O
e O
no O
go O
school O
and O
e O
carry O
di O
game O
go O
anoda O
level O
as O
im O
begin O
compete O
for O
international O
tournaments O
. O

For O
2017 B-DATE
, O
dem O
say O
she O
don O
recover O
but O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
dem O
find O
anoda O
tumor O
. O

Di O
62nd O
annual O
Grammy O
Awards O
go O
happun O
for O
Los B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC
on O
Sunday B-DATE
night I-DATE
, I-DATE
January I-DATE
26 I-DATE
. O

Pop O
star O
Lizzo B-PER
dey O
lead O
di O
nominations O
for O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
with O
eight O
awards O
, O
including O
album O
and O
song O
of O
di O
year O
. O

Billie B-PER
Eilish I-PER
and O
Lil B-PER
Nas I-PER
X I-PER
dey O
close O
to O
am O
with O
six O
nominations O
for O
each O
of O
dem O
. O

Angelique B-PER
Kidjo I-PER
from O
Benin B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
na O
anoda O
pesin O
wey O
also O
dey O
dis O
same O
award O
category O
wit O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
. O

Dugan B-PER
respond O
as O
she O
file O
discrimination O
complaint O
wia O
she O
suggest O
say O
di O
voting O
process O
for O
di O
Grammys O
get O
mago O
- O
mago O
inside O
. O

Dungan B-PER
still O
confam O
am O
say O
dem O
dey O
represent O
di O
artists O
to O
sit O
on O
di O
"""" O
secret O
committees O
"""" O
wey O
dey O
decide O
who O
dem O
go O
shortlist O
and O
dem O
go O
chook O
demselves O
for O
di O
list O
. O

Meanwhile O
, O
dem O
nominate O
Michelle B-PER
Obama I-PER
for O
spoken O
word O
category O
for O
di O
audiobook O
of O
her O
memoir O
, O
Becoming O
. O

Di O
musician O
, O
72 B-DATE
, O
lose O
im O
voice O
for O
di O
middle O
of O
im O
set O
for O
Auckland's B-LOC
Mount I-LOC
Smart I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
for O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

Di O
audience O
give O
am O
ogbonge O
applause O
as O
plenti O
attendants O
help O
am O
comot O
stage O
. O

Walking O
pneumonia O
na O
type O
of O
lung O
infection O
wey O
bacteria O
or O
virus O
dey O
cause O
and O
e O
no O
dey O
serious O
like O
oda O
type O
of O
pneumonia O
and O
some O
of O
im O
victims O
no O
even O
need O
go O
hospital O
. O

E O
tok O
dis O
one O
for O
di O
latest O
episode O
of O
im O
YouTube O
series O
"""" O
Justin O
Bieber O
Seasons O
"""" O
, O
di O
singer O
tok O
say O
e O
bin O
dey O
addicted O
to O
drugs O
and O
cannabis O
wen O
e O
be O
13 B-DATE
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

Di O
25 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
pop O
star O
don O
tok O
about O
im O
drug O
abuse O
and O
abusing O
im O
relationship O
before O
, O
but O
dis O
latest O
video O
na O
di O
first O
time O
e O
dey O
tok O
about O
am O
for O
camera O
. O

Di O
series O
also O
show O
di O
star O
dey O
use O
oxygen O
mask O
to O
reduce O
im O
stress O
, O
anxiety O
and O
depression O
and O
how O
e O
dey O
work O
with O
brain O
disorder O
sabi O
person O
. O

Di O
National B-ORG
Film I-ORG
and I-ORG
Video I-ORG
Censors I-ORG
Board I-ORG
announce O
wey O
dey O
approve O
feem O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
tok O
dis O
one O
for O
inside O
statement O
on O
Friday B-DATE
, I-DATE
17 I-DATE
January I-DATE
. O

Di O
director O
of O
di O
feem O
, O
Kayode B-PER
Kasum I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

Di O
mata O
make O
pipo O
start O
to O
dey O
bring O
dia O
own O
reasoning O
on O
top O
wetin O
fit O
don O
cause O
authorities O
to O
remove O
di O
movie O
as O
tori O
bin O
start O
to O
dey O
trend O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
banned O
. O

Small O
time O
afta O
, O
di O
NFVCB B-ORG
comot O
with O
statement O
say O
no O
be O
as O
Nigerians O
dey O
see O
am O
. O

Di O
executive O
director O
for O
di O
Board O
, O
Alhaji O
Adedayo B-PER
Thomas I-PER
tok O
for O
statement O
, O
"""" O
I O
take O
responsibility O
for O
di O
lack O
of O
communication O
and O
delay O
to O
grant O
final O
approval O
before O
di O
temporary O
approval O
bin O
expire O
. O
"""" O

Joseph B-PER
Shabalala I-PER
, O
wey O
help O
introduce O
di O
sound O
of O
traditional O
Zulu O
music O
to O
di O
world O
, O
don O
die O
for O
di O
age O
of O
78 B-DATE
. O

Shabalala B-PER
die O
for O
hospital O
inside O
Pretoria B-LOC
, O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
, O
di O
band O
manager O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Di O
group O
dey O
on O
tour O
for O
US B-LOC
, O
but O
dem O
don O
hear O
di O
news O
and O
e O
affect O
dia O
mood O
well O
- O
well O
becos O
di O
group O
na O
family O
. O
"""" O

Through O
your O
music O
and O
di O
millions O
wey O
you O
come O
in O
contact O
with O
, O
you O
shall O
live O
forever O
. O
"""" O

Dem O
born O
Joseph B-PER
Shabalala I-PER
for O
1941 B-DATE
and O
e O
be O
di O
eldest O
of O
eight O
children O
wey O
dey O
live O
for O
one O
farm O
inside O
Tugela B-LOC
, O
near O
di O
town O
of O
Ladysmith B-LOC
inside O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

But O
e O
come O
dey O
forced O
to O
leave O
school O
for O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
12 I-DATE
wen O
im O
papa O
die O
. O

During O
im O
spare O
time O
, O
e O
go O
sing O
with O
friends O
for O
one O
local O
group O
wey O
dem O
call O
di O
Blacks O
. O

"""" O
Wen O
di O
young O
boys O
get O
togeda O
, O
dem O
go O
start O
to O
dey O
sing O
di O
songs O
, O
until O
di O
mamas O
and O
di O
neighbours O
go O
tok O
say O
, O
'Hey O
, O
do O
am O
again O
, O
' O
"""" O
Shabalala B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
. O

"""" O
E O
just O
dey O
like O
dat O
. O

Shabalala B-PER
come O
finally O
become O
di O
leader O
and O
main O
composer O
for O
di O
choir O
, O
e O
mix O
indigenous O
Zulu O
songs O
and O
dances O
with O
South O
African O
isicathamiya O
singing O
style O
- O
dat O
na O
acapella O
tradition O
wey O
involve O
soft O
, O
shuffling O
style O
of O
dance O
. O

E O
continue O
to O
dey O
teach O
traditional O
choral O
music O
, O
while O
four O
of O
im O
sons O
( O
and O
one O
grandson O
) O
continue O
im O
legacy O
within O
Ladysmith B-ORG
Black I-ORG
Mambazo I-ORG
. O

Di O
three B-DATE
seconds I-DATE
video O
wey O
go O
viral O
on O
Friday B-DATE
don O
make O
many O
pipo O
to O
comment O
on O
social O
media O
on O
weda O
na O
her O
friend O
or O
boyfriend O
record O
am O
. O

How O
far O
you O
fit O
go O
to O
find O
your O
true O
love O
? O

Na O
di O
first O
time O
wey O
dey O
do O
dis O
kind O
of O
show O
wia O
couples O
go O
compete O
and O
one O
of O
dem O
go O
come O
as O
di O
Ultimate O
Couple O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
na O
DSTV B-ORG
dey O
organise O
am O
. O

Nollywood B-ORG
actress O
, O
Dakore B-PER
Akande I-PER
and O
radio O
OAP O
, O
Oluwaseun B-PER
na O
dem O
go O
host O
di O
show O
while O
media O
personality O
, O
Adesua B-PER
Onyenokwe I-PER
go O
be O
di O
"""" O
Aunty O
"""" O
. O

Theresa B-PER
Theresa I-PER
na O
23 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
eye O
doctor O
wey O
want O
man O
wey O
fit O
give O
her O
attention O
well O
- O
well O
. O

She O
say O
she O
don O
propose O
to O
man O
before O
but O
her O
papa O
no O
gree O
afta O
im O
realise O
say O
her O
bobo O
too O
old O
for O
her O
. O

Rosie B-PER
Rosie I-PER
na O
35 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
pre O
- O
school O
teacher O
. O

For O
di O
35 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
public O
proposal O
na O
big O
no O
- O
no O
. O

She O
dey O
find O
man O
wey O
sabi O
express O
imsef O
and O
sabi O
tok O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Cherry B-PER
na O
medical O
doctor O
from O
Imo B-LOC
state I-LOC
wit O
fine O
smile O
to O
match O
. O

Ebiteinye B-PER
believe O
say O
pesin O
fit O
find O
love O
anywia O
sharp O
- O
sharp O
. O

One O
of O
di O
youngest O
for O
di O
house O
, O
24 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
Iyke B-PER
get O
only O
one O
target O
- O
to O
find O
im O
ride O
or O
die O
. O

Jay B-PER
believe O
say O
love O
na O
all O
about O
attraction O
and O
na O
di O
basis O
for O
anytin O
else O
wey O
go O
follow O
. O

Im O
go O
like O
propose O
to O
im O
ultimate O
woman O
for O
France B-LOC
, O
near O
di O
Eiffel B-LOC
tower I-LOC
. O

Im O
don O
vow O
say O
im O
no O
go O
knack O
anybodi O
for O
di O
house O
. O

Before O
im O
performance O
, O
Plenti O
Nigerians O
wey O
no O
know O
about O
im O
coming O
, O
dey O
shock O
wey O
dem O
find O
out O
through O
im O
wife O
, O
Christine B-PER
Teigen I-PER
say O
di O
singer O
don O
enta O
Lagos B-LOC
Afta O
di O
plenti O
twitter B-ORG
reaction O
from O
Nigerians O
, O
videos O
of O
wen O
John B-PER
Legend I-PER
dey O
perform O
for O
stage O
don O
flood O
everywhere O
for O
social O
media O
, O
togeda O
with O
reactions O
from O
im O
fans O
. O

Yesterday B-DATE
, O
Sarkodie B-PER
tweet O
say O
make O
Yemi B-PER
Alade I-PER
follow O
am O
back O
on O
Twitter B-ORG
and O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
singer O
agree O
. O

Sarkodie B-PER
na O
im O
first O
call O
for O
peace O
afta O
e O
share O
for O
twitter B-ORG
di O
new O
song O
wey O
Alade B-PER
and O
Beninese O
singer O
Angélique B-PER
Kidjo I-PER
sing O
togeda O
. O

Di O
'Harriet' O
actress O
collect O
nomination O
for O
best O
actress O
and O
also O
best O
original O
song O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Academy O
Awards O
. O

If O
Erivo B-PER
win O
one O
of O
di O
categories O
, O
she O
go O
become O
di O
16th O
person O
to O
win O
Emmy O
, O
Grammy O
, O
Oscar O
and O
Tony O
Award O
. O

Di O
comic O
book O
original O
story O
dey O
up O
for O
best O
picture O
, O
best O
director O
and O
best O
actor O
for O
Joaquin B-PER
Phoenix I-PER
, O
plus O
eight O
oda O
awards O
. O

Ogbonge O
hip O
- O
hop O
music O
oga O
, O
Dr B-PER
Dre I-PER
follow O
do O
collabo O
wit O
Eminem B-PER
on O
di O
project O
as O
album O
producer O
. O

Eminem B-PER
wey O
im O
real O
name O
na O
Marshall B-PER
Mathers I-PER
, O
also O
release O
music O
video O
for O
Darkness O
, O
one O
of O
di O
songs O
inside O
di O
new O
album O
. O

South O
African O
presenter O
Bonang B-PER
Matheba I-PER
, O
na O
im O
host O
di O
event O
. O

- O
FireBoy B-PER
DML I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Killin O
Dem O
- O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Malwhede B-PER
- O
King B-PER
Monada I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Soapy O
- O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Tetema O
- O
Rayvanny B-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Zanku O
( O
Legwork O
) O
- O
Zlatan B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Baby O
- O
JoeBoy B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Case O
- O
Teni B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Rema B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Fetch O
Your O
Life O
- O
Prince B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Jama B-PER
- O
DJ B-PER
Mic I-PER
Smith I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Davido B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Diamond B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Shatta B-PER
Wale I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
ShoMadjozi B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Tiwa B-PER
Savage I-PER
( O

If O
no O
be O
dis O
wan O
today O
, O
na O
anoda O
wan O
tomorrow B-DATE
. O

Di O
House O
don O
already O
impeach O
am O
and O
President O
Trump B-PER
don O
make O
history O
as O
di O
third O
presido O
of O
di O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
wey O
dem O
go O
impeach O
. O

Wetin O
dey O
interesting O
about O
am O
na O
say O
for O
di O
first O
time O
in O
50 B-DATE
years I-DATE
citizens O
go O
get O
chance O
to O
vote O
who O
dem O
want O
by O
demsef O
, O
instead O
of O
wetin O
dey O
happun O
before O
wia O
na O
delegates O
go O
helep O
dem O
vote O
in O
one O
system O
wey O
dem O
dey O
call O
popular O
vote O
. O

Anoda O
election O
wey O
good O
to O
look O
out O
for O
for O
Africa B-LOC
na O
Burundi B-LOC
own O
. O

Im O
don O
dey O
power O
since O
2005 B-DATE
. O

Dis O
go O
be O
test O
for O
di O
local O
organising O
committee O
and O
preparation O
to O
host O
di O
African O
Nations O
Cup O
for O
2021 B-DATE
. O

Anoda O
sports O
competition O
wey O
go O
grab O
pipo O
attention O
na O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
wey O
go O
also O
happun O
for O
April B-DATE
. O

Di O
competition O
dey O
bring O
togeda O
European O
kontris O
to O
come O
play O
ball O
. O

Anoda O
big O
thing O
na O
Britain B-LOC
wey O
wan O
comot O
from O
di O
European B-ORG
Union I-ORG
. O

Di O
journey O
na O
upandan O
since O
dem O
agree O
through O
yes O
or O
no O
vote O
for O
2016 B-DATE
say O
dem O
wan O
comot O
. O

Since O
dat O
time O
, O
dem O
don O
postpone O
di O
Brexit O
mata O
several O
times O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
every O
suppose O
click O
especially O
after O
Prime O
Minister O
Boris B-PER
Johnson I-PER
win O
during O
di O
last O
general O
elections O
. O

E O
don O
tey O
wey O
Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
drop O
im O
own O
music O
and O
as O
pipo O
dey O
enjoy O
Yummy O
wey O
just O
land O
, O
e O
don O
also O
announce O
say O
im O
dey O
release O
im O
first O
album O
since O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
Sony B-ORG
dey O
move O
di O
number O
on O
top O
dia O
Play O
Station O
series O
to O
5 O
. O

With O
No O
Time O
To O
Die O
( O
James B-PER
bond I-PER
feem O
) O
, O
Coming O
to O
America B-LOC
, O
Bad O
Boys O
For O
Life O
with O
some O
ogbonge O
, O
correct O
superhero O
movies O
like O
Black O
Widow O
wey O
dey O
drop O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
cinema O
go O
just O
dey O
hungry O
you O
to O
go O
. O

Power O
, O
Modern O
Family O
, O
Arrow O
and O
Lucifer O
na O
some O
of O
di O
shows O
wey O
dey O
comot O
from O
our O
screen O
for O
dis O
new B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

For O
now O
, O
e O
never O
clear O
wen O
e O
go O
happun O
. O

Dis O
go O
be O
di O
fourth O
edition O
of O
di O
Big O
Brother O
Naija O
edition O
. O

Ghana B-LOC
follow O
show O
interest O
for O
dis O
mata O
because O
West B-LOC
African I-LOC
kontris I-LOC
bin O
don O
dey O
tok O
single O
currency O
to O
helep O
trade O
. O

Wetin O
go O
happun O
with O
di O
Cameroon B-LOC
crisis O
and O
di O
recent O
Anglophone O
palava O
, O
wey O
don O
dey O
ground O
since O
2017 B-DATE
and O
lead O
to O
di O
death O
of O
plenti O
pipo O
? O

Last B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
Presido O
Paul B-PER
Biya I-PER
hold O
National O
Dialogue O
plus O
some O
oda O
tins O
im O
do O
so O
peace O
go O
dey O
di O
region O
including O
to O
give O
di O
region O
special O
status O
. O

Plenti O
goments O
across O
di O
world O
for O
dia O
new B-DATE
year I-DATE
messages O
don O
promise O
wetin O
dem O
go O
do O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
to O
boost O
dia O
kontries O
. O

Na O
sake O
of O
di O
closing O
of O
dis O
Art B-LOC
and I-LOC
Craft I-LOC
Village I-LOC
inside O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
make O
one O
High B-ORG
Court I-ORG
for O
Abuja B-LOC
on O
Thursday B-DATE
send O
di O
Director O
- O
General O
of O
Council O
to O
go O
stay O
for O
prison O
. O

Runsewe B-PER
dey O
chill O
for O
prison O
afta O
Ummakalif B-PER
ask O
court O
to O
commit O
am O
to O
prison O
becos O
im O
disobey O
court O
order O
. O

Di O
musician O
make O
announcement O
for O
social O
media O
say O
im O
don O
sign O
di O
final O
agreement O
with O
goment O
for O
di O
Akon B-LOC
city I-LOC
. O

Im O
bin O
tok O
say O
e O
go O
build O
di O
city O
on O
top O
2 O
, O
000 O
acre O
of O
land O
wey O
di O
Presido O
of O
Senegal B-LOC
, O
Macky B-PER
Sall I-PER
dash O
am O
. O

Lawyer O
to O
Naira B-PER
marley I-PER
, O
Ayodeji B-PER
Awokunlehin I-PER
claim O
say O
all O
di O
accuse O
wey O
dem O
sama O
against O
di O
singer O
na O
lie O
and O
dem O
don O
even O
fix O
di O
car O
of O
di O
pesin O
wey O
carry O
di O
mata O
come O
court O
. O

Di O
name O
come O
from O
time O
wen O
di O
rich O
bin O
dey O
box O
up O
gifts O
to O
give O
di O
poor O
. O

Di O
day O
also O
get O
religious O
connections O
and O
dem O
dey O
celebrate O
am O
as O
Saint B-DATE
Stephen's I-DATE
Day I-DATE
for O
Ireland B-LOC
and O
DI O
Catalonia B-LOC
region I-LOC
of O
Spain B-LOC
. O

Through O
out O
di O
year O
, O
dem O
go O
collect O
money O
from O
churchgoers O
in O
di O
form O
of O
collection O
and O
give O
am O
out O
for O
Christmas B-DATE
. O

Na O
also O
public O
holiday O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
nd O
some O
oda O
kontries O
around O
di O
world O
. O
. O
Wen O
26 B-DATE
December I-DATE
na O
Saturday B-DATE
, O
di O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
holiday O
go O
move O
to O
di O
next B-DATE
Monday I-DATE
. O

Di O
final O
Christmas B-DATE
Day I-DATE
football O
match O
happun O
for O
1957 B-DATE
, O
dis O
wan O
make O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
di O
traditional O
festive O
fixture O
. O

Hmm O
, O
my O
mouth O
don O
dey O
water O
already O
. O

Di O
Marvel B-ORG
Cinematic O
Universe O
don O
dey O
set O
to O
get O
dia O
first O
transgender O
superhero O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Eternals O
go O
introduce O
Marvel B-ORG
movie O
first O
gay O
character O
. O

Dem O
point O
out O
say O
di O
only O
existing O
trans O
superhero O
inside O
Marvel B-ORG
Comics I-ORG
na O
Sera B-PER
wey O
dem O
recently O
introduce O
from O
one O
group O
of O
all O
- O
male O
angels O
wey O
dem O
call O
di O
Ancharites O
- O
wey O
transition O
from O
man O
to O
woman O
. O

She O
act O
for O
Thor B-PER
world O
- O
dem O
keep O
am O
inside O
one O
temple O
for O
di O
realm O
of O
Heven O
before O
she O
come O
meet O
Thor B-PER
long O
- O
lost O
half O
- O
sister O
Angela B-PER
, O
wey O
come O
finally O
be O
her O
romantic O
interest O
. O

Tessa B-PER
Thompson I-PER
character O
Valkyrie B-PER
- O
wey O
Thor B-PER
make O
di O
King O
of O
New O
Asgard O
for O
di O
last O
Avengers O
film O
- O
reveal O
wetin O
di O
"""" O
first O
order O
of O
business O
"""" O
go O
be O
for O
her O
inside O
di O
feem O
. O

2019 B-DATE
Big O
Brother O
Naija O
, O
Pepper O
Dem O
season O
housemate O
Khafi B-PER
Kareem I-PER
don O
engage O
. O

Actress O
Sharon B-PER
Stone I-PER
say O
dem O
block O
am O
for O
di O
dating O
app O
, O
Bumble O
. O

And O
say O
some O
pipo O
bin O
report O
her O
give O
di O
online O
platform O
sat O
her O
profile O
na O
fake O
. O

Di O
62 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
ogbonge O
actress O
rake O
give O
dem O
on O
top O
Twitter B-ORG
, O
as O
she O
ask O
weda O
she O
no O
fit O
join O
di O
platform O
on O
top O
say O
she O
na O
star O
. O

Di O
app O
editorial O
director O
, O
Clare B-PER
O'Connor I-PER
, O
say O
"""" O
Trust O
us O
, O
we O
want O
make O
you O
dey O
di O
Hive O
. O

Na O
since O
2014 B-DATE
, O
she O
don O
tok O
say O
she O
dey O
available O
for O
dating O
and O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
she O
say O
she O
like O
for O
her O
men O
to O
dey O
tall O
. O

Dem O
arrest O
Mollie B-PER
Fitzgerald I-PER
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
, O
charge O
am O
with O
second O
- O
degree O
murder O
afta O
authorities O
find O
68 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
Patricia B-PER
Fitzgerald I-PER
wey O
be O
her O
mama O
, O
dead O
for O
dia O
Olathe B-LOC
, O
Kansas B-LOC
, O
home O
on O
December B-DATE
20 I-DATE
, O
according O
to O
di O
Olathe B-ORG
Police I-ORG
Department I-ORG
. O

Authorities O
neva O
know O
wetin O
make O
her O
stab O
her O
mama O
but O
dem O
don O
arrange O
say O
she O
go O
appear O
for O
court O
again O
for O
January B-DATE
9 I-DATE
. O

Dem O
sabi O
her O
well O
for O
di O
appearance O
wey O
she O
make O
for O
di O
2011 B-DATE
Marvel B-ORG
film O
Captain O
America B-LOC
: O
Di O
First O
Avenger O
. O

But O
also O
e O
don O
cari O
small O
gbas O
gbos O
about O
Nigerians O
and O
Ghanaians O
back O
for O
table O
, O
as O
Cardi B-PER
B I-PER
visit O
di O
two O
kontris O
for O
her O
first O
trip O
to O
Africa B-LOC
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

Soundcity B-ORG
don O
announce O
di O
nomination O
list O
for O
dia O
MVP O
Awards O
show O
wey O
go O
happun O
for O
January B-DATE
11 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
. O

For O
dia O
2019 B-DATE
show O
, O
di O
event O
trend O
afta O
di O
mama O
of O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
comot O
to O
collect O
her O
pikin O
award O
. O

Di O
event O
producer O
, O
Adeniji B-PER
Daniel I-PER
tok O
say O
"""" O
di O
show O
go O
get O
international O
show O
hosts O
, O
collabo O
you O
no O
go O
expect O
and O
pop O
culture O
moments O
wey O
go O
make O
pipo O
tok O
for O
a O
long O
time O
"""" O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
nominees O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Soundcity B-ORG
MVP O
Awards O
. O

Tetema O
- O
Rayvanny B-PER
x O
Diamond B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Zanku O
( O
Legwork O
) O
- O
Zlatan B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
BEST O
FEMALE O
MVP O
Betty B-PER
G I-PER
( O
ETH B-LOC
) O
Daphne B-PER
( O
CMR B-LOC
) O
Nandy B-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Sho B-PER
Madjozi I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Teni B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Tiwa B-PER
Savage I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Yemi B-PER
Alade I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
BEST O
MALE O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Davido B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Diamond B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
King B-PER
Promise I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Sjava B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Wizkid B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Zlatan B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
SONG O
OF O
DI O
YEAR O
Baby O
- O
Joeboy B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Case O
- O
Teni B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Rema B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

Organizers O
of O
di O
concert O
, O
Nativeland O
, O
don O
comot O
to O
tok O
sorry O
afta O
dia O
every B-DATE
year I-DATE
show O
wey O
happun O
on O
Thursday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

But O
BBC B-ORG
tori O
pesin O
Yemisi B-PER
Adegoke I-PER
, O
wey O
attend O
di O
event O
say O
di O
stage O
bin O
collapse O
as O
dem O
bin O
all O
dey O
on O
top O
and O
di O
staff O
bin O
no O
even O
boda O
to O
ask O
if O
any O
pesin O
injure O
for O
di O
fall O
. O

Even O
celebs O
sef O
chook O
dia O
mouth O
put O
for O
inside O
di O
Nativeland O
mata O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
4th O
edition O
of O
di O
show O
wey O
don O
feature O
Davido B-PER
, O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
, O
Teni B-PER
di O
Entertainer O
before O
. O

Sierra B-LOC
Leone I-LOC
Tourism O
Minister O
Memunatu B-PER
Pratt I-PER
describe O
Elba B-PER
visit O
as O
"""" O
homecoming O
"""" O
. O

Elba B-PER
bin O
act O
as O
Nelson B-PER
Mandela I-PER
for O
di O
feem O
Long O
Walk O
to O
Freedom O
, O
but O
im O
blow O
afta O
im O
act O
for O
HBO B-ORG
series O
The O
Wire O
, O
for O
di O
feem O
im O
act O
as O
drug O
capone O
for O
Stringer O
Bell O
. O

Im O
also O
act O
for O
Netflix B-ORG
feem O
Beasts O
of O
No O
Nation O
about O
child O
soldiers O
. O

Elba B-PER
bin O
meet O
President O
Bio B-PER
for O
one O
investment O
conference O
for O
UK B-LOC
and O
also O
for O
UN B-ORG
General O
Assembly O
meeting O
for O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
. O

Ms O
Tunzi B-PER
come O
out O
top O
for O
di O
contest O
afta O
she O
impress O
di O
judges O
and O
fans O
through O
di O
different O
rounds O
wit O
her O
different O
outfits O
. O

"""" O
Na O
something O
wey O
young O
girls O
and O
women O
dey O
lack O
for O
very O
long O
time O
now O
because O
we O
no O
want O
to O
but O
because O
of O
wetin O
society O
don O
label O
women O
to O
be O
. O

Dem O
dey O
use O
di O
# O
GhanavrsNaija O
take O
tok O
about O
Cardi B-PER
B I-PER
post O
and O
many O
oda O
issues O
. O

Thief O
pipo O
don O
steal O
£ O
50m O
worth O
of O
jewellery O
from O
Tamara B-PER
Ecclestone I-PER
house O
for O
Kensington B-LOC
. O

According O
to O
tori O
pipo O
The B-ORG
Sun I-ORG
, O
rings O
, O
earrings O
, O
one O
Cartier B-PER
bangle O
wey O
reach O
£ O
80 O
, O
000 O
, O
wey O
her O
papa O
give O
her O
as O
wedding O
present O
dey O
among O
wetin O
dem O
tiff O
. O

Di O
Met B-ORG
Police I-ORG
say O
dem O
neva O
arrest O
anybody O
. O

Tok O
- O
tok O
pesin O
for O
Ecclestone B-PER
say O
: O
"""" O
I O
go O
fit O
confam O
say O
dem O
break O
enta O
house O
. O

"""" O
Tamara B-PER
and O
family O
dey O
angry O
and O
dey O
shake O
sake O
of O
di O
incident O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Dem O
report O
di O
amount O
of O
jewellery O
wey O
dem O
tiff O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
di O
tok O
- O
tok O
pesin O
add O
put O
. O

E O
claim O
say O
Imo B-LOC
state I-LOC
goment O
under O
di O
tenure O
of O
Owelle B-PER
Rochas I-PER
Okorocha I-PER
, O
through O
di O
office O
of O
di O
SA B-LOC
on O
Entertainment O
, O
sign O
one O
deal O
with O
Duncan B-PER
Mighty I-PER
to O
manage O
, O
promote O
, O
arrange O
collaboration O
with O
oda O
top O
artist O
and O
sign O
M2 B-PER
under O
YOUNG B-ORG
WEALTH I-ORG
record I-ORG
label I-ORG
wey O
be O
Duncan B-PER
Mighty I-PER
own O
. O

Davido B-PER
feature O
many O
guest O
artist O
from O
Popcaan B-PER
, O
Peruzzi B-PER
, O
Zlatan B-PER
, O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
, O
WurlD B-PER
, O
Summer B-PER
Walker I-PER
, O
Chris B-PER
Brown I-PER
, O
Gunna B-PER
, O
Dremo B-PER
, O
A B-PER
Boogie I-PER
Wit I-PER
Da I-PER
Hoodie I-PER
and O
Yonda B-PER
. O

Di O
collabo O
wey O
Grammy O
- O
nominated O
Afro O
beat O
singer O
, O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
do O
togeda O
with O
Ghanaian O
rapper O
Stormzy B-PER
and O
English O
singer O
- O
songwriter O
Ed B-PER
Sheeran I-PER
don O
pass O
one O
million O
view O
for O
Youtube O
under O
24 B-DATE
hours I-DATE
. O

Di O
song O
wey O
dey O
all O
about O
promise O
of O
love O
na O
4 B-DATE
- I-DATE
minute I-DATE
video O
and O
e O
don O
get O
more O
than O
1 O
, O
122 O
, O
410 O
views O
for O
YouTube O
. O

Dis O
no O
be O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
first O
international O
collabo O
. O

E O
don O
work O
with O
artists O
like O
Beyonce B-PER
, O
Jorja B-PER
Smith I-PER
and O
Lily B-PER
Allen I-PER
. O
