Even O
though O
dem O
dey O
away O
from O
dia O
training O
base O
for O
Carrington B-LOC
, O
Solskjaer's B-PER
staff O
still O
dey O
monitor O
di O
players O
fitness O
, O
weight O
and O
nutrition O

Italy B-LOC
never O
decide O
how O
dem O
go O
do O
dia O
own O
top O
league O
but O
some O
clubs O
don O
return O
to O
training O
. O

Bjornsson B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
powerlifter O
play O
di O
role O
of O
Ser O
Gregor O
"""" O
Di O
Mountain O
"""" O
Clegane O
for O
di O
HBO B-ORG
series O
, O
break O
di O
record O
for O
Im O
own O
gym O
for O
Im O
hometown O
, O
Iceland B-LOC
. O

He O
lift O
di O
barbell O
for O
two B-DATE
seconds I-DATE
, O
before O
im O
drop O
drop O
di O
weights O
. O

However O
, O
Philippe B-PER
tok O
say O
: O
"""" O
Di O
2019 B-DATE
- I-DATE
20 I-DATE
season O
of O
professional O
sports O
, O
including O
football O
, O
no O
go O
fit O
resume O
. O

"""" O
E O
go O
dey O
possible O
, O
on O
sunny O
days O
, O
to O
practice O
individual O
sporting O
activity O
outdoors O
, O
as O
dem O
go O
respect O
di O
rules O
of O
social O
distancing O
. O

European O
leagues O
get O
until O
25 B-DATE
May I-DATE
to O
tell O
European O
football O
goment O
join O
- O
bodi O
Uefa B-ORG
weda O
dem O
wan O
complete O
or O
cancel O
dia O
seasons O
. O

Di O
head O
of O
di O
Dutch B-ORG
FA I-ORG
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
say O
im O
tink O
say O
e O
dey O
"""" O
very O
doubtful O
"""" O
say O
Premier O
League O
go O
fit O
complete O
di O
2019 B-DATE
- I-DATE
20 I-DATE
campaign O
. O

Dis O
na O
one O
of O
di O
many O
tins O
wey O
go O
change O
for O
football O
reality O
sake O
of O
Coronavirus O
. O

But O
di O
first O
match O
go O
be O
Köln B-ORG
vs O
Mainz B-ORG
by O
2 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30pm I-DATE
Sunday I-DATE
. O

Police O
make O
sure O
say O
fans O
no O
gada O
outside O
. O

Meanwhile O
, O
dem O
don O
postpone O
di O
second O
leg O
of O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
last O
- O
16 O
second O
leg O
Champions O
League O
tie O
against O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
, O
wey O
dem O
wan O
play O
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
17 I-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

Di O
result O
mean O
say O
dem O
dey O
13 O
position O
for O
table O
with O
28 O
points O
. O

Dem O
don O
confam O
di O
condition O
of O
both O
of O
dem O
. O

Dem O
bin O
postpone O
di O
fight O
on O
top O
di O
coronavirus O
palava O
for O
world O
. O

Joshua B-PER
neva O
fight O
since O
December B-DATE
wen O
im O
win O
di O
fight O
against O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jr I-PER
for O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
to O
collect O
back O
im O
belts O
wey O
di O
Mexican O
- O
American O
bin O
collect O
for O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
wen O
dem O
first O
fight O
for O
June B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
. O

Everton B-ORG
don O
score O
in O
all O
10 O
of O
dia O
league O
games O
under O
the O
Italian O
- O
di O
current O
longest O
scoring O
run O
for O
di O
division O
. O

Im O
last O
fight O
, O
im O
win O
with O
unanimous O
points O
victory O
, O
against O
American O
Rydell B-PER
Booker I-PER
, O
for O
November B-DATE
. O

Na O
during O
im O
waka O
come O
back O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
, O
di O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
player O
die O
from O
wetin O
im O
club O
say O
na O
police O
fault O
. O

"""" O
Wen O
you O
see O
di O
white O
shirt O
you O
go O
know O
exactly O
which O
club O
e O
dey O
stand O
for O
, O
dem O
dey O
very O
big O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Sterling B-PER
tok O
. O

Dem O
ask O
am O
weda O
im O
go O
like O
play O
for O
Real B-ORG
, O
im O
tok O
say O
: O
"""" O
How O
I O
go O
carry O
answer O
dis O
one O
? O

Di O
American O
, O
34 B-DATE
, O
say O
im O
costume O
heavy O
so O
tey O
"""" O
legs O
weak O
am O
"""" O
for O
di O
fight O
. O

Fury B-PER
on O
di O
oda O
hand O
no O
use O
im O
leg O
waka O
enta O
ring O
as O
im O
sidon O
ontop O
throne O
wey O
four O
pipo O
carri O
. O

"""" O
I O
respect O
say O
im O
na O
big O
man O
for O
sports O
but O
di O
law O
no O
dey O
respect O
pesin O
. O

For O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
Strip O
, O
fans O
fit O
pay O
$ O
100 O
( O
£ O
77 O
) O
to O
watch O
di O
fight O
for O
big O
screen O
while O
di O
fight O
go O
cost O
$ O
74 O
. O
99 O
( O
£ O
58 O
) O
to O
buy O
for O
house O
for O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
live O
for O
US B-LOC
, O
e O
mean O
say O
dem O
fit O
raise O
up O
to O
$ O
150m O
( O
£ O
116m O
) O
even O
before O
dem O
collect O
ticket O
money O
. O

I O
believe O
say O
Fury B-PER
go O
survive O
some O
difficult O
moment O
and O
then O
win O
on O
points O
. O

"""" O
Dis O
na O
di O
moment O
we O
don O
dey O
wait O
for O
tey O
- O
tey O
, O
"""" O
dat O
na O
wetin O
Wilder B-PER
tok O
dis B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

SugarHill B-PER
Steward I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
policeman O
before O
, O
dey O
call O
imself O
"""" O
di O
knockout O
architect O
"""" O
, O
afta O
im O
learn O
how O
to O
box O
for O
di O
legendary O
Detroit B-ORG
Kronk I-ORG
Gym I-ORG
. O

According O
to O
one O
local O
news O
website O
for O
Lorraine B-LOC
, O
kasala O
burst O
wen O
one O
of O
di O
players O
from O
each O
of O
di O
team O
begin O
fight O
demself O
, O
another O
Terville B-ORG
player O
come O
join O
, O
tori O
be O
say O
im O
try O
to O
separate O
dem O
. O

Di O
incident O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
for O
di O
stadium O
car O
park O
. O

Dis O
don O
end O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
five B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
reign O
as O
WBC O
heavyweight O
world O
champion O
. O

But O
Fury B-PER
do O
wetin O
im O
do O
and O
I O
no O
get O
excuses O
. O
"""" O

Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
tok O
. O

United B-ORG
bin O
decide O
to O
no O
carry O
di O
striker O
go O
dia O
winter O
break O
training O
camp O
for O
Spain B-LOC
becos O
of O
concern O
say O
im O
fit O
experience O
difficulty O
to O
return O
back O
to O
UK B-LOC
. O

Ighalo B-PER
, O
30 B-DATE
, O
dey O
expected O
to O
travel O
with O
di O
squad O
for O
Monday B-DATE
game O
against O
Chelsea B-ORG
. O

Na O
for O
di O
National B-ORG
Taekwondo I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
wey O
dey O
close O
to O
Etihad B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
and O
wia O
im O
don O
dey O
stay O
dem O
dey O
use O
since O
e O
land O
from O
China B-LOC
11 B-DATE
days I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

Yobo B-PER
wey O
play O
100 O
matches O
for O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
also O
play O
for O
Everton B-ORG
, O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
, O
Marseille B-ORG
, O
Standard B-ORG
Liege I-ORG
and O
Norwich B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

Fans O
target O
Mikel B-PER
on O
social O
media O
afta O
2 O
- O
1 O
victory O
wey O
move O
Trabzonspor B-ORG
above O
dia O
opponents O
into O
third O
place O
. O

E O
no O
dey O
possible O
to O
say O
. O

Bet O
, O
e O
fair O
to O
assume O
say O
afta O
im O
win O
Premier O
League O
titles O
back O
- O
to O
- O
back O
with O
ogbonge O
points O
for O
table O
, O
plus O
become O
di O
first O
side O
to O
gbab O
all O
di O
three O
domestic O
trophies O
for O
one O
single O
season O
, O
Guardiola B-PER
morale O
fit O
dey O
low O
. O

Even O
if O
City B-ORG
win O
di O
Champions O
League O
this O
season O
, O
Guardiola B-PER
still O
waka O
. O

Meanwhile O
, O
oda O
clubs O
dey O
call O
to O
ask O
Ighalo B-PER
to O
sign O
for O
dem O
. O

United B-ORG
boss O
Ole B-PER
Gunnar I-PER
Solskjaer I-PER
say O
: O
"""" O
We O
don O
dey O
track O
Bruno B-PER
for O
many O
months O
and O
everyone O
hia O
dey O
very O
impressed O
wit O
all O
im O
attributes O
and O
wetin O
im O
go O
bring O
to O
dis O
team O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
two O
clubs O
don O
dey O
negotiate O
throughout O
di O
transfer O
window O
until O
Tuesday B-DATE
wey O
dem O
get O
breakthrough O
afta O
reports O
begin O
fly O
up O
and O
down O
say O
Barcelona B-ORG
sef O
dey O
interested O
. O

"""" O
Pipo O
for O
media O
dey O
ask O
why O
Benfica B-ORG
, O
Sporting B-ORG
or O
Porto B-ORG
no O
go O
for O
Fernandes B-PER
because O
im O
be O
fantastic O
player O
. O
"""" O

Tori O
be O
say O
dis O
na O
United B-ORG
first O
senior O
loan O
signing O
since O
Radamel B-PER
Falcao I-PER
for O
2014 B-DATE
. O

Ighalo B-PER
na O
di O
third O
player O
wey O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
sign O
for O
dis O
January B-DATE
transfer O
window O
, O
afta O
dem O
sign O
Bruno B-PER
Fernandes I-PER
from O
Sporting B-ORG
Lisbon I-ORG
and O
Southend B-ORG
goalkeeper O
Nathan B-PER
Bishop I-PER
. O

Na O
within O
two B-DATE
hours I-DATE
of O
losing O
to O
Leicester B-ORG
na O
im O
West B-ORG
Ham I-ORG
make O
di O
announcement O
. O

We O
ask O
Essien B-PER
who O
be O
im O
top O
players O
from O
di O
last O
decade O
. O

Vincent B-PER
Enyeama I-PER
arguably O
be O
Nigeria B-LOC
best O
player O
for O
di O
2014 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
wen O
dem O
qualify O
to O
di O
knockout O
stage O
. O

Di O
Cameroonian O
peak O
for O
Tottenham B-ORG
for O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
and O
na O
one O
of O
di O
best O
left O
backs O
for O
Premier O
League O
under O
Harry B-PER
Redknapp I-PER
. O

E O
also O
captain O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
to O
dia O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
crown O
for O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Di O
"""" O
Egyptian O
King O
"""" O
na O
di O
only O
African O
player O
to O
make O
di O
Fifa B-ORG
Best O
top O
3 O
dis O
decade O
. O

For O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
Drogba B-PER
reach O
im O
career O
high O
of O
37 O
goals O
to O
help O
Chelsea B-ORG
win O
domestic O
Cup O
double O
and O
also O
win O
e O
second O
Premier O
League O
Golden O
Boot O
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
fit O
play O
like O
dat O
. O

Leicester B-ORG
manage O
to O
match O
brake O
for O
di O
ginger O
wey O
Brentford B-ORG
carri O
come O
for O
second O
half O
of O
dem O
two O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
fourth O
round O
match O
. O

E O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
MOTD I-ORG
: O
"""" O
We O
dey O
happy O
for O
di O
win O
today B-DATE
and O
to O
go O
to O
di O
next O
round O
. O

We O
work O
really O
hard O
to O
di O
end O
and O
stand O
our O
ground O
. O

Dr O
Newson B-PER
suggest O
say O
make O
stadiums O
dey O
dim O
light O
, O
play O
music O
wey O
dey O
calm O
bodi O
afta O
games O
wey O
no O
go O
well O
. O

Before O
di O
tournament O
, O
Togo B-LOC
decide O
to O
camp O
for O
Pointe B-LOC
Noir I-LOC
for O
Republic B-LOC
of I-LOC
Congo I-LOC
, O
just O
over O
100km O
from O
wia O
dem O
go O
play O
dia O
group O
games O
for O
Angola B-LOC
city O
of O
Cabinda B-LOC
. O

Players O
bin O
just O
dey O
laugh O
and O
joking O
amongst O
demselves O
for O
di O
bus O
. O

Di O
small O
convoy O
move O
from O
di O
border O
, O
to O
di O
road O
through O
di O
forest O
. O

Im O
life O
change O
for O
just O
few O
seconds O
, O
as O
e O
realise O
say O
dem O
don O
shoot O
am O
too O
. O

I O
no O
wan O
die O
here O
. O
' O
"""" O

Even O
as O
im O
dey O
handle O
e O
own O
injuries O
, O
and O
fear O
, O
Obilale B-PER
bin O
dey O
able O
to O
remember O
and O
tok O
wetin O
happun O
dat O
day O
. O

"""" O
I O
think O
dat O
na O
di O
worst O
moment O
of O
dis O
day O
, O
because O
you O
fit O
see O
pipo O
tell O
dia O
last O
words O
, O
because O
dem O
think O
say O
dem O
go O
die O
. O
"""" O

Throughout O
di O
meal O
, O
evriwia O
bin O
dey O
silent O
. O

Odas O
na O
e O
former O
captain O
Adebayor B-PER
and O
Ghana B-LOC
Ayew B-PER
brothers O
- O
Andre B-PER
Ayew I-PER
and O
e O
brother O
Rahim B-PER
bin O
dey O
part O
of O
di O
Black B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
squad O
wey O
play O
for O
Cabinda B-LOC
for O
2010 B-DATE
. O

"""" O
E O
bin O
dey O
psychologically O
catastrophic O
, O
e O
turn O
[ O
tins O
] O
upside O
down O
, O
"""" O
na O
so O
im O
tok O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
keep O
me O
going O
but O
of O
course O
work O
still O
dey O
to O
do O
, O
I O
want O
to O
create O
my O
own O
history O
and O
not O
just O
equal O
someone O
else O
record O
- O
I O
go O
give O
my O
best O
to O
create O
my O
own O
. O
"""" O

Oshoala B-PER
, O
wey O
claim O
di O
award O
for O
2014 B-DATE
, O
2016 B-DATE
and O
2017 B-DATE
, O
bin O
dey O
up O
against O
Valerenga B-ORG
and O
Cameroon B-LOC
forward O
Ajara B-PER
Nchout I-PER
plus O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
winner O
Thembi B-PER
Kgatlana I-PER
of O
Beijing B-ORG
BG I-ORG
Phoenix I-ORG
and O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

Toure B-PER
add O
: O
"""" O
Of O
course O
e O
dey O
shocking O
because O
na O
2019 B-DATE
we O
dey O
. O

For O
2020 B-DATE
, O
2025 B-DATE
we O
go O
get O
young O
pikin O
dem O
wey O
don O
grow O
- O
wetin O
we O
go O
come O
do O
? O

Di O
former O
midfielder O
sabi O
speak O
plenty O
language O
dem O
, O
im O
dey O
speak O
Spanish O
, O
Basque O
, O
Catalan O
and O
English O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Ancelotti B-PER
wey O
Napoli B-ORG
bin O
sack O
early B-DATE
dis I-DATE
month I-DATE
, O
go O
take O
ova O
from O
Marco B-PER
Silva I-PER
, O
wey O
Everton B-ORG
sack O
for O
6 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

Oga O
Ancelotti B-PER
wey O
be O
former O
AC B-ORG
Milan I-ORG
, O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
, O
Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
and O
Paris B-ORG
St I-ORG
- I-ORG
Germain I-ORG
boss O
tok O
say O
Everton B-ORG
"""" O
na O
great O
club O
with O
rich O
history O
and O
a O
very O
passionate O
fanbase O
. O
"""" O

Dat O
na O
something O
wey O
I O
like O
me O
as O
a O
manager O
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
relaxed O
becos O
I O
know O
wetin O
I O
go O
do O
. O
"""" O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
sama O
Newcastle B-ORG
4 O
- O
1 O
for O
Old B-LOC
Trafford I-LOC
. O

Fury B-PER
survive O
knockdown O
two O
times O
from O
di O
American O
to O
get O
draw O
during O
di O
Los B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC
fight O
. O

Fury B-PER
defeat O
Germany B-LOC
fighter O
Tom B-PER
Schwarz I-PER
for O
June B-DATE
, O
but O
im O
injure O
im O
eye O
during O
di O
beating O
im O
give O
Swedish O
man O
Otto B-PER
Wallin I-PER
for O
September B-DATE
. O

Joshua B-PER
na O
im O
get O
di O
oda O
three O
world O
heavyweight O
belts O
- O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBO O
and O
WBA O
titles O
. O

Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
go O
face O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
while O
reigning O
champions O
Liverpool B-ORG
go O
play O
Atletico B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
for O
di O
round O
of O
16 O
of O
dis O
season O
Champions O
League O
. O

From O
Kevin B-PER
De I-PER
Bruyne I-PER
, O
to O
Raheem B-PER
Sterlin I-PER
to O
Ilkay B-PER
Gündogan I-PER
. O

Liverpool B-ORG
midfielder O
James B-PER
Milner I-PER
no O
dey O
hide O
am O
say O
im O
no O
like O
VAR O
at O
all O
. O

For O
November B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
, O
Chelsea B-ORG
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Frank B-PER
Lampard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

"""" O
On O
Wednesday B-DATE
afternoon I-DATE
, O
Rummenigge B-PER
bin O
call O
me O
. O

Di O
fight O
go O
happun O
from O
8 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
PM I-DATE
Nigerian O
Time O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
. O

I O
know O
say O
im O
lost O
weight O
. O
. O
. O

Di O
American O
bin O
struggle O
for O
di O
fight O
as O
Ruiz B-PER
start O
strong O
for O
dia O
rematch O
fight O
wey O
happun O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

But O
for O
seventh O
round O
, O
Wilder B-PER
right O
hand O
blow O
land O
Ortiz B-PER
for O
ground O
. O

Mexican O
boxer O
, O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jr I-PER
bin O
scata O
Joshua B-PER
perfect O
record O
for O
boxing O
for O
June B-DATE
but O
now O
, O
Joshua B-PER
don O
join O
di O
ogbonge O
group O
of O
boxers O
wey O
don O
fight O
collect O
dia O
titles O
back O
. O

Marcus B-PER
Rashford I-PER
bin O
praise O
di O
Bulgaria B-LOC
captain O
for O
im O
"""" O
courage O
"""" O
afta O
di O
match O
ontop O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

"""" O
He O
be O
son O
, O
brother O
, O
and O
good O
friend O
to O
many O
, O
"""" O
one O
statement O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Patrick B-PER
kindness O
, O
positivity O
, O
and O
generosity O
of O
spirit O
make O
am O
be O
correct O
pesin O
to O
anyone O
wey O
im O
meet O
. O
"""" O

Joe B-PER
Aribo I-PER
score O
Nigeria B-LOC
first O
goal O
for O
di O
35th B-DATE
minute I-DATE
of O
di O
game O
afta O
im O
collect O
fine O
pass O
from O
Simon B-PER
inside O
di O
penalty O
box O
. O

Senegal B-LOC
International O
player O
Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
score O
di O
first O
goal O
for O
di O
defending O
champions O
. O

Goals O
from O
Norwich B-ORG
top O
scorer O
Teemu B-PER
Pukki I-PER
, O
Todd B-PER
Cantwell I-PER
and O
Kenny B-PER
McLean I-PER
na O
im O
help O
di O
newly O
promoted O
side O
beat O
di O
reigning O
league O
champions O
. O

But O
Siasia B-PER
say O
di O
police O
no O
get O
good O
news O
for O
am O
ontop O
her O
rescue O
. O

Police O
tok O
- O
tok O
pesin O
for O
Bayelsa B-LOC
state I-LOC
, O
SP O
Butswat B-PER
Asinim I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
investigation O
still O
dey O
go O
on O
and O
dem O
neva O
relax O
for O
di O
mata O
to O
rescue O
Samson B-PER
Siasia I-PER
mama O
. O

Im O
add O
am O
say O
very O
soon O
dem O
go O
make O
sure O
say O
dem O
save O
her O
from O
kidnappers O
hand O
Di O
kidnappers O
dey O
demand O
for O
N70 O
million O
from O
di O
family O
to O
release O
her O
, O
according O
to O
wetin O
one O
family O
member O
bin O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
But O
SP O
Butswat B-PER
say O
di O
kidnappers O
no O
dey O
demand O
any O
moni O
. O

"""" O
What O
else O
I O
fit O
do O
now O
but O
to O
beg O
for O
assistance O
from O
di O
goment O
, O
police O
and O
my O
kontri O
wey O
I O
don O
serve O
as O
player O
and O
coach O
, O
"""" O
Siasia B-PER
tok O
. O

"""" O
My O
mama O
sickness O
dey O
serious O
and O
dis O
dey O
worry O
me O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Red O
hot O
Lille B-ORG
of O
France B-LOC
striker O
Victor B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
wey O
don O
score O
six O
goals O
for O
French O
league O
go O
dey O
expected O
to O
lead O
di O
line O
again O
. O

"""" O
We O
don O
hear O
wetin O
di O
critics O
dey O
tok O
and O
we O
sef O
don O
follow O
di O
organisers O
yarn O
about O
am O
. O

Some O
pipo O
don O
criticize O
di O
event O
wen O
di O
tori O
comot O
say O
na O
for O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
e O
go O
happun O
. O

To O
go O
back O
work O
Pressure O
don O
dey O
goment O
neck O
to O
reduce O
restrictions O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
work O
. O

Bangladesh B-LOC
wey O
be O
di O
second O
largest O
explorer O
of O
clothes O
for O
world O
dem O
don O
dey O
suffer O
on O
top O
cancellation O
of O
orders O
from O
Europe B-LOC
and O
South B-LOC
America I-LOC
. O

Rubana B-PER
Huq I-PER
, O
president O
of O
Bangladesh B-ORG
Garment I-ORG
Manufacturers I-ORG
and I-ORG
Exporters I-ORG
Association I-ORG
say O
two O
million O
of O
dia O
workers O
fit O
lose O
dia O
jobs O
even O
with O
di O
fear O
of O
dia O
safety O
as O
dem O
dey O
work O
. O

Di O
pandemic O
don O
scata O
di O
calendars O
of O
plenti O
faiths O
. O

Dis O
come O
lead O
to O
many O
reports O
by O
international O
media O
ontop O
story O
wey O
get O
just O
one O
source O
. O

But O
later O
one O
sensational O
headline O
for O
US B-LOC
media O
comot O
say O
di O
North O
Korean O
leader O
dey O
in O
critical O
condition O
after O
heart O
surgery O
. O

If O
anytin O
happun O
to O
di O
North O
Korean O
leader O
, O
e O
no O
dey O
clear O
who O
go O
replace O
am O
. O

Di O
Kim B-PER
dynasty O
look O
secure O
. O

But O
make O
dem O
avoid O
sex O
if O
one O
of O
dem O
suspect O
say O
di O
oda O
pesin O
get O
coronavirus O
, O
di O
advice O
tok O
. O

But O
, O
e O
no O
too O
dey O
normal O
. O

Na O
where O
e O
begin O
be O
dat O
. O

She O
go O
scratch O
my O
skin O
wit O
her O
fingernails O
till O
I O
start O
to O
dey O
bleed O
, O
she O
go O
punch O
me O
. O

I O
no O
defend O
mysef O
becos O
I O
bin O
dey O
tink O
say O
to O
harm O
woman O
dey O
wrong O
. O

I O
come O
end O
up O
trapped O
. O

"""" O
Why O
I O
need O
attend O
those O
conferences O
? O
"""" O

So O
evritin O
go O
start O
again O
di O
next B-DATE
day I-DATE
. O

Ira B-PER
think O
say O
we O
dey O
get O
sex O
problems O
becose O
of O
me O
so O
she O
dey O
carryime O
go O
sex O
doctor O
evri O
few O
years O
. O

Sita B-PER
Tyasutami I-PER
and O
her O
mama O
Maria B-PER
Darmaningsih I-PER
bin O
get O
all O
di O
symptoms O
of O
coronovirus O
and O
bin O
dey O
chill O
for O
hospital O
bed O
dey O
wait O
for O
di O
result O
of O
dia O
test O
. O

Na O
on O
27 B-DATE
February I-DATE
when O
one O
of O
Tyasutami B-PER
friends O
tell O
am O
say O
she O
go O
di O
same O
dance O
event O
with O
one O
Japanese O
woman O
wey O
don O
test O
positive O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
, O
na O
im O
she O
know O
say O
water O
don O
pass O
garri O
even O
though O
she O
bin O
no O
know O
the O
Japanese O
woman O
. O

Right O
or O
wrong O
, O
di O
announcement O
make O
dem O
turn O
negative O
celebs O
overnight O
. O

E O
fit O
neva O
clear O
who O
cari O
coronavirus O
enta O
Indonesia B-LOC
but O
di O
first O
wo O
pipo O
wey O
test O
positive O
to O
am O
name O
don O
dey O
on O
record O
. O

Di O
health O
minister O
no O
gree O
follow O
di O
BBC B-ORG
tok O
. O

Allen B-PER
, O
wey O
dem O
born O
for O
Lagos B-LOC
for O
1940 B-DATE
, O
teach O
imsef O
how O
to O
drum O
when O
im O
be O
18 B-DATE
. O

Allen B-PER
migrate O
to O
London B-LOC
for O
1984 B-DATE
, O
and O
later O
move O
go O
Paris B-LOC
. O

Im O
agency O
say O
Khan B-PER
die O
for O
hospital O
for O
di O
western B-LOC
city I-LOC
of I-LOC
Mumbai I-LOC
. O

"""" O
Incredible O
talent O
. O
. O
. O
gracious O
colleague O
. O
. O
. O
very O
good O
contributor O
to O
di O
world O
of O
Cinema O
. O
. O
. O
e O
leave O
us O
too O
soon O
… O
e O
go O
create O
huge O
gap O
, O
"""" O
dat O
na O
wetin O
superstar O
actor O
Amitabh B-PER
Bachchan I-PER
wey O
work O
with O
am O
for O
Piku B-PER
tweet O
. O

You O
go O
dey O
sweat O
. O

E O
write O
say O
; O
"""" O
We O
feel O
a O
bit O
tired O
, O
like O
we O
say O
we O
get O
cold O
, O
and O
some O
body O
ache O
. O

Game O
of O
Thrones' O
actor O
, O
Kristofer B-PER
Hivju I-PER
, O
wey O
play O
di O
role O
of O
Tormund B-PER
, O
also O
don O
test O
positive O
for O
coronavirus O
. O

We O
use O
di O
party O
take O
gist O
on O
top O
di O
Covid O
- O
19 O
mata O
and O
also O
play O
some O
of O
my O
song O
wey O
I O
neva O
release O
. O

I O
no O
find O
your O
Twitter B-ORG
address O
, O
my O
name O
na O
Keta B-PER
Henshaw I-PER
and O
I O
no O
dey O
chop O
my O
words O
when O
I O
tok O
say O
@ O
AbboElisha B-PER
no O
dey O
worthy O
to O
be O
patron O
for O
di O
Actors B-ORG
Guild I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
. O

We O
get O
women O
for O
di O
guild O
and O
we O
no O
want O
make O
person O
slap O
us O
! O
! O
"""" O

Di O
film O
wey O
she O
do O
for O
2016 B-DATE
na O
true O
life O
story O
of O
Phiona B-PER
Mutesi I-PER
, O
wey O
begin O
play O
chess O
for O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
nine I-DATE
even O
though O
say O
e O
no O
go O
school O
and O
e O
carry O
di O
game O
go O
anoda O
level O
as O
im O
begin O
compete O
for O
international O
tournaments O
. O

Dem O
nominate O
Imogen B-PER
Heap I-PER
song O
for O
Harry B-PER
Potter I-PER
and O
di O
Cursed O
Child O
for O
best O
musical O
theatre O
album O
category O
; O
while O
new O
recording O
of O
Hedwig B-PER
Theme I-PER
, O
wey O
appear O
for O
all O
di O
eight O
Potter B-PER
films O
, O
collect O
nomination O
for O
best O
instrumental O
arrangement O
. O

Afta O
e O
die O
, O
di O
Los B-ORG
Angeles I-ORG
Police I-ORG
Department I-ORG
hail O
am O
as O
a O
"""" O
peacemaker O
"""" O
. O

E O
tok O
dis O
one O
for O
di O
latest O
episode O
of O
im O
YouTube O
series O
"""" O
Justin O
Bieber O
Seasons O
"""" O
, O
di O
singer O
tok O
say O
e O
bin O
dey O
addicted O
to O
drugs O
and O
cannabis O
wen O
e O
be O
13 B-DATE
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

Di O
25 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
pop O
star O
don O
tok O
about O
im O
drug O
abuse O
and O
abusing O
im O
relationship O
before O
, O
but O
dis O
latest O
video O
na O
di O
first O
time O
e O
dey O
tok O
about O
am O
for O
camera O
. O

Di O
singer O
tok O
say O
na O
as O
im O
hard O
am O
to O
cope O
with O
im O
fame O
na O
im O
make O
am O
to O
start O
dey O
take O
hard O
drugs O
. O

Shabalala B-PER
die O
for O
hospital O
inside O
Pretoria B-LOC
, O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
, O
di O
band O
manager O
tok O
. O

E O
begin O
work O
for O
di O
family O
farm O
and O
later O
, O
for O
one O
local O
factory O
. O

"""" O
E O
just O
dey O
like O
dat O
. O

She O
say O
as O
long O
as O
she O
dey O
in O
love O
, O
she O
dey O
ready O
to O
say O
yes O
to O
life O
- O
long O
commitment O
. O

Love O
at O
first O
sight O
for O
her O
mean O
more O
than O
di O
physical O
and O
for O
her O
e O
go O
depend O
weda O
she O
feel O
any O
meaningful O
connection O
with O
di O
pesin O
. O

She O
dey O
find O
man O
wey O
sabi O
express O
imsef O
and O
sabi O
tok O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Jay B-PER
believe O
say O
love O
na O
all O
about O
attraction O
and O
na O
di O
basis O
for O
anytin O
else O
wey O
go O
follow O
. O

If O
you O
wan O
win O
her O
heart O
, O
just O
surprise O
her O
wit O
gifts O
like O
flower O
or O
accessories O
. O

Di O
awards O
, O
wey O
dey O
celebrate O
excellence O
for O
film O
and O
television O
, O
dey O
come O
out O
on O
behalf O
of O
di O
Hollywood B-ORG
Foreign I-ORG
Press I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
HFPA B-ORG
) O
. O

Here O
na O
di O
full O
list O
of O
nominees O
: O
Best O
motion O
picture O
- O
drama O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
for O
motion O
picture O
- O
drama O
Best O
actor O
for O
motion O
picture O
- O
drama O
Best O
motion O
picture O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
for O
motion O
picture O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
motion O
picture O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
motion O
picture O
- O
animated O
Best O
motion O
picture O
- O
foreign O
language O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
wey O
dey O
supporting O
role O
for O
any O
motion O
picture O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
wey O
dey O
supporting O
role O
for O
any O
motion O
picture O
Best O
director O
for O
motion O
picture O
Best O
screenplay O
- O
motion O
picture O
Best O
original O
score O
Best O
original O
song O
- O
motion O
picture O
Best O
Television O
series O
- O
drama O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
for O
drama O
series O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
drama O
series O
Best O
television O
series O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O

Eh O
eh O
, O
US B-LOC
also O
dey O
di O
middle O
of O
di O
impeachment O
process O
of O
President O
Trump B-PER
on O
top O
one O
phone O
call O
with O
di O
Ukraine B-LOC
presido O
wey O
dem O
accuse O
am O
say O
im O
mis O
- O
use O
im O
office O
. O

Dis O
go O
be O
test O
for O
di O
local O
organising O
committee O
and O
preparation O
to O
host O
di O
African O
Nations O
Cup O
for O
2021 B-DATE
. O

Ogbonge O
Nigerian O
musician O
Davido B-PER
dey O
set O
to O
wed O
im O
babe O
and O
di O
mother O
of O
im O
pikin O
( O
Ifeanyi B-PER
) O
, O
Chioma B-PER
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
afta O
e O
sama O
her O
proposal O
inside O
London B-LOC
for O
2019 B-DATE
. O

Wetin O
go O
happun O
with O
di O
Cameroon B-LOC
crisis O
and O
di O
recent O
Anglophone O
palava O
, O
wey O
don O
dey O
ground O
since O
2017 B-DATE
and O
lead O
to O
di O
death O
of O
plenti O
pipo O
? O

Plenti O
goments O
across O
di O
world O
for O
dia O
new B-DATE
year I-DATE
messages O
don O
promise O
wetin O
dem O
go O
do O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
to O
boost O
dia O
kontries O
. O

Citizens O
across O
dis O
kontries O
and O
di O
world O
, O
go O
dey O
chook O
eye O
to O
see O
wetin O
go O
play O
at O
di O
end O
of O
di O
day O
with O
all O
these O
visions O
and O
promises O
. O

Now O
, O
di O
council O
say O
di O
Art B-LOC
and I-LOC
Craft I-LOC
Village I-LOC
wey O
worth O
N9 O
. O
8 O
billion O
don O
become O
wia O
robbers O
dey O
hide O
plus O
wia O
dem O
dey O
sell O
bad O
drugs O
. O

Di O
NCAC B-ORG
describe O
di O
Art B-LOC
and I-LOC
Craft I-LOC
Village I-LOC
as O
"""" O
rented O
house O
for O
hooligans O
, O
robbers O
, O
criminals O
and O
depot O
for O
illegal O
arms O
"""" O
and O
add O
say O
di O
area O
don O
become O
"""" O
security O
threat O
not O
only O
to O
Abuja B-LOC
pipo O
but O
also O
to O
foreigners O
wey O
dey O
do O
early B-DATE
morning I-DATE
exercises O
. O
"""" O

Im O
bin O
tok O
say O
e O
go O
build O
di O
city O
on O
top O
2 O
, O
000 O
acre O
of O
land O
wey O
di O
Presido O
of O
Senegal B-LOC
, O
Macky B-PER
Sall I-PER
dash O
am O
. O

Dem O
fail O
to O
realize O
say O
doctor O
recently O
diagnose O
me O
with O
Lyme O
disease O
, O
not O
only O
dat O
but O
I O
get O
serious O
case O
of O
chronic O
mono O
wey O
affect O
my O
, O
skin O
, O
brain O
function O
, O
energy O
, O
and O
overall O
health O
. O
"""" O

E O
tok O
say O
im O
dey O
get O
"""" O
di O
right O
treatment O
"""" O
wey O
go O
help O
treat O
dis O
disease O
wey O
no O
get O
cure O
, O
and O
im O
go O
reveal O
more O
for O
di O
documentary O
series O
about O
im O
life O
wey O
go O
dey O
YouTube O
soon O
. O

Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
wife O
, O
model O
Hailey B-PER
Bieber I-PER
, O
defend O
her O
husband O
against O
criticism O
from O
those O
wey O
dey O
try O
to O
make O
di O
Lyme O
disease O
look O
common O
. O

Lawyer O
to O
Naira B-PER
marley I-PER
, O
Ayodeji B-PER
Awokunlehin I-PER
claim O
say O
all O
di O
accuse O
wey O
dem O
sama O
against O
di O
singer O
na O
lie O
and O
dem O
don O
even O
fix O
di O
car O
of O
di O
pesin O
wey O
carry O
di O
mata O
come O
court O
. O

Church O
dem O
also O
play O
role O
for O
di O
creation O
of O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
. O

Na O
also O
day O
to O
continue O
all O
di O
chopping O
because O
many O
pipo O
dey O
prepare O
so O
much O
food O
for O
Christmas B-DATE
wey O
dem O
go O
end O
up O
eating O
throughout O
di O
next B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

Hmm O
, O
my O
mouth O
don O
dey O
water O
already O
. O

Di O
next O
Thor B-PER
film O
, O
Love O
and O
Thunder O
, O
go O
come O
out O
for O
2021 B-DATE
according O
to O
di O
schedule O
. O

Di O
former O
housemate O
announce O
her O
engagement O
ontop O
Instagram O
on O
Thursday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
, O
December B-DATE
26 I-DATE
, O
2019 B-DATE
. O

E O
never O
too O
tey O
wey O
Gedoni B-PER
, O
write O
special O
message O
ontop O
Instagram O
, O
wia O
e O
praise O
and O
express O
im O
love O
for O
Khafi B-PER
. O

One O
actress O
wey O
play O
minor O
role O
for O
"""" O
Captain O
America B-LOC
: O
Di O
First O
Avenger O
"""" O
film O
dey O
face O
court O
accuse O
say O
she O
stab O
her O
mama O
to O
death O
. O

Di O
rapper O
don O
dey O
trend O
when O
she O
tok O
say O
no O
be O
joke O
even O
follow O
repost O
Nigerian O
clothes O
wey O
pipo O
Photoshop O
on O
top O
her O
and O
her O
pikin O
, O
Kulture B-PER
bodi O
. O

For O
dia O
2019 B-DATE
show O
, O
di O
event O
trend O
afta O
di O
mama O
of O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
comot O
to O
collect O
her O
pikin O
award O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
nominees O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Soundcity B-ORG
MVP O
Awards O
. O

She O
say O
she O
bin O
dey O
on O
top O
of O
di O
VIP O
podium O
when O
e O
collapse O
because O
she O
bin O
wan O
see O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
and O
Santan B-PER
. O

Di O
show O
dey O
always O
pull O
plenti O
crowd O
. O

Sierra B-LOC
Leone I-LOC
Tourism O
Minister O
Memunatu B-PER
Pratt I-PER
describe O
Elba B-PER
visit O
as O
"""" O
homecoming O
"""" O
. O

Some O
Ghanaians O
and O
Nigerians O
dey O
yab O
demself O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

Tok O
- O
tok O
pesin O
for O
di O
state O
police O
command O
, O
Ikeokwu B-PER
Godson I-PER
Orland I-PER
na O
im O
confam O
di O
arrest O
give O
BBC B-ORG
as O
rumours O
bin O
dey O
fly O
say O
some O
gunmen O
kidnap O
di O
singer O
. O

For O
di O
statement O
wen O
oga O
Orlando B-PER
carry O
come O
out O
, O
e O
say O
dem O
arrest O
Duncan B-PER
Mighty I-PER
afta O
one O
upcoming O
rapper O
, O
M2 B-PER
write O
complain O
against O
am O
say O
e O
collect O
money O
and O
no O
gree O
do O
work O
wey O
dem O
pay O
am O
to O
do O
. O

Di O
song O
wey O
dey O
all O
about O
promise O
of O
love O
na O
4 B-DATE
- I-DATE
minute I-DATE
video O
and O
e O
don O
get O
more O
than O
1 O
, O
122 O
, O
410 O
views O
for O
YouTube O
. O

on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
, O
23 B-DATE
, I-DATE
November I-DATE
. O

Through O
di O
project O
she O
wan O
draw O
attention O
to O
how O
katakata O
fit O
affect O
di O
mental O
health O
of O
di O
victims O
of O
Boko B-ORG
Haram I-ORG
wahala O
wey O
dey O
happen O
for O
north B-LOC
- I-LOC
east I-LOC
Nigeria I-LOC
. O

High O
Society O
na O
popular O
musical O
feem O
wey O
dem O
do O
for O
1957 B-DATE
and O
na O
Grace B-PER
Kelly I-PER
last O
work O
before O
she O
become O
princess O
of O
Monaco B-LOC
. O

Di O
video O
Hart B-PER
post O
for O
Instagram O
show O
am O
for O
hospital O
, O
and O
also O
as O
im O
dey O
recover O
for O
house O
. O

"""" O
As O
we O
dey O
move O
forward O
we O
go O
dey O
submit O
film O
wey O
dem O
no O
speak O
too O
much O
English O
inside O
. O

Lionheart O
movie O
na O
Nigeria B-LOC
first O
submission O
for O
di O
Oscars O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
winners O
of O
di O
2019 B-DATE
Africa B-LOC
Movie O
Academy O
Awards O
( O
AMAA O
) O
wey O
shele O
on O
27 B-DATE
October I-DATE
for O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

Im O
come O
tweet O
say O
dem O
dey O
try O
finish O
di O
mix O
on O
top O
some O
songs O
. O

For O
im O
interview O
with O
Zane B-PER
Lowe I-PER
of O
Beats O
1 O
, O
Kanye B-PER
tok O
say O
im O
tell O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
work O
on O
di O
album O
say O
make O
dem O
no O
sleep O
with O
pipo O
way O
dem O
no O
dey O
married O
to O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
13th B-DATE
year I-DATE
wey O
dem O
dey O
run O
dis O
awards O
show O
wey O
dem O
bin O
call O
Hip O
Hop O
World O
Awards O
wey O
Hip B-ORG
TV I-ORG
dey O
organize O
. O

Also O
, O
actress O
Nancy B-PER
Isime I-PER
and O
rapper O
Reminisce B-PER
na O
who O
dey O
follow O
host O
di O
event O
. O

Di O
song O
become O
instant O
hit O
and O
di O
unofficial O
anthem O
for O
di O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
as O
dem O
dey O
go O
World O
Cup O
. O

He O
don O
collaborate O
with O
Olamide B-PER
before O
ontop O
previous O
track O
wey O
him O
call O
"""" O
Ko O
Si O
Werey O
. O
"""" O

Na O
May B-DATE
9 I-DATE
, I-DATE
1994 I-DATE
dem O
born O
and O
na O
one O
day O
afta O
im O
25 B-DATE
years I-DATE
birthday O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
corruption O
police O
bin O
arrest O
. O

Cobain's B-PER
custom O
- O
made O
Fender O
Mustang O
guitar O
- O
wey O
im O
use O
for O
Nirvana's B-ORG
In O
Utero O
tour O
- O
also O
dey O
up O
for O
sale O
, O
and O
dem O
buy O
am O
for O
$ O
340 O
, O
000 O
( O
£ O
265 O
, O
000 O
) O
. O

However O
, O
many O
of O
di O
pipo O
wey O
watch O
di O
event O
from O
dia O
house O
tok O
say O
di O
two O
of O
dem O
no O
gel O
togeda O
, O
wetin O
oyibo O
pipo O
dey O
call O
'chemistry' O
, O
as O
dem O
no O
feel O
say O
di O
two O
of O
dem O
connect O
well O
. O

More O
than O
100 O
authors O
, O
poets O
, O
dancers O
, O
musicians O
and O
oda O
creative O
arts O
pipo O
don O
gada O
for O
Ake O
Arts O
and O
Book O
Festival O
for O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
South B-LOC
West I-LOC
Nigeria I-LOC
. O

To O
be O
Free' O
wey O
be O
feem O
by O
Nigerian O
- O
American O
actress O
Adepero B-PER
Oduye I-PER
go O
screen O
for O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
festival O
. O

Also O
, O
di O
obonge O
documentary O
'Toni B-PER
Morrison I-PER
: O
The O
Pieces O
I O
Am' O
, O
wey O
show O
pipo O
di O
life O
and O
work O
of O
di O
ogbonge O
author O
, O
go O
also O
show O
for O
di O
festival O
. O

Lady B-PER
Gaga I-PER
fall O
yakata O
inside O
di O
crowd O
during O
her O
latest O
show O
wey O
she O
dey O
do O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

Dis O
wan O
happun O
afta O
di O
star O
bin O
call O
one O
of O
her O
fans O
wey O
im O
name O
na O
Jack B-PER
make O
e O
come O
stage O
, O
na O
as O
she O
jump O
for O
im O
bodi O
to O
begin O
dey O
dance O
, O
na O
im O
e O
leg O
shift O
and O
dem O
come O
land O
yakata O
for O
ground O
. O

Big O
Brother O
Naija O
don O
become O
important O
part O
of O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
society O
as O
pipo O
don O
do O
pass O
normal O
to O
carri O
di O
mata O
for O
head O
- O
even O
wen O
all O
dem O
be O
na O
just O
fans O
. O

One O
example O
na O
di O
rumour O
wey O
comot O
for O
2018 B-DATE
afta O
Teddy B-PER
A I-PER
comot O
from O
di O
house O
say O
fans O
wan O
donate O
N45 O
million O
to O
am O
as O
'no O
too O
tink O
am O
money' O
. O

Tacha B-PER
na O
one O
of O
di O
controversial O
contestants O
wey O
dey O
di O
Big O
Brother O
Naija O
house O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
and O
as O
dem O
disqualify O
am O
. O

Di O
'Jane B-PER
di O
Virgin' O
actress O
post O
video O
ontop O
her O
social O
media O
wen O
she O
dey O
do O
her O
make O
up O
. O

Rodriguez B-PER
delete O
di O
video O
from O
her O
Instastories O
come O
also O
apologise O
say O
she O
no O
mean O
to O
offend O
any O
pesin O
. O

