Di O
matches O
no O
go O
get O
any O
fans O
for O
inside O
di O
stadium O
and O
infact O
na O
only O
essential O
staff O
dem O
go O
dey O
di O
area O
wey O
dem O
go O
fight O
di O
matches O
. O

So O
far O
, O
di O
UFC B-ORG
don O
schedule O
three O
match O
for O
May B-DATE
9 I-DATE
, O
13 B-DATE
and O
16 B-DATE
for O
dia O
UFC B-ORG
249 O
fighting O
. O

"""" O
Fortunately O
, O
most O
of O
di O
boys O
dey O
well O
and O
we O
no O
get O
any O
real O
issues O
at O
all O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
di O
McNally B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
club O
official O
app O
. O

"""" O
Di O
nutritionist O
put O
di O
boys O
for O
one O
Instagram O
page O
wia O
dem O
go O
take O
cooking O
lessons O
, O
so O
a O
lot O
of O
dem O
don O
start O
to O
dey O
develop O
new O
skill O
- O
and O
one O
or O
two O
of O
dem O
don O
get O
injury O
. O
"""" O

If O
dem O
win O
, O
Dortmund B-ORG
go O
close O
reduce O
to O
one O
point O
di O
gap O
wey O
Bayern B-ORG
dey O
give O
dem O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
great O
- O
nothing O
better O
pass O
make O
you O
prove O
pipo O
wrong O
. O

so O
many O
pipo O
don O
tok O
say O
, O
'501kg O
no O
go O
ever O
go O
up' O
. O
. O
. O

Di O
Ligue O
1 O
and O
Ligue O
2 O
seasons O
no O
go O
resume O
afta O
France B-LOC
don O
ban O
all O
sporting O
events O
, O
plus O
di O
one O
wey O
dem O
wan O
do O
behind O
closed O
doors O
, O
until O
September B-DATE
. O

German O
Bundesliga O
action O
go O
continue O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
as O
league O
leaders O
Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
face O
Union B-ORG
Berlin I-ORG
later O
. O

Uefa B-ORG
don O
call O
emergency O
meeting O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
wia O
dem O
go O
discuss O
di O
possibility O
of O
postponing O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
by O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

Discussions O
go O
cover O
all O
domestic O
and O
European O
competitions O
, O
including O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
. O

"""" O
I O
proposed O
to O
postpone O
for O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
and O
[ O
IOC B-ORG
] O
president O
Thomas B-PER
Bach I-PER
don O
give O
100 O
% O
support O
, O
"""" O
Im O
tok O
. O

Di O
fight O
bin O
suppose O
hold O
for O
Tottenham B-LOC
Hotspur I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
, I-DATE
20 I-DATE
June I-DATE
. O

Im O
bin O
suppose O
fight O
Joshua B-PER
for O
October B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
but O
n O
fit O
do O
am O
because O
of O
sholder O
injury O
. O

Dem O
sack O
am O
afta O
e O
finish O
second O
for O
di O
league O
in O
2010 B-DATE
- I-DATE
11 I-DATE
. O

By O
unanimous O
decision O
by O
di O
judges O
declare O
say O
na O
di O
Nigerian O
- O
born O
Israel B-PER
, O
na O
im O
fight O
pass O
on O
di O
night B-DATE
. O

Di O
fight O
wey O
many O
sabi O
pipo O
say O
no O
two O
sweet O
to O
watch O
, O
bin O
happun O
for O
di O
T B-LOC
- I-LOC
Mobile I-LOC
Arena I-LOC
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
, O
American O
early O
mor O
mor O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

Israel B-PER
Adesanya I-PER
wey O
im O
nickname O
na O
Stylebender B-PER
, O
dey O
represent O
New B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC
wey O
be O
di O
kontri O
im O
parents O
migrate O
to O
. O

Fury B-PER
beat O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
to O
collect O
di O
WBC O
title O
last B-DATE
month I-DATE
, O
e O
mean O
say O
na O
British O
heavyweights O
hold O
all O
di O
belts O
dem O
for O
di O
division O
. O

And O
say O
di O
plan O
na O
to O
sleep O
for O
im O
manager O
side O
and O
come O
back O
house O
di O
next O
dey O
. O

Im O
coach O
Daniel B-PER
Ogunmodede I-PER
, O
say O
na O
Kazeem B-PER
good O
behaviour O
make O
am O
promote O
Kazeem B-PER
to O
assistant O
captain O
, O
even O
though O
na O
four B-DATE
months I-DATE
ago I-DATE
im O
join O
dem O
. O

Authorities O
don O
say O
now O
dem O
go O
look O
di O
mata O
and O
investigate O
. O

"""" O
I O
respect O
say O
im O
na O
big O
man O
for O
sports O
but O
di O
law O
no O
dey O
respect O
pesin O
. O

No O
mata O
who O
you O
be O
, O
di O
law O
still O
apply O
to O
you O
, O
"""" O
Oga O
Acevedo B-PER
tell O
local O
tori O
pipo O
. O

Hannah B-PER
Baxter I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
31 B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
die O
later O
for O
hospital O
from O
serious O
burns O
all O
ova O
her O
bodi O
. O

Tickets O
for O
dia O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
fights O
dey O
go O
for O
thousands O
of O
dollars O
, O
already O
di O
fighters O
dey O
badmouth O
each O
oda O
ahead O
of O
di O
fight O
. O

Na O
di O
biggest O
heavyweight O
fight O
for O
20 B-DATE
, O
30 B-DATE
, O
or O
even O
50 B-DATE
years I-DATE
- O
dat O
na O
if O
you O
listen O
to O
wetin O
Fury B-PER
dey O
tok O
. O

Some O
UK B-LOC
betting O
company O
dey O
put O
Wilder B-PER
as O
slight O
favourite O
for O
di O
sports O
betting O
facility O
for O
MGM B-LOC
Grand I-LOC
, O
wia O
some O
big O
spenders O
fit O
force O
di O
prize O
to O
change O
as O
di O
fight O
dey O
near O
. O

Bunce B-PER
respond O
: O
"""" O
I O
feel O
say O
we O
go O
see O
Wilder B-PER
box O
small O
and O
Fury B-PER
go O
dey O
more O
aggressive O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
latest O
twist O
for O
dis O
rivalry O
. O

"""" O
I O
feel O
say O
Wilder B-PER
go O
come O
out O
of O
di O
gates O
like O
horse O
wey O
dey O
run O
to O
try O
to O
knock O
me O
out O
. O
"""" O

Cameroon B-LOC
go O
host O
CHAN O
2020 B-DATE
from O
4 B-DATE
- I-DATE
25 I-DATE
April I-DATE
and O
na O
one O
of O
de O
kontris O
for O
announce O
say O
two O
pipo O
don O
test O
positive O
for O
coronavirus O
recently O
. O

"""" O
We O
no O
di O
too O
worry O
about O
de O
situation O
but O
we O
bi O
on O
alert O
for O
future O
matches O
like O
CAF B-ORG
Champions O
League O
, O
CAF B-ORG
Confederations O
Cup O
and O
African O
Nations O
Championship O
, O
CHAN O
weh O
e O
suppose O
take O
place O
for O
Cameroon B-LOC
. O

My O
coach O
throw O
in O
di O
towel O
but O
I O
dey O
ready O
to O
go O
out O
on O
my O
shield O
. O

E O
get O
up O
and O
battle O
onto O
round O
seven O
. O

But O
di O
king O
don O
return O
to O
di O
top O
of O
di O
throne O
. O
"""" O

Na O
for O
di O
National B-ORG
Taekwondo I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
wey O
dey O
close O
to O
Etihad B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
and O
wia O
im O
don O
dey O
stay O
dem O
dey O
use O
since O
e O
land O
from O
China B-LOC
11 B-DATE
days I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

Di O
current O
medical O
advice O
na O
say O
travellers O
wey O
dey O
come O
into O
di O
UK B-LOC
from O
specific O
kontris O
, O
including O
China B-LOC
, O
dem O
go O
quarantine O
dem O
for O
14 B-DATE
days I-DATE
. O

Nigeria B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
don O
appoint O
former O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
captain O
Joseph B-PER
Yobo I-PER
as O
assistant O
coach O
of O
di O
team O
. O

Yobo B-PER
wey O
play O
100 O
matches O
for O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
also O
play O
for O
Everton B-ORG
, O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
, O
Marseille B-ORG
, O
Standard B-ORG
Liege I-ORG
and O
Norwich B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

But O
di O
number O
of O
players O
wey O
dia O
contracts O
go O
expire O
before O
City B-ORG
go O
return O
back O
to O
Champions O
League O
na O
mata O
wey O
dey O
worry O
. O

I O
want O
to O
come O
here' O
, O
"""" O
Ighalo B-PER
add O
. O

Make O
dis O
deal O
happun O
. O

Dis O
na O
one O
of O
di O
longest O
running O
transfers O
of O
di O
window O
and O
yes O
but O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
don O
get O
dia O
man O
- O
Bruno B-PER
Fernandes I-PER
don O
sign O
five B-DATE
- I-DATE
and I-DATE
- I-DATE
a I-DATE
- I-DATE
half I-DATE
year I-DATE
deal O
from O
Sporting B-ORG
Lisbon I-ORG
. O

Wetin O
surprise O
me O
be O
say O
nobody O
really O
look O
im O
side O
until O
Jorge B-PER
Jesus I-PER
, O
di O
current O
Flamengo B-ORG
boss O
decided O
to O
sign O
am O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Portuguese O
football O
writer O
Jose B-PER
Delgado I-PER
. O

Fernandes B-PER
na O
di O
shinning O
light O
for O
Sporting B-ORG
, O
even O
though O
im O
bin O
struggle O
and O
e O
help O
Portugal B-LOC
to O
win O
Nation O
League O
for O
June B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
- O
di O
big O
question O
now O
na O
whether O
im O
fit O
deliver O
for O
United B-ORG
? O

Na O
good O
player O
wey O
get O
potential O
to O
grow O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Italian O
football O
writer O
Danielle B-PER
Vieri I-PER
tok O
. O

"""" O
Na O
correct O
pesin O
in O
be O
and O
im O
dey O
very O
professional O
, O
im O
go O
make O
use O
of O
im O
time O
here O
well O
. O
"""" O

God O
willing O
, O
I O
come O
out O
with O
no O
injury O
. O

I O
still O
work O
to O
do O
to O
return O
to O
how O
I O
be O
before O
. O
"""" O

Mohamed B-PER
Salah I-PER
( O
Egypt B-LOC
& O
Liverpool B-ORG
) O
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
( O
Algeria B-LOC
& O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
) O
Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
( O
Senegal B-LOC
& O
Liverpool B-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Ajara B-PER
Nchout I-PER
( O
Cameroon B-LOC
& O
Valerenga B-ORG
) O
Asisat B-PER
Oshoala I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Barcelona B-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Thembi B-PER
Kgatlana I-PER
( O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
& O
Beijing B-ORG
Phoenix I-ORG
FC I-ORG
) O
Anice B-PER
Badri I-PER
( O
Tunisia B-LOC
& O
Esperance B-ORG
) O
Tarek B-PER
Hamed I-PER
( O
Egypt B-LOC
& O
Zamalek B-ORG
) O
Youcef B-PER
Belaïli I-PER
( O
Algeria B-LOC
& O
Esperance B-ORG
/ O
Ahli B-ORG
Jeddah I-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Achraf B-PER
Hakimi I-PER
( O
Morocco B-LOC
& O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Samuel B-PER
Chukwueze I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Villarreal B-ORG
) O
Victor B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Lille B-ORG
) O
Aliou B-PER
Cisse I-PER
( O
Senegal B-LOC
- O
Senegal B-LOC
) O
Djamel B-PER

Di O
Cameroonian O
peak O
for O
Tottenham B-ORG
for O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
and O
na O
one O
of O
di O
best O
left O
backs O
for O
Premier O
League O
under O
Harry B-PER
Redknapp I-PER
. O

Dem O
name O
am O
as O
di O
club O
player O
- O
of O
di O
- O
season O
for O
2014 B-DATE
before O
e O
join O
Pep B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
for O
di O
end O
of O
dat O
season O
. O

Im O
be O
di O
reigning O
Caf B-ORG
footballer O
of O
di O
year O
afta O
im O
retain O
di O
crown O
for O
2019 B-DATE
. O

She O
add O
say O
"""" O
I O
just O
make O
far O
too O
many O
errors O
to O
be O
professional O
athlete O
today B-DATE
. O
"""" O

E O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
MOTD I-ORG
: O
"""" O
We O
dey O
happy O
for O
di O
win O
today B-DATE
and O
to O
go O
to O
di O
next O
round O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
very O
important O
as O
one O
team O
and O
as O
one O
group O
of O
players O
. O

"""" O
Clubs O
fit O
dey O
do O
heart O
screening O
or O
oda O
health O
measures O
for O
dia O
fans O
wey O
dey O
committed O
because O
na O
dem O
dey O
at O
risk O
to O
experience O
stress O
during O
di O
game O
, O
"""" O
she O
add O
. O

As O
di O
day O
waka O
dey O
go O
, O
unconfam O
reports O
of O
shooting O
, O
wey O
involve O
Togo B-LOC
national O
team O
, O
start O
to O
fly O
evriwia O
. O

Wen O
e O
siddon O
to O
tok O
, O
e O
give O
shocking O
details O
of O
di O
attack O
wey O
kill O
two O
members O
of O
di O
Togo B-LOC
delegation O
and O
result O
in O
life O
changing O
injuries O
to O
some O
odas O
. O

Di O
small O
convoy O
move O
from O
di O
border O
, O
to O
di O
road O
through O
di O
forest O
. O

"""" O
All O
of O
us O
bin O
dey O
enjoy O
, O
afta O
we O
don O
cross O
di O
border O
. O

Di O
convoy O
by O
- O
force O
stop O
, O
and O
serious O
firefight O
brake O
out O
between O
di O
attackers O
and O
di O
security O
forces O
. O

Can O
you O
imagine O
? O

Di O
news O
of O
di O
attack O
make O
global O
headlines O
, O
and O
wia O
24 B-DATE
hours I-DATE
earlier I-DATE
I O
bin O
dey O
able O
to O
walk O
in O
simply O
wit O
tournament O
accreditation O
, O
di O
next B-DATE
day I-DATE
heavy O
paramilitary O
security O
surround O
di O
hotel O
complex O
. O

Anoda O
question O
lie O
for O
di O
presence O
Angolan O
security O
wey O
travel O
with O
di O
team O
. O

"""" O
I O
done O
do O
lot O
of O
tins O
, O
and O
I O
happy O
say O
I O
do O
dem O
. O

I O
find O
no O
reason O
at O
all O
to O
play O
football O
for O
my O
club O
because O
psychologically O
I O
bin O
dey O
shocked O
. O
"""" O

Oshoala B-PER
year O
include O
goal O
for O
Women O
World O
Cup O
to O
help O
Nigeria B-LOC
reach O
di O
last O
16 O
inside O
France B-LOC
and O
10 O
goals O
for O
13 O
appearances O
afta O
she O
join O
Spanish O
side O
Barcelona B-ORG
for O
February B-DATE
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
really O
excited O
- O
proud O
of O
myself O
, O
four O
times O
na O
something O
to O
always O
remember O
, O
"""" O
she O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
Africa I-ORG
. O

Im O
tok O
join O
: O
"""" O
Fans O
, O
pipo O
, O
no O
get O
sense O
again O
like O
dem O
get O
before O
. O
"""" O

Arteta B-PER
na O
di O
20th O
manager O
wey O
di O
club O
go O
appoint O
inside O
dia O
133 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
history O
. O

Im O
also O
dey O
speak O
French O
, O
Italian O
and O
Portuguese O
small O
too O
. O

Kamaru B-PER
kpo O
- O
kpo O
Covington B-PER
patapata O
for O
di O
last O
round O
, O
and O
put O
am O
for O
ground O
two O
times O
with O
two O
big O
punch O
, O
e O
come O
begin O
dey O
punch O
am O
, O
punch O
am O
before O
referee O
Marc B-PER
Goddard I-PER
come O
dey O
force O
to O
shout O
say O
di O
fight O
don O
do O
oh O
! O

Im O
record O
na O
15 O
- O
1 O
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
real O
. O

Plenti O
fighters O
dey O
fear O
to O
fall O
. O
Me O
I O
know O
dey O
fear O
to O
fall O
becos O
I O
know O
say O
I O
be O
winner O
and O
I O
go O
continue O
to O
win O
. O
"""" O

Joshua B-PER
na O
im O
get O
di O
oda O
three O
world O
heavyweight O
belts O
- O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBO O
and O
WBA O
titles O
. O

I O
not O
fit O
ansa O
and O
by O
cool O
way O
I O
call O
am O
back O
. O

Seven B-DATE
months I-DATE
later O
Ali B-PER
defeat O
Spinks B-PER
for O
15 O
rounds O
afta O
all O
di O
judges O
give O
am O
di O
victory O
. O

Ortiz B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
40 B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
manage O
to O
stand O
up O
but O
im O
no O
fit O
beat O
di O
10 O
count O
. O

Wen O
Nigeria B-LOC
use O
di O
national O
stadium O
take O
host O
di O
Fifa B-ORG
U O
- O
17 O
World O
Cup O
for O
2009 B-DATE
, O
di O
grass O
ontop O
di O
field O
still O
green O
well O
- O
well O
and O
facility O
dey O
work O
. O

But O
today B-DATE
, O
na O
di O
opposite O
. O

"""" O
If O
e O
happun O
and O
warning O
don O
sound O
comot O
for O
di O
stadium O
, O
and O
e O
come O
happun O
again O
, O
we O
go O
need O
to O
decide O
as O
one O
team O
and O
wit O
di O
staff O
, O
"""" O
Abraham B-PER
bin O
tok O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Super B-ORG
Falcons I-ORG
don O
troway O
dia O
chance O
to O
go O
Tokyo B-LOC
2020 B-DATE
Olympic O
Games O
afta O
Cote B-LOC
d' I-LOC
Ivoire I-LOC
waya O
dem O
1 O
- O
1 O
ontop O
home O
soil O
for O
second O
leg O
qualifier O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

Na O
only O
one O
automatic O
slot O
dey O
for O
Africa B-LOC
and O
Cote B-LOC
d' I-LOC
Ivoire I-LOC
go O
feel O
say O
strong O
chance O
dey O
now O
for O
dem O
to O
grab O
am O
. O

Boxer O
Patrick B-PER
Day I-PER
don O
die O
at O
age B-DATE
27 I-DATE
- O
four B-DATE
days I-DATE
afta O
im O
suffer O
brain O
injury O
from O
fight O
against O
Charles B-PER
Conwell I-PER
. O

"""" O
Patrick B-PER
Day I-PER
no O
need O
to O
box O
, O
"""" O
di O
statement O
from O
DiBella B-ORG
Entertainment I-ORG
continue O
. O

Protests O
don O
dey O
happun O
for O
Barcelona B-ORG
since O
last B-DATE
week I-DATE
afta O
nine O
Catalan O
separatist O
leaders O
get O
jail O
sentence O
earlier B-DATE
dis I-DATE
month I-DATE
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
dey O
for O
Group O
E O
wit O
Argentina B-LOC
, O
Spain B-LOC
, O
Tajikistan B-LOC
and O
Brazil B-LOC
. O

Fraser B-PER
- I-PER
Pryce I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
32 B-DATE
- I-DATE
years I-DATE
don O
become O
di O
oldest O
woman O
to O
win O
Olympic O
or O
world O
100m O
title O
, O
two B-DATE
years I-DATE
afta O
she O
born O
her O
pikin O
, O
Zyon B-PER
. O

But O
Siasia B-PER
say O
di O
police O
no O
get O
good O
news O
for O
am O
ontop O
her O
rescue O
. O

"""" O
So O
di O
only O
tin O
wey O
I O
fit O
do O
na O
to O
just O
beg O
dis O
guys O
to O
free O
my O
mama O
. O

As O
coach O
im O
lead O
di O
kontri O
under O
- O
20 O
and O
under O
- O
23 O
sides O
to O
success O
in O
AFCON O
for O
2005 B-DATE
and O
2015 B-DATE
respectively O
. O

Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
coach O
Gernot B-PER
Rohr I-PER
put O
players O
like O
Alex B-PER
Iwobi I-PER
, O
William B-PER
Troost I-PER
- I-PER
Ekong I-PER
, O
Samuel B-PER
Chukwueze I-PER
and O
Wilfred B-PER
Ndidi I-PER
for O
di O
list O
of O
23 O
players O
wey O
go O
travel O
go O
Singapore B-LOC
to O
play O
Brazil B-LOC
. O

Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
say O
boxing O
'undercard' O
match O
wey O
women O
go O
fight O
fit O
happun O
on O
di O
day O
of O
im O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
rematch O
wit O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jr I-PER
. O
Joshua B-PER
, O
29 B-DATE
, O
dey O
target O
to O
get O
back O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBA O
and O
WBO O
world O
heavyweight O
titles O
inside O
"""" O
Clash O
on O
di O
Dunes O
"""" O
wey O
go O
happun O
for O
Diriyah B-LOC
on O
7 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

"""" O
We O
dey O
hear O
say O
grassroot O
fighters O
dey O
come O
up O
for O
dia O
. O

Some O
pipo O
don O
criticize O
di O
event O
wen O
di O
tori O
comot O
say O
na O
for O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
e O
go O
happun O
. O

Dis O
na O
as O
plenti O
kontris O
dey O
look O
into O
mass O
testing O
as O
way O
to O
avoid O
second O
wave O
. O

From O
small O
businesses O
to O
even O
multi O
- O
nationals O
sef O
, O
many O
businesses O
dem O
don O
suffer O
for O
di O
pandemic O
hand O
. O

Na O
why O
plenti O
goments O
for O
world O
get O
stimuli O
packages O
for O
workers O
and O
companies O
. O

To O
go O
back O
work O
Pressure O
don O
dey O
goment O
neck O
to O
reduce O
restrictions O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
work O
. O

Many O
kontris O
no O
wan O
reduce O
lockdown O
restriction O
for O
restaurants O
, O
pubs O
and O
theatres O
, O
For O
Thailand B-LOC
, O
na O
cubicle O
pipo O
don O
dey O
eat O
inside O
as O
dem O
restaurants O
don O
dey O
get O
protective O
barriers O
and O
oda O
kontris O
don O
dey O
tink O
di O
same O
way O
. O

But O
kontris O
dey O
wey O
dey O
try O
normalise O
di O
attendance O
for O
religious O
events O
. O

Dis O
also O
no O
go O
be O
di O
first O
time O
rumour O
about O
im O
health O
go O
bring O
up O
plenty O
tok O
tok O
- O
only O
for O
dem O
to O
dismiss O
am O
later O
. O

Dis O
come O
lead O
to O
many O
reports O
by O
international O
media O
ontop O
story O
wey O
get O
just O
one O
source O
. O

However O
, O
statement O
from O
South B-LOC
Korea I-LOC
goment O
, O
and O
sources O
for O
Chinese O
intelligence O
- O
for O
interview O
with O
Reuters B-ORG
news O
agency O
- O
say O
di O
tori O
no O
dey O
true O
. O

Di O
truth O
be O
say O
when O
e O
come O
to O
information O
about O
di O
North O
Korean O
leadership O
, O
many O
times O
we O
dey O
struggle O
to O
see O
road O
inside O
darkness O
. O

Dis O
be O
after O
17 O
new O
people O
recover O
after O
de O
last O
declaration O
by O
Ghana B-ORG
Health I-ORG
Service I-ORG
. O

Dutch O
goment O
don O
issue O
new O
guidance O
to O
single O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
find O
closeness O
during O
di O
pandemic O
, O
with O
advise O
for O
dem O
to O
find O
"""" O
sex O
buddy O
"""" O
. O

If O
singles O
choose O
to O
engage O
in O
sexual O
contact O
, O
dem O
must O
take O
precautions O
to O
minimise O
di O
risk O
of O
coronavirus O
exposure O
, O
di O
authority O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Make O
good O
arrangements O
with O
dis O
pesin O
about O
how O
many O
oda O
pipo O
two O
of O
una O
dey O
see O
you O
both O
. O

My O
fear O
na O
to O
avoid O
to O
dey O
alone O
for O
di O
same O
place O
wit O
her O
. O

Inside O
one O
day O
, O
I O
lose O
evritin O
. O

I O
don O
dey O
overwork O
and O
I O
bin O
want O
rest O
, O
but O
she O
say O
she O
wan O
do O
kerewa O
. O

She O
go O
dey O
ontop O
of O
me O
. O

I O
don O
count O
wen O
we O
go O
leave O
Ukraine B-LOC
. O

And O
I O
go O
go O
back O
to O
her O
evri O
time O
. O

Na O
once O
a O
day O
dis O
kind O
tin O
dey O
happun O
or O
even O
evri O
oda O
day O
. O

She O
go O
dey O
tell O
me O
di O
kind O
man O
wey O
she O
need O
, O
wetin O
he O
suppose O
do O
. O

To O
dey O
avoid O
all O
dis O
, O
I O
use O
to O
work O
10 B-DATE
, O
12 B-DATE
, O
14 B-DATE
hours I-DATE
every O
day O
, O
on O
weekends B-DATE
and O
even O
for O
holiday O
time O
. O

E O
dey O
easy O
: O
some O
pipo O
dey O
drink O
- O
oda O
pipo O
dey O
choose O
to O
work O
. O

You O
no O
even O
dey O
tink O
say O
you O
get O
time O
to O
escape O
, O
e O
just O
dey O
hopeless O
. O

In O
di O
beginning O
, O
I O
no O
just O
like O
am O
but O
later O
, O
like O
three B-DATE
to I-DATE
four I-DATE
years I-DATE
of O
do O
relationship O
, O
I O
bin O
dey O
get O
heart O
attack O
anytime O
she O
tok O
sex O
. O

She O
say O
di O
media O
too O
far O
and O
even O
when O
she O
bin O
dey O
for O
hospital O
, O
she O
watch O
for O
television O
as O
dem O
pack O
for O
her O
house O
even O
as O
one O
press O
freedom O
group O
, O
Alliance B-ORG
of I-ORG
Independent I-ORG
Journalists I-ORG
say O
make O
di O
media O
avoid O
"""" O
sensationalism O
"""" O
and O
respect O
privacy O
of O
covid O
- O
19 O
cases O
. O

He O
warn O
say O
assurance O
no O
dey O
if O
di O
virus O
no O
go O
come O
again O
as O
kontris O
reduce O
lockdown O
small O
. O

Di O
dancer O
dey O
for O
di O
musician O
hit O
music O
video O
WO O
! O
! O

Na O
Kodak B-PER
tori O
full O
plenty O
pipo O
mouth O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
as O
many O
of O
her O
fans O
dey O
sad O
to O
hear O
about O
di O
tori O
of O
her O
death O
. O

Allen B-PER
na O
di O
drummer O
, O
musical O
director O
and O
leader O
of O
Fela B-PER
Kuti I-PER
famous O
band O
Africa B-ORG
'70 I-ORG
for O
1960 B-DATE
- I-DATE
70s I-DATE
. O

E O
say O
im O
learn O
im O
technique O
from O
di O
music O
of O
American O
jazz O
drummers O
Art B-PER
Blakey I-PER
and O
Max B-PER
Roach I-PER
. O

Bollywood B-ORG
actor O
Irrfan B-PER
Khan I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
popular O
around O
di O
world O
for O
di O
role O
wey O
im O
play O
for O
Slumdog O
Millionaire O
and O
Jurassic O
World O
don O
die O
at O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
53 I-DATE
. O

Di O
couple O
go O
spend O
three B-DATE
hours I-DATE
per O
day O
, O
excluding O
Saturday B-DATE
and O
Sunday B-DATE
to O
visit O
10 O
important O
public O
places O
for O
Lagos B-LOC
to O
educate O
di O
public O
on O
di O
consequence O
of O
non O
- O
compliance O
with O
goment O
restriction O
order O
. O

Rita B-PER
experience O
some O
chills O
wey O
come O
and O
later O
go O
. O

Di O
advice O
and O
tips O
include O
make O
pipo O
wear O
protective O
cloth O
, O
greet O
each O
oda O
with O
dia O
elbow O
plus O
songs O
wey O
get O
to O
do O
with O
washing O
of O
hands O
. O

We O
dey O
pretend O
say O
we O
dey O
for O
inside O
club O
and O
for O
di O
chat O
we O
, O
go O
dey O
do O
like O
na O
real O
party O
, O
dey O
chyke O
babe O
, O
dey O
bounce O
pipo O
comot O
and O
like O
say O
pesin O
dey O
order O
bottles O
. O
"""" O

She O
con O
add O
put O
say O
person O
wey O
be O
paron O
go O
be O
person O
wey O
get O
moral O
and O
no O
be O
person O
wey O
dey O
slap O
women O
. O

He O
say O
wetin O
pipo O
dey O
tok O
about O
"""" O
no O
count O
"""" O
. O

As O
di O
palava O
dey O
hot O
for O
social O
media O
, O
BBC B-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
try O
tok O
to O
di O
senator O
wey O
dey O
di O
eyes O
of O
di O
storm O
but O
im O
no O
reply O
message O
wey O
our O
correspondent O
send O
give O
am O
. O

Rogers B-PER
win O
three O
Grammy O
awards O
and O
dey O
popular O
for O
songs O
like O
Tyhe O
Gambler O
, O
Lucile O
, O
Cowartd O
of O
the O
County O
among O
plenti O
odas O
wey O
make O
im O
career O
last O
ova O
sixty B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

Keny B-PER
Rogers I-PER
bin O
grow O
up O
for O
inside O
poverty O
for O
Texas B-LOC
before O
im O
start O
music O
wey O
make O
am O
launch O
im O
solo O
career O
for O
1976 B-DATE
. O

Ramsey B-PER
Nouah I-PER
feem O
, O
Living O
In O
Bondage O
: O
Breaking O
Free O
, O
pack O
seven O
awards O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
for O
di O
seventh O
edition O
of O
di O
Africa B-LOC
Magic O
Viewers O
Choice O
Awards O
. O

Di O
feem O
wey O
be O
di O
follow O
- O
up O
to O
di O
1992 B-DATE
classic O
of O
di O
same O
name O
na O
di O
first O
time O
Ramsey B-PER
Nouah I-PER
wey O
follow O
win O
di O
Best O
Director O
award O
for O
im O
work O
, O
go O
direct O
a O
movie O
. O

Dem O
dey O
advise O
make O
pesin O
wear O
shoe O
wey O
go O
dey O
comfortable O
. O

Before O
in O
start O
, O
Elton B-PER
John I-PER
bin O
tell O
di O
sold O
out O
crowd O
say O
im O
get O
walking O
pneumonia O
dat O
Sunday B-DATE
even O
as O
im O
dey O
perform O
for O
im O
Farewell O
Yellow O
Brick O
Road O
tour O
. O

Last B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Biebs B-PER
take O
break O
from O
music O
to O
repair O
"""" O
some O
deep O
rooted O
mata O
dem O
"""" O
but O
announce O
before O
Christmas B-DATE
say O
e O
go O
come O
back O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
with O
album O
and O
US B-LOC
tour O
. O

One O
radio O
performance O
wey O
dem O
do O
for O
1970 B-DATE
lead O
to O
one O
recording O
contract O
, O
and O
for O
1973 B-DATE
dem O
release O
Africa B-LOC
first O
gold O
- O
selling O
album O
, O
Amabutho O
. O

E O
continue O
to O
dey O
teach O
traditional O
choral O
music O
, O
while O
four O
of O
im O
sons O
( O
and O
one O
grandson O
) O
continue O
im O
legacy O
within O
Ladysmith B-ORG
Black I-ORG
Mambazo I-ORG
. O

Theresa B-PER
Theresa I-PER
na O
23 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
eye O
doctor O
wey O
want O
man O
wey O
fit O
give O
her O
attention O
well O
- O
well O
. O

Im O
longest O
relationship O
last O
for O
four B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
na O
with O
im O
high O
school O
sweetheart O
. O

For O
di O
35 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
public O
proposal O
na O
big O
no O
- O
no O
. O

Alade B-PER
come O
para O
and O
accuse O
Sarkodie B-PER
say O
im O
dey O
unprofessional O
and O
since O
den O
di O
two O
of O
dem O
no O
too O
dey O
yarn O
with O
each O
oda O
until O
now O
. O

Di O
awards O
, O
wey O
dey O
celebrate O
excellence O
for O
film O
and O
television O
, O
dey O
come O
out O
on O
behalf O
of O
di O
Hollywood B-ORG
Foreign I-ORG
Press I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
HFPA B-ORG
) O
. O

Most O
of O
di O
times O
, O
na O
dem O
dey O
set O
di O
agenda O
for O
Oscars O
wey O
go O
happun O
next B-DATE
month I-DATE
( O
dem O
no O
dey O
too O
dey O
wrong O
) O
. O

actress O
for O
television O
series O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
television O
series O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
television O
limited O
series O
or O
motion O
picture O
wey O
dem O
do O
for O
television O
Best O
actress O
for O
limited O
series O
or O
TV O
movie O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
limited O
series O
or O
motion O
picture O
wey O
dem O
make O
for O
television O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
for O
supporting O
role O
in O
a O
series O
, O
limited O
series O
or O
a O
motion O
picture O
wey O
dem O
make O
for O
television O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
supporting O
role O
for O
series O
, O
limited O
series O
or O
motion O
picture O
wey O
dem O
make O
for O
television O

FireBoy B-PER
DML I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
JoeBoy B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Marioo B-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Rema B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Simmy B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Wendy B-PER
Shay I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Blow O
My O
Mind O
- O
Davido B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Daz O
How O
Star O
Do O
- O
Skibii B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Gugulethu O
- O
Prince B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
[ O
SA B-LOC
] O
- O
Winner O
Jama B-PER
- O
DJ B-PER
Mic I-PER
Smith I-PER
[ O
GH B-LOC
] O
Killin O
Dem O
- O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Inama B-PER
- O
Diamond B-PER
PlatNumz I-PER
[ O
TZ B-LOC
] O
Innos B-PER
B I-PER
[ O
CG B-LOC
] O
Nandy B-PER
[ O
TZ B-LOC
] O
JoeBoy B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
- O
Winner O
Otile B-PER
Brown I-PER
[ O
KE B-LOC
] O
Kizz B-PER
Daniel I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Teni B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Mayorkun B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Rayvanny B-PER
[ O

But O
Donald B-PER
Trump I-PER
don O
already O
start O
im O
campaign O
for O
di O
presidential O
elections O
wey O
go O
hold O
for O
November B-DATE
, I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
. O

Di O
House O
don O
already O
impeach O
am O
and O
President O
Trump B-PER
don O
make O
history O
as O
di O
third O
presido O
of O
di O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
wey O
dem O
go O
impeach O
. O

For O
2017 B-DATE
, O
when O
dem O
hold O
dia O
last O
presidential O
election O
, O
na O
14 O
, O
000 O
clan O
delegates O
pick O
dia O
lawmakers O
wey O
later O
pick O
dia O
president O
. O

Im O
don O
dey O
power O
since O
2005 B-DATE
. O

Every B-DATE
four I-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
one O
sports O
event O
dey O
always O
come O
around O
wey O
dey O
bring O
di O
world O
togeda O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Olympics O
go O
start O
for O
July B-DATE
and O
end O
for O
August B-DATE
. O

E O
don O
tey O
wey O
Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
drop O
im O
own O
music O
and O
as O
pipo O
dey O
enjoy O
Yummy O
wey O
just O
land O
, O
e O
don O
also O
announce O
say O
im O
dey O
release O
im O
first O
album O
since O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Now O
to O
some O
tori O
about O
di O
Economy O
. O
. O
. O
Ending O
of O
2019 B-DATE
, O
French O
Presido O
Emmanuel B-PER
Macron I-PER
announce O
say O
for O
2020 B-DATE
, O
dem O
go O
release O
di O
ECO O
currency O
to O
free O
francophone O
African O
kontris O
from O
di O
cefas O
wey O
dem O
bin O
dey O
spend O
. O

Wetin O
go O
happun O
with O
di O
Cameroon B-LOC
crisis O
and O
di O
recent O
Anglophone O
palava O
, O
wey O
don O
dey O
ground O
since O
2017 B-DATE
and O
lead O
to O
di O
death O
of O
plenti O
pipo O
? O

Akon B-PER
bin O
first O
announce O
im O
plans O
for O
di O
"""" O
crypto O
city O
"""" O
for O
2018 B-DATE
for O
di O
Cannes B-LOC
Lion O
Festival O
for O
France B-LOC
, O
wen O
im O
launch O
di O
crypto O
- O
currency O
wey O
di O
city O
go O
dey O
use O
, O
AKoin O
. O

Dem O
fail O
to O
realize O
say O
doctor O
recently O
diagnose O
me O
with O
Lyme O
disease O
, O
not O
only O
dat O
but O
I O
get O
serious O
case O
of O
chronic O
mono O
wey O
affect O
my O
, O
skin O
, O
brain O
function O
, O
energy O
, O
and O
overall O
health O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Please O
do O
your O
research O
, O
"""" O
she O
advise O
dem O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Lawyer O
to O
Naira B-PER
marley I-PER
, O
Ayodeji B-PER
Awokunlehin I-PER
claim O
say O
all O
di O
accuse O
wey O
dem O
sama O
against O
di O
singer O
na O
lie O
and O
dem O
don O
even O
fix O
di O
car O
of O
di O
pesin O
wey O
carry O
di O
mata O
come O
court O
. O

Di O
servants O
go O
also O
den O
go O
home O
on O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
to O
give O
Christmas B-DATE
boxes O
to O
dia O
families O
. O

For O
some O
European O
kontries O
- O
like O
Hungary B-LOC
, O
Germany B-LOC
, O
Poland B-LOC
, O
and O
di O
Netherlands B-LOC
- O
Dem O
dey O
celebrate O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
as O
a O
second O
Christmas B-DATE
Day I-DATE
. O

Na O
also O
public O
holiday O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
nd O
some O
oda O
kontries O
around O
di O
world O
. O
. O
Wen O
26 B-DATE
December I-DATE
na O
Saturday B-DATE
, O
di O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
holiday O
go O
move O
to O
di O
next B-DATE
Monday I-DATE
. O

If O
26 B-DATE
December I-DATE
fall O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
, O
den O
di O
holiday O
na O
di O
following O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

Yes O
. O
"""" O

Although O
di O
picture O
wey O
she O
put O
no O
show O
di O
face O
of O
her O
fiancé O
, O
she O
use O
di O
# O
MrsEkpataLoading O
to O
take O
announce O
her O
engagement O
. O

Bumble O
na O
app O
wey O
different O
from O
oda O
apps O
because O
e O
dey O
allow O
di O
woman O
make O
di O
first O
move O
. O

Fitzgerald B-PER
dey O
for O
jail O
on O
a O
$ O
500 O
, O
000 O
bond O
, O
according O
to O
records O
from O
di O
Johnson B-ORG
County I-ORG
Sheriff's I-ORG
Office I-ORG
. O

Di O
event O
producer O
, O
Adeniji B-PER
Daniel I-PER
tok O
say O
"""" O
di O
show O
go O
get O
international O
show O
hosts O
, O
collabo O
you O
no O
go O
expect O
and O
pop O
culture O
moments O
wey O
go O
make O
pipo O
tok O
for O
a O
long O
time O
"""" O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
nominees O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Soundcity B-ORG
MVP O
Awards O
. O

Fetch O
Your O
Life O
- O
Prince B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
x O
Msaki B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Jama B-PER
- O
DJ B-PER
Micsmith I-PER
x O
Patoranking B-PER
, O
Shaker B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Jealous O
- O
Fireboy B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Killin O
Dem O
- O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
x O
Zlatan B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Malwhede B-PER
- O
King B-PER
Monada I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Soapy O
- O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Tetema O
- O
Rayvanny B-PER
x O
Diamond B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Zanku O
( O
Legwork O
) O
- O
Zlatan B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
ARTISTE O
OF O
DI O
YEAR O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Davido B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Diamond B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Shatta B-PER
Wale I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Sho B-PER
Madjozi I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Tiwa B-PER
Savage I-PER
( O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
VIP O
stage O
fall O
yakata O
with O
pipo O
ontop O
as O
di O
show O
bin O
dey O
go O
on O
. O

She O
say O
she O
bin O
dey O
on O
top O
of O
di O
VIP O
podium O
when O
e O
collapse O
because O
she O
bin O
wan O
see O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
and O
Santan B-PER
. O

For O
her O
Insta O
story O
for O
her O
official O
account O
Cardi B-PER
B I-PER
drop O
video O
wey O
she O
put O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
Ghana B-LOC
flag O
come O
write O
"""" O
take O
me O
back O
to O
Africa B-LOC
"""" O
. O

Dem O
dey O
use O
di O
# O
GhanavrsNaija O
take O
tok O
about O
Cardi B-PER
B I-PER
post O
and O
many O
oda O
issues O
. O

"""" O
Dis O
arrest O
follow O
one O
petition O
wey O
one O
upcoming O
rap O
artist O
M2 B-PER
write O
. O

Davido B-PER
"""" O
A O
Good O
Time O
"""" O
album O
dey O
come O
seven B-DATE
years I-DATE
afta O
im O
first O
one O
- O
Omo O
Baba O
Olowo O
. O

Dem O
release O
di O
song O
, O
on O
Friday B-DATE
wey O
dem O
title O
"""" O
Own O
It O
"""" O
na O
part O
of O
Stormzy B-PER
album O
wey O
im O
wan O
release O
for O
December B-DATE
. O

Sheeran B-PER
also O
don O
win O
four O
Grammy O
Awards O
and O
e O
dey O
very O
popular O
with O
two O
of O
im O
ogbonge O
song O
wey O
be O
"""" O
Shape O
of O
You O
"""" O
and O
"""" O
Thinking O
Out O
Loud O
. O
"""" O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
na O
di O
6th O
edition O
of O
di O
event O
, O
e O
happun O
for O
di O
Convention B-LOC
Centre I-LOC
for I-LOC
Eko I-LOC
Hotel I-LOC
& I-LOC
Suites I-LOC
, O
Victoria B-LOC
Island I-LOC
, O
Lagos B-LOC
. O

Grammy O
Album O
of O
di O
year O
nominee O
, O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
win O
'Best O
Male O
artiste O
inside O
West B-LOC
Africa' I-LOC
with O
im O
song O
'Ye' O
and O
also O
Artist O
of O
di O
year O
award O
. O

She O
ginger O
pipo O
say O
make O
dia O
different O
journey O
for O
life O
dey O
kind O
to O
dem O
. O

But O
one B-DATE
week I-DATE
afta O
di O
ceremony O
dem O
cancel O
di O
award O
. O

A O
Place O
for O
di O
World O
, O
na O
Uruguay B-LOC
submission O
for O
1993 B-DATE
Oscars O
, O
wey O
dem O
nominate O
for O
best O
international O
picture O
. O

Di O
popular O
American O
comedian O
for O
im O
nearly O
two B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
video O
say O
"""" O
No O
matter O
how O
much O
you O
think O
say O
you O
dey O
in O
control O
, O
you O
no O
dey O
in O
control O
. O

De O
organisers O
Livespot360 B-ORG
say O
Cardi B-PER
B I-PER
go O
visit O
Nigeria B-LOC
first O
on O
December B-DATE
7 I-DATE
den O
come O
Ghana B-LOC
December B-DATE
8 I-DATE
for O
en O
performance O
which O
go O
happen O
for O
Accra B-LOC
Sports I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
. O

Linc B-PER
Edochie I-PER
wey O
be O
di O
pikin O
of O
di O
ogbonge O
actor O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
as O
di O
72 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
actor O
dey O
grow O
old O
, O
writers O
for O
di O
Nollywood B-ORG
movie O
industry O
no O
dey O
give O
am O
roles O
wey O
go O
stress O
am O
sake O
of O
im O
health O
, O
so O
na O
Igwe O
roles O
im O
dey O
play O
pass O
. O

Ogbonge O
American O
director O
Ava B-PER
DuVernay I-PER
wey O
comment O
on O
di O
mata O
, O
feel O
saydem O
no O
sppose O
disqualify O
di O
movie O
as O
English O
na O
Nigeria B-LOC
official O
language O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
some O
ogbonge O
tins O
happun O
as O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
break O
record O
on O
top O
say O
im O
gbab O
ten O
nominations O
dis B-DATE
evening I-DATE
for O
Eko B-LOC
hotel I-LOC
Lagos I-LOC
wia O
di O
award O
happun O
. O

1 O
. O
Even O
though O
dem O
born O
am O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
move O
to O
Peckham B-LOC
for O
England B-LOC
wen O
he O
dey O
11 B-DATE
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

Di O
artist O
get O
ogbonge O
success O
after O
im O
formNirvana O
for O
1987 B-DATE
, O
but O
im O
struggle O
with O
fame O
, O
depression O
and O
drug O
addiction O
. O

Correct O
gist O
dey O
always O
follow O
di O
event O
and O
di O
2019 B-DATE
edition O
no O
dey O
different O
at O
all O
, O
as O
pipo O
don O
go O
social O
media O
to O
tok O
some O
of O
di O
tins O
wey O
dem O
feel O
no O
work O
for O
dem O
as O
dem O
dey O
watch O
di O
award O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
edition O
happun O
for O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
with O
Reminisce B-PER
and O
Nancy B-PER
Isime I-PER
as O
di O
hosts O
of O
di O
event O
. O

Although O
e O
no O
be O
new O
tin O
for O
di O
Headies O
to O
use O
pipo O
wey O
no O
dey O
di O
industry O
to O
present O
awards O
. O

Lola B-PER
Shoneyin I-PER
wey O
be O
di O
Festival O
Director O
tok O
say O
di O
event O
wey O
dem O
tag O
'Black O
Bodies O
. O

Pipo O
like O
Bernardine B-PER
Evaristo I-PER
wey O
win O
di O
Booker O
Prize O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
and O
Oyinkan B-PER
Braithwaite I-PER
, O
wey O
get O
one O
of O
di O
best O
selling O
books O
of O
di O
year O
. O

Feminism O
and O
misogny O
na O
some O
of O
di O
hot O
topics O
wey O
dey O
cause O
plenti O
tok O
tok O
for O
social O
media O
and O
award O
winning O
Nigerian O
actor O
, O
Tope B-PER
Tedela I-PER
go O
perform O
'Whumanizer' O
, O
one O
man O
play O
wey O
go O
address O
all O
di O
issues O
. O

Also O
, O
di O
obonge O
documentary O
'Toni B-PER
Morrison I-PER
: O
The O
Pieces O
I O
Am' O
, O
wey O
show O
pipo O
di O
life O
and O
work O
of O
di O
ogbonge O
author O
, O
go O
also O
show O
for O
di O
festival O
. O

"""" O
Nor O
worry O
, O
everytin O
dey O
OK O
, O
no O
be O
your O
fault O
, O
"""" O
she O
tok O
, O
she O
also O
add O
say O
: O
"""" O
You O
fit O
promise O
me O
something O
? O

One O
example O
na O
di O
rumour O
wey O
comot O
for O
2018 B-DATE
afta O
Teddy B-PER
A I-PER
comot O
from O
di O
house O
say O
fans O
wan O
donate O
N45 O
million O
to O
am O
as O
'no O
too O
tink O
am O
money' O
. O

From O
Tboss B-PER
for O
2017 B-DATE
to O
Nina B-PER
for O
2018 B-DATE
and O
Tacha B-PER
for O
2019 B-DATE
, O
tori O
be O
say O
Bobrisky B-PER
dey O
carri O
big O
money O
support O
housemates O
during O
and O
even O
after O
di O
competition O
. O

Pipo O
ontop O
social O
media O
no O
dey O
gree O
ontop O
Gina B-PER
Rodriguez I-PER
mata O
. O

Dis O
time O
na O
because O
she O
use O
di O
'N' O
- O
word O
. O

Some O
even O
tok O
say O
dem O
don O
dey O
wait O
for O
am O
to O
tok O
sumtin O
wey O
go O
make O
dem O
find O
fault O
for O
her O
side O
. O

