Bundesliga O
don O
set O
record O
as O
di O
first O
major O
league O
to O
restart O
during O
di O
coronavirus O
pandemic O
and O
for O
millions O
of O
football O
fans O
, O
di O
main O
kweshion O
na O
how O
to O
watch O
di O
matches O
, O
live O
. O

SATURDAY B-DATE
16TH I-DATE
MAY I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
B B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Schalke B-ORG
Augsburg I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Wolfsburg B-ORG
Düsseldorf I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Paderborn B-ORG
RB I-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Freiburg B-ORG
Hoffenheim I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Hertha B-ORG
Berlin I-ORG
Frankfurt I-ORG
17 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
B B-ORG
Mgladbach I-ORG

Conditions O
Di O
french O
league O
bin O
cancel O
dia O
current O
season O
for O
April B-DATE
, O
say O
whichever O
position O
club O
dey O
for O
table O
, O
na O
final O
. O

Toulouse B-ORG
dey O
bottom O
of O
di O
table O
, O
17 O
points O
from O
safety O
, O
and O
10 O
points O
behind O
Amiens B-ORG
. O

Dis O
na O
one O
of O
di O
many O
tins O
wey O
go O
change O
for O
football O
reality O
sake O
of O
Coronavirus O
. O

Liverpool B-ORG
wey O
be O
di O
defending O
champions O
lose O
3 O
- O
2 O
to O
Atletico B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
for O
Anfield B-LOC
and O
4 O
- O
2 O
on O
aggregate O
for O
dia O
round O
of O
16 O
second O
leg O
match O
. O

BOA B-ORG
chairman O
Hugh B-PER
Robertson I-PER
don O
already O
say O
Great B-LOC
Britain I-LOC
dey O
unlikely O
to O
send O
team O
to O
Tokyo B-LOC
for O
dis O
summer B-DATE
. O

"""" O
But O
the O
advice O
I O
give O
am O
na O
to O
continue O
to O
work O
and O
to O
attract O
di O
attention O
of O
di O
biggest O
clubs O
and O
di O
most O
ambitious O
clubs O
. O
"""" O

Everton B-ORG
don O
score O
in O
all O
10 O
of O
dia O
league O
games O
under O
the O
Italian O
- O
di O
current O
longest O
scoring O
run O
for O
di O
division O
. O

For O
di O
UFC B-ORG
248 O
event O
, O
di O
two O
fighters O
wey O
dey O
undefeated O
before O
dis O
match O
bin O
dey O
hope O
to O
go O
back O
house O
with O
di O
middleweight O
belt O
. O

British O
world O
champion O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
go O
fight O
Kubrat B-PER
Pulev I-PER
for O
Tottenham B-LOC
Hotspur I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
20 I-DATE
June I-DATE
. O

Pulev B-PER
wey O
be O
38 B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
come O
from O
Bulgaria B-LOC
and O
na O
him O
IBF O
, O
wey O
be O
boxing O
join O
- O
body O
say O
Joshua B-PER
wey O
get O
di O
WBA O
, O
IBF O
and O
WBO O
titles O
must O
fight O
. O

Pulev B-PER
, O
na O
former O
European O
heavyweight O
champion O
. O

Although O
police O
never O
accept O
responsibility O
, O
dia O
oga O
patapata O
IGP O
Mohammed B-PER
Adamu I-PER
don O
order O
investigation O
into O
am O
. O

"""" O
Wen O
you O
see O
di O
white O
shirt O
you O
go O
know O
exactly O
which O
club O
e O
dey O
stand O
for O
, O
dem O
dey O
very O
big O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Sterling B-PER
tok O
. O

Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
don O
blame O
im O
big O
costume O
wey O
im O
wear O
enta O
ring O
for O
why O
Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
defeat O
am O
for O
di O
WBC O
heavyweight O
title O
. O

Fury B-PER
from O
Britain B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

"""" O
Dis O
na O
horrific O
scene O
, O
"""" O
Det O
Insp O
Mark B-PER
Thompson I-PER
tel O
tori O
pipo O
: O
"""" O
We O
still O
dey O
investigate O
di O
mata O
, O
but O
wen O
police O
reach O
di O
crime O
scene O
di O
car O
dey O
burn O
. O

She O
bin O
dey O
critical O
condition O
wen O
dem O
cari O
her O
go O
Royal B-ORG
Brisbane I-ORG
and I-ORG
Women's I-ORG
Hospital I-ORG
, O
police O
tok O
. O

If O
Fury B-PER
win O
am O
e O
mean O
say O
all O
four O
heavyweight O
belts O
go O
dey O
shared O
between O
two O
British O
fighters O
- O
him O
and O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
, O
go O
hold O
di O
IBF O
, O
WBA O
and O
WBO O
titles O
. O

Wilder B-PER
dey O
start O
as O
favourite O
according O
to O
betting O
pipo O
before O
di O
fighters O
go O
waka O
enta O
di O
ring O
around O
05 B-DATE
: I-DATE
00 I-DATE
GMT I-DATE
on O
Sunday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
. O

Costello B-PER
add O
say O
: O
I O
feel O
say O
Wilder B-PER
don O
learn O
from O
im O
first O
fight O
and O
e O
go O
dey O
better O
dis O
time O
to O
close O
di O
space O
dem O
. O

Just O
now O
CAF B-ORG
medical O
teams O
di O
watch O
, O
di O
report O
for O
executive O
committee O
and O
if O
de O
situation O
wowo O
, O
CAF B-ORG
for O
decide O
make O
de O
play O
matches O
wit O
no O
fans O
, O
postpone O
or O
cancel O
. O

One O
player O
chop O
five B-DATE
years I-DATE
suspension O
for O
France B-LOC
sake O
of O
say O
im O
bite O
im O
opponent O
penis O
for O
fight O
wey O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
. O

While O
di O
injured O
Terville B-ORG
player O
chop O
six B-DATE
months I-DATE
suspension O
. O

Di O
king O
don O
return O
to O
di O
top O
of O
di O
throne' O
Dis O
na O
wetin O
Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
tok O
afta O
im O
beat O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
hands O
down O
to O
become O
WBC O
world O
heavyweight O
champion O
for O
dia O
rematch O
wey O
happun O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
former O
trainer O
Ben B-PER
Davison I-PER
, O
tweet O
say O
na O
good O
decision O
Wilder B-PER
corner O
take O
to O
trow O
in O
di O
tower O
. O

Guardiola B-PER
feel O
say O
dem O
disappoint O
am O
by O
dis O
decision O
? O

We O
alreadi O
know O
say O
veteran O
midfielder O
David B-PER
Silva I-PER
go O
comot O
for O
end O
of O
dis O
season O
. O

Both O
Ighalo B-PER
, O
im O
agent O
and O
di O
clubs O
spent O
di O
night B-DATE
dey O
negotiate O
and O
sign O
paper O
work O
so O
dat O
everi O
- O
everi O
go O
set O
before O
di O
deadline O
of O
07 B-DATE
: I-DATE
00 I-DATE
Shanghai B-LOC
time O
. O

Ighalo B-PER
say O
e O
don O
tey O
wey O
im O
na O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
fan O
, O
na O
since O
wen O
im O
be O
small O
boy O
and O
e O
dey O
happy O
say O
im O
dream O
to O
play O
for O
di O
Old B-LOC
Trafford I-LOC
club O
don O
come O
through O
. O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
striker O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
go O
miss O
di O
club O
training O
camp O
for O
Spain B-LOC
sake O
of O
fear O
of O
coronavirus O
outbreak O
wey O
fit O
make O
immigration O
for O
UK B-LOC
no O
allow O
enta O
back O
inside O
di O
kontri O
. O

Wetin O
im O
don O
do O
for O
Portugal B-LOC
don O
show O
say O
if O
fit O
do O
di O
same O
for O
bigger O
stage O
. O

For O
di O
foto O
wey O
dem O
use O
illustration O
do O
, O
her O
daughter O
wear O
Los B-ORG
Angeles I-ORG
Lakers I-ORG
jersey O
, O
with O
her O
papa O
jersey O
number O
, O
24 O
. O

Kobe B-PER
and O
Vanessa B-PER
get O
four O
daughters O
togeda O
including O
Gianna B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
13 B-DATE
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
wey O
also O
die O
for O
di O
Helicopter O
crash O
. O

After O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
im O
move O
go O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
and O
im O
don O
score O
10 O
times O
for O
19 O
games O
. O

As O
2019 B-DATE
don O
end O
, O
Former O
Chelsea B-ORG
and O
Ghana B-LOC
star O
Michael B-PER
Essien I-PER
don O
choose O
im O
best O
11 O
African O
players O
from O
2010 B-DATE
to O
2019 B-DATE
. O

Kolo's B-PER
acquisition O
signal O
shift O
in O
power O
for O
City B-ORG
because O
im O
come O
from O
direct O
rival O
, O
Arsenal B-ORG
. O

Essien B-PER
prowess O
begin O
to O
die O
down O
just O
for O
di O
turn O
of O
di O
decade O
with O
injuries O
taking O
dia O
toll O
but O
e O
bin O
still O
dey O
important O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
as O
dem O
qualify O
for O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
- O
e O
insists O
say O
im O
deserve O
place O
for O
e O
team O
of O
di O
decade O
! O

I O
literally O
no O
fit O
do O
dat O
again O
. O

Afta O
di O
game O
Kelechi B-PER
Iheanacho I-PER
carrri O
di O
award O
for O
Man O
of O
the O
Match O
. O

Ogbonge O
football O
fans O
dey O
get O
one O
kain O
deep O
level O
of O
physical O
stress O
wen O
dem O
dey O
watch O
dia O
team O
dey O
play O
and O
dem O
fit O
give O
diasef O
heart O
attack O
, O
na O
so O
research O
tok O
. O

Former O
research O
don O
show O
say O
heart O
attack O
among O
fans O
wen O
dia O
team O
dey O
play O
important O
match O
dey O
increases O
weda O
dem O
dey O
support O
di O
club O
or O
dia O
kontri O
. O

For O
dia O
study O
, O
di O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Oxford I-ORG
sabi O
pipo O
don O
track O
cortisol O
levels O
for O
40 O
fans' O
saliva O
before O
, O
during O
and O
afta O
three O
World O
Cup O
match O
. O

Di O
one O
wey O
dey O
stressful O
pass O
na O
di O
semi O
- O
final O
. O

I O
bin O
dey O
di O
province O
of O
Cabinda B-LOC
, O
dey O
prepare O
to O
cover O
Group O
B O
for O
di O
BBC B-ORG
World I-ORG
Service I-ORG
, O
and O
bin O
also O
dey O
in O
charge O
of O
handing O
ova O
di O
BBC B-ORG
African O
Footballer O
of O
the O
Year O
trophy O
to O
di O
newly O
- O
crowned O
winner O
, O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
captain O
Didier B-PER
Drogba I-PER
. O

As O
di O
day O
waka O
dey O
go O
, O
unconfam O
reports O
of O
shooting O
, O
wey O
involve O
Togo B-LOC
national O
team O
, O
start O
to O
fly O
evriwia O
. O

Before O
di O
tournament O
, O
Togo B-LOC
decide O
to O
camp O
for O
Pointe B-LOC
Noir I-LOC
for O
Republic B-LOC
of I-LOC
Congo I-LOC
, O
just O
over O
100km O
from O
wia O
dem O
go O
play O
dia O
group O
games O
for O
Angola B-LOC
city O
of O
Cabinda B-LOC
. O

Players O
bin O
just O
dey O
laugh O
and O
joking O
amongst O
demselves O
for O
di O
bus O
. O

Senaya B-PER
remember O
Togo B-LOC
media O
officer O
, O
Stanislas B-PER
Ocloo I-PER
, O
bin O
stand O
to O
video O
dia O
arrival O
for O
Angola B-LOC
at O
di O
moment O
of O
di O
attack O
. O

Adebayor B-PER
tok O
about O
how O
serious O
di O
longest O
half B-DATE
hour I-DATE
of O
e O
life O
dey O
. O

Honestly O
na O
one O
of O
di O
worst O
experiences O
I O
don O
eva O
get O
for O
my O
life O
. O

But O
eventually O
dem O
take O
all O
of O
dem O
to O
hospital O
for O
di O
outskirts O
of O
Cabinda B-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
wia O
those O
wey O
noting O
do O
help O
carry O
dia O
dead O
and O
colleagues O
wey O
wunjure O
inside O
. O

Shortly O
afta O
di O
attack O
claim O
of O
responsibility O
comot O
from O
di O
Front B-ORG
for I-ORG
di I-ORG
Liberation I-ORG
of I-ORG
di I-ORG
Enclave I-ORG
of I-ORG
Cabinda I-ORG
, O
wey O
be O
separatist O
group O
wey O
never O
don O
accept O
di O
decision O
of O
di O
former O
colonial O
power O
, O
Portugal B-LOC
, O
to O
integrate O
Cabinda B-LOC
into O
Angola B-LOC
in O
di O
late B-DATE
1950s I-DATE
. O

Since O
den O
e O
don O
face O
eight O
major O
operations O
and O
don O
get O
to O
rebuild O
e O
life O
, O
physically O
and O
emotionally O
. O

"""" O
I O
done O
do O
lot O
of O
tins O
, O
and O
I O
happy O
say O
I O
do O
dem O
. O

On O
Tuesday B-DATE
night I-DATE
Caf B-ORG
give O
am O
special O
award O
, O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
from O
Cabinda B-LOC
, O
to O
recognise O
e O
achievement O
for O
im O
recovery O
, O
and O
wetin O
e O
dey O
do O
to O
help O
odas O
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
legend O
Samuel B-PER
Eto'o I-PER
na O
di O
host O
for O
Hurghada B-LOC
, O
and O
e O
be O
one O
of O
several O
former O
players O
wey O
don O
provide O
steady O
support O
. O

But O
no O
one O
fit O
deny O
di O
human O
cost O
of O
dat O
short O
bus O
trip O
for O
Cabinda B-LOC
, O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

Additional O
research O
and O
reporting O
by O
Blame B-PER
Ekoue I-PER
for O
Lome B-LOC
and O
Victoire B-PER
Eyoum I-PER
in O
London B-LOC
. O

"""" O
I've O
chat O
wit O
Fifa B-ORG
because O
dis O
na O
very O
important O
something O
, O
"""" O
di O
former O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
international O
tok O
. O

Everton B-ORG
director O
of O
football O
, O
Marcel B-PER
Brands I-PER
tok O
say O
Ancelotti B-PER
na O
"""" O
one O
of O
di O
finest O
managers O
for O
di O
world O
football O
"""" O
and O
na O
"""" O
proven O
winner O
"""" O
. O

Covington B-PER
get O
four O
career O
win O
by O
submission O
and O
three O
knockout O
victory O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
Usman B-PER
and O
Covington B-PER
go O
make O
$ O
500 O
, O
000 O
each O
for O
dis O
dia O
fight O
. O

Oda O
Boxing O
Day O
matches O
see O
Chelsea B-ORG
surprisingly O
lose O
2 O
- O
0 O
to O
Southampton B-ORG
for O
Stamford B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
while O
Tottenham B-ORG
come O
from O
behind O
to O
beat O
Brighton B-ORG
2 O
- O
1 O
. O

Tottenham B-ORG
Hotspur I-ORG
2 O
- O
1 O
Brighton B-ORG
Bournemouth I-ORG
1 O
- O
1 O
Arsenal B-ORG
Chelsea I-ORG
0 O
- O
2 O
Southampton B-ORG
Aston I-ORG
Villa I-ORG
1 O
- O
0 O
Norwich B-ORG
Everton I-ORG
1 O
- O
0 O
Burnley B-ORG
Sheffield I-ORG
United I-ORG
1 O
- O
1 O
Watford B-ORG
. O

Wilder B-PER
, O
wey O
im O
WBC O
belt O
go O
dey O
on O
di O
line O
when O
they O
jam O
for O
MGM B-LOC
Grand I-LOC
, O
tweet O
say O
: O
"""" O
kweshion O
no O
go O
dey O
again O
"""" O
and O
"""" O
I O
go O
finish O
wetin O
I O
start O
"""" O
. O

Oda O
big O
big O
matches O
go O
see O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
play O
Paris B-ORG
St I-ORG
- I-ORG
Germain I-ORG
and O
Napoli B-ORG
go O
take O
on O
Barcelona B-ORG
. O

Premier O
League O
legends O
like O
Alan B-PER
Shearer I-PER
, O
Robbie B-PER
Fowler I-PER
and O
Phil B-PER
Neville I-PER
no O
happy O
at O
all O
wit O
di O
way O
tins O
dey O
go O
. O

Former O
Arsenal B-ORG
oga O
Arsene B-PER
Wenger I-PER
go O
hold O
tok O
tok O
wit O
Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
next B-DATE
week I-DATE
on O
top O
vacant O
manager O
job O
. O

"""" O
We O
decide O
togeda O
say O
we O
go O
tok O
next B-DATE
week I-DATE
becos O
I O
dey O
inside O
Doha B-LOC
until O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
true O
story O
, O
"""" O
Wenger B-PER
tok O
. O

I O
not O
fit O
ansa O
and O
by O
cool O
way O
I O
call O
am O
back O
. O

"""" O
Him O
bein O
dey O
inside O
him O
car O
dey O
go O
for O
di O
game O
against O
Olympiakos B-ORG
. O

Afta O
Moorer B-PER
victory O
to O
Holyfield B-PER
e O
come O
choose O
to O
fight O
45 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
ex O
- O
Heavyweight O
champion O
George B-PER
Foreman I-PER
instead O
but O
im O
lose O
dat O
fight O
. O

Dis O
victory O
mean O
say O
Wilder B-PER
don O
move O
to O
dis O
level O
with O
Muhammad B-PER
Ali I-PER
for O
straight O
title O
defence O
win O
without O
defeat O
. O

Les B-ORG
Elephantes I-ORG
and O
Super B-ORG
Falcons I-ORG
bin O
play O
0 O
- O
0 O
draw O
for O
Abidjan B-LOC
four B-DATE
days I-DATE
earlier I-DATE
, O
and O
Nigeria B-LOC
be O
di O
favourite O
to O
win O
am O
for O
Agege B-LOC
, O
but O
coach O
Clementine B-PER
Toure I-PER
and O
her O
girls O
decide O
say O
dem O
go O
change O
am O
for O
dem O
. O

Boxer O
Patrick B-PER
Day I-PER
don O
die O
at O
age B-DATE
27 I-DATE
- O
four B-DATE
days I-DATE
afta O
im O
suffer O
brain O
injury O
from O
fight O
against O
Charles B-PER
Conwell I-PER
. O

Dem O
carry O
Day B-PER
from O
di O
ring O
wit O
stretcher O
. O

Protests O
don O
dey O
happun O
for O
Barcelona B-ORG
since O
last B-DATE
week I-DATE
afta O
nine O
Catalan O
separatist O
leaders O
get O
jail O
sentence O
earlier B-DATE
dis I-DATE
month I-DATE
. O

La O
Liga O
want O
make O
di O
new O
date O
be O
4 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

Di O
two O
goals O
for O
di O
match O
come O
inside O
di O
first O
half O
as O
Senegal B-LOC
make O
sure O
say O
Brazil B-LOC
no O
beat O
dem O
for O
dia O
first O
meeting O
togeda O
. O

Joe B-PER
Aribo I-PER
score O
Nigeria B-LOC
first O
goal O
for O
di O
35th B-DATE
minute I-DATE
of O
di O
game O
afta O
im O
collect O
fine O
pass O
from O
Simon B-PER
inside O
di O
penalty O
box O
. O

Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
coach O
, O
Gernot B-PER
Rohr I-PER
plan O
use O
today B-DATE
match O
take O
prepare O
im O
team O
for O
dia O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

Dem O
beat O
Valencia B-ORG
3 O
- O
0 O
for O
Spain B-LOC
, O
Ziyech B-PER
waya O
shot O
from O
25 O
yards O
to O
score O
di O
first O
goal O
of O
di O
match O
. O

Di O
last O
time O
wey O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
lose O
for O
Premier O
League O
na O
for O
January B-DATE
29 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2019 I-DATE
wen O
Newcastle B-ORG
bin O
beat O
dem O
2 O
- O
1 O
. O

Fraser B-PER
- I-PER
Pryce I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
32 B-DATE
- I-DATE
years I-DATE
don O
become O
di O
oldest O
woman O
to O
win O
Olympic O
or O
world O
100m O
title O
, O
two B-DATE
years I-DATE
afta O
she O
born O
her O
pikin O
, O
Zyon B-PER
. O

Mrs O
Ogere B-PER
Siasia I-PER
, O
76 B-DATE
, O
and O
two O
odas O
don O
dey O
di O
hands O
of O
jaguda O
pipo O
wey O
kidnap O
dem O
for O
Bayelsa B-LOC
, O
southern B-LOC
Nigeria I-LOC
ten B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

Recently O
Siasia B-PER
bin O
file O
appeal O
against O
di O
life O
ban O
wey O
world O
football O
joinbodi O
Fifa B-ORG
nack O
ontop O
im O
head O
for O
match O
- O
fixing O
. O

Siasia B-PER
na O
di O
most O
decorated O
African O
football O
coach O
for O
Olympics O
, O
afta O
im O
win O
silver O
for O
Beijing B-LOC
Games O
in O
2008 B-DATE
and O
bronze O
for O
2016 B-DATE
Games O
in O
Rio B-LOC
. O

Defenders O
: O
Olaoluwa B-PER
Aina I-PER
( O
Torino B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Italy B-LOC
) O
; O
Abdullahi B-PER
Shehu I-PER
( O
Bursaspor B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Turkey B-LOC
) O
; O
Chidozie B-PER
Awaziem I-PER
( O
CD B-ORG
Leganes I-ORG
, O
Spain B-LOC
) O
; O
William B-PER
Ekong I-PER
( O
Udinese B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Italy B-LOC
) O
; O
Kenneth B-PER
Omeruo I-PER
( O
CD B-ORG
Leganes I-ORG
, O
Spain B-LOC
) O
; O
Jamilu B-PER
Collins I-PER
( O
SC B-ORG
Padeborn I-ORG
07 I-ORG
, O
Germany B-LOC
) O
; O
Oluwasemilogo B-PER
Ajayi I-PER
( O
West B-ORG
Bromwich I-ORG
Albion I-ORG
, O
England B-LOC
) O
. O

No O
be O
just O
say O
make O
two O
men O
come O
togeda O
to O
fight O
. O
"""" O

Na O
just O
recently O
for O
2018 B-DATE
, O
dem O
begin O
allow O
women O
to O
drive O
car O
but O
even O
now O
women O
still O
need O
permission O
of O
man O
to O
travel O
or O
carri O
passport O
. O

Scientists O
don O
warn O
say O
if O
authorities O
too O
rush O
with O
di O
way O
dem O
call O
of O
dia O
lockdown O
measures O
, O
e O
fit O
lead O
to O
second O
wave O
of O
coronavirus O
infections O
even O
as O
cases O
and O
deaths O
don O
dey O
reduce O
. O

In O
just O
3 B-DATE
days I-DATE
dem O
see O
3 O
, O
000 O
new O
cases O
for O
April B-DATE
and O
come O
put O
back O
di O
lockdown O
to O
1 B-DATE
June I-DATE
. O

Di O
number O
of O
new O
cases O
bin O
don O
go O
down O
to O
zero O
but O
by O
17 B-DATE
March I-DATE
need O
dey O
for O
second O
lockdown O
na O
why O
e O
dey O
important O
for O
oda O
kontris O
to O
keep O
dat O
one O
for O
mind O
. O

But O
e O
go O
work O
? O

Di O
IMF B-ORG
director O
of O
Research O
Gita B-PER
Gopinath I-PER
tink O
say O
di O
economy O
of O
di O
world O
go O
lose O
US B-LOC
$ O
9 O
trilliom O
and O
dat O
na O
for O
di O
best O
case O
scenario O
. O

Dem O
go O
fit O
cancel O
di O
annual O
Hajj O
Pilgrimage O
for O
July B-DATE
in O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
ontop O
dis O
same O
Covid O
- O
9 O
. O

Headlines O
wey O
say O
Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
dey O
"""" O
seriously O
sick O
"""" O
, O
"""" O
brain O
- O
dead O
"""" O
or O
im O
dey O
"""" O
recover O
from O
operation O
"""" O
go O
always O
dey O
impossible O
to O
torchlight O
. O

E O
dey O
important O
to O
note O
say O
nobody O
don O
deny O
say O
Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
undergo O
heart O
surgery O
. O

Kim B-PER
sister O
, O
Kim B-PER
Yo I-PER
- I-PER
jong I-PER
, O
look O
like O
di O
clear O
choice O
. O

If O
singles O
choose O
to O
engage O
in O
sexual O
contact O
, O
dem O
must O
take O
precautions O
to O
minimise O
di O
risk O
of O
coronavirus O
exposure O
, O
di O
authority O
tok O
. O

Di O
more O
pipo O
una O
dey O
see O
, O
di O
greater O
di O
chance O
of O
( O
spreading O
) O
di O
coronavirus O
. O
"""" O

Di O
RIVM B-ORG
also O
issue O
advice O
for O
pipo O
wey O
dia O
long O
- O
term O
partners O
suspect O
say O
don O
catch O
di O
coronavirus O
. O

"""" O
Sex O
with O
yourself O
or O
with O
odas O
at O
a O
distance O
dey O
possible O
, O
"""" O
e O
add O
, O
e O
suggest O
"""" O
erotic O
stories O
"""" O
and O
"""" O
masturbating O
togeda O
"""" O
as O
possible O
solutions O
. O

I O
no O
defend O
mysef O
becos O
I O
bin O
dey O
tink O
say O
to O
harm O
woman O
dey O
wrong O
. O

She O
go O
dey O
ontop O
of O
me O
. O

I O
come O
dey O
fear O
to O
return O
to O
di O
hotel O
afta O
work O
, O
so O
I O
go O
dey O
waka O
about O
shopping O
mall O
until O
dem O
close O
. O

She O
go O
call O
and O
promise O
say O
evritin O
go O
dey O
fine O
. O

She O
no O
fit O
go O
anywhere O
without O
me O
- O
I O
be O
play O
toy O
wey O
need O
to O
entertain O
her O
all O
di O
time O
. O

We O
get O
house O
wey O
get O
two O
bedroom O
but O
she O
no O
go O
gree O
me O
use O
di O
main O
bedroom O
, O
na O
di O
one O
wey O
guest O
dey O
use O
I O
bin O
give O
. O

She O
waka O
pass O
me O
and O
see O
me O
. O

Alyona B-PER
Kryvuliak I-PER
, O
head O
of O
the O
La B-ORG
Strada I-ORG
- I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG
National I-ORG
Hotline I-ORG
Department I-ORG
, O
and O
Olena B-PER
Kochemyrovska I-PER
, O
adviser O
to O
the O
UN B-ORG
Population I-ORG
Fund I-ORG
on O
prevention O
and O
counteraction O
of O
gender O
- O
caused O
violence O
, O
name O
these O
and O
oda O
reasons O
. O

I O
dey O
tink O
wetin O
wey O
I O
no O
want O
do O
sake O
of O
say O
I O
don O
dey O
used O
to O
am O
. O

Wen O
I O
bin O
dey O
used O
to O
dey O
panic O
, O
I O
go O
push O
her O
away O
, O
hide O
, O
and O
run O
- O
run O
away O
from O
house O
, O
or O
from O
di O
room O
. O

But O
on O
top O
one O
or O
two O
digging O
dem O
find O
dia O
identity O
and O
like O
day O
, O
Sita B-PER
turn O
di O
face O
of O
coronavirus O
for O
Indonesia B-LOC
. O

She O
say O
di O
media O
too O
far O
and O
even O
when O
she O
bin O
dey O
for O
hospital O
, O
she O
watch O
for O
television O
as O
dem O
pack O
for O
her O
house O
even O
as O
one O
press O
freedom O
group O
, O
Alliance B-ORG
of I-ORG
Independent I-ORG
Journalists I-ORG
say O
make O
di O
media O
avoid O
"""" O
sensationalism O
"""" O
and O
respect O
privacy O
of O
covid O
- O
19 O
cases O
. O

WHO B-ORG
Emergencies O
Director O
, O
Dr O
Mike B-PER
Ryan I-PER
wey O
tok O
dis O
one O
for O
one O
virtual O
press O
briefing O
say O
, O
e O
dey O
important O
for O
pipo O
to O
know O
say O
dis O
virus O
fit O
become O
anoda O
common O
virus O
for O
di O
world O
just O
like O
HIV O
. O

Kaffy B-PER
wey O
be O
dancer O
like O
her O
also O
comment O
. O

Tori O
pipo O
AFP B-ORG
say O
im O
death O
no O
dey O
linked O
to O
coronavirus O
. O

Steven B-PER
Wonder I-PER
, O
Billie B-PER
Eilish I-PER
and O
Sir O
Elton B-PER
John I-PER
go O
perform O
for O
TV O
concert O
wey O
Lady B-PER
Gaga I-PER
go O
organise O
, O
to O
celebrate O
health O
workers O
wey O
dey O
fight O
di O
coronavirus O
crisis O
. O

Many O
of O
im O
fans O
around O
di O
world O
reach O
out O
to O
am O
to O
try O
to O
support O
am O
. O

For O
2013 B-DATE
, O
Khan B-PER
win O
India B-LOC
National O
Film O
Award O
for O
im O
leading O
role O
for O
Paan B-PER
Singh I-PER
Tomar I-PER
, O
di O
life O
story O
about O
one O
top O
athlete O
wey O
become O
bandit O
. O

Na O
so O
Teni B-PER
tok O
Nigeria B-LOC
musician O
, O
Teni B-PER
, O
na O
one O
of O
di O
most O
celebrated O
afrobeats O
artists O
today B-DATE
. O

She O
dey O
conscious O
to O
be O
role O
model O
to O
plenti O
boys O
and O
girls O
wey O
fit O
dey O
deal O
with O
dia O
own O
images O
and O
self O
- O
acceptance O
. O

"""" O
I O
remember O
one O
time O
wey O
I O
go O
Disney B-ORG
with O
my O
friend O
for O
Orlando B-LOC
during O
summer B-DATE
and O
e O
dey O
hot O
and O
my O
friend O
face O
look O
like O
mud O
! O

She O
say O
: O
"""" O
I O
no O
dey O
sure O
of O
my O
next O
step O
but O
i O
go O
remain O
in O
quarantine O
until O
dem O
tell O
me O
to O
do O
otherwise O
. O
. O
. O
"""" O
Kim B-PER
Kardashian I-PER
, O
Naomi B-PER
Campbell I-PER
, O
Arnold B-PER
Schwarzenegger I-PER
, O
Taylor B-PER
Swift I-PER
, O
Ariana B-PER
Grande I-PER
, O
Lizzo B-PER
and O
oda O
celebrities O
don O
come O
out O
for O
social O
media O
to O
share O
tips O
wey O
go O
help O
stop O
di O
spread O
of O
di O
virus O
. O

She O
tok O
say O
, O
"""" O
DJ B-PER
Obi I-PER
party O
bin O
get O
plenti O
celebs O
with O
oda O
pipo O
join O
and O
dey O
very O
interesting O
. O

Anoda O
pesin O
, O
Moses B-PER
Imodu I-PER
describe O
di O
House O
Party O
App O
say O
, O
"""" O
na O
like O
combination O
of O
Whatsapp O
, O
Snapchat O
an O
Skype O
as O
you O
fit O
video O
chat O
with O
up O
to O
eight O
pipo O
and O
also O
fit O
play O
online O
games O
. O
"""" O

Although O
the O
president O
of O
di O
guild O
, O
Emeka B-PER
Rollas I-PER
, O
say O
im O
no O
go O
fit O
prove O
if O
Henshaw B-PER
be O
member O
of O
di O
actors O
joinbodi O
, O
na O
on O
top O
interview O
wey O
im O
give O
Plustv B-ORG
Africa I-ORG
im O
tok O
dat O
one O
. O

"""" O
You O
fit O
be O
be O
star O
or O
celebrity O
but O
you O
fit O
no O
be O
member O
of O
our O
joinbodi O
, O
"""" O
Rollas B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
interview O
. O

Rollas B-PER
say O
im O
no O
see O
way O
Henshaw B-PER
and O
di O
rest O
pipo O
dey O
vex O
. O

Di O
president O
even O
say O
na O
Senator O
Abbo B-PER
holy O
pass O
. O

Pipo O
for O
social O
media O
don O
dey O
tok O
dia O
mind O
on O
top O
di O
movie O
. O

Di O
African O
Giant O
album O
of O
Burna B-PER
wey O
im O
real O
name O
na O
Damini B-PER
Ebunoluwa I-PER
Ogulu I-PER
, O
dey O
for O
di O
Best O
World O
Music O
Album O
category O
of O
di O
award O
wey O
be O
number O
54 O
category O
. O

Di O
25 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
pop O
star O
don O
tok O
about O
im O
drug O
abuse O
and O
abusing O
im O
relationship O
before O
, O
but O
dis O
latest O
video O
na O
di O
first O
time O
e O
dey O
tok O
about O
am O
for O
camera O
. O

Di O
director O
of O
di O
feem O
, O
Kayode B-PER
Kasum I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Wen O
I O
be O
young O
boy O
, O
I O
dream O
of O
becoming O
pesin O
wey O
dey O
educated O
; O
maybe O
teacher O
, O
doctor O
or O
something O
like O
dat O
, O
"""" O
Shabalala B-PER
tell O
tori O
pipo O
, O
The B-ORG
Citizen I-ORG
for O
2014 B-DATE
. O

E O
begin O
work O
for O
di O
family O
farm O
and O
later O
, O
for O
one O
local O
factory O
. O

"""" O
My O
sincere O
condolences O
to O
im O
family O
and O
friends O
. O
"""" O

She O
just O
comot O
from O
bathroom O
and O
dey O
try O
change O
cloth O
wen O
di O
pesin O
record O
her O
. O
"""" O

But O
Deezel B-PER
also O
release O
im O
own O
statement O
say O
no O
be O
im O
release O
di O
video O
and O
e O
no O
get O
anything O
to O
gain O
by O
doing O
dat O
. O

E O
neva O
too O
tay O
wey O
somebody O
release O
anoda O
nude O
video O
for O
social O
media O
wey O
show O
somebody O
wey O
look O
like O
one O
senator O
and O
di O
issue O
also O
cause O
tok O
- O
tok O
for O
Twitter B-ORG
. O

Cherry B-PER
na O
medical O
doctor O
from O
Imo B-LOC
state I-LOC
wit O
fine O
smile O
to O
match O
. O

Di O
artists O
coming O
back O
togeda O
as O
friends O
lead O
to O
happiness O
for O
many O
of O
dia O
fans O
as O
dem O
begin O
tweet O
concerning O
dis O
. O

FireBoy B-PER
DML I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
JoeBoy B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Marioo B-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Rema B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Simmy B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Wendy B-PER
Shay I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Blow O
My O
Mind O
- O
Davido B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Daz O
How O
Star O
Do O
- O
Skibii B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Gugulethu O
- O
Prince B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
[ O
SA B-LOC
] O
- O
Winner O
Jama B-PER
- O
DJ B-PER
Mic I-PER
Smith I-PER
[ O
GH B-LOC
] O
Killin O
Dem O
- O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Inama B-PER
- O
Diamond B-PER
PlatNumz I-PER
[ O
TZ B-LOC
] O
Innos B-PER
B I-PER
[ O
CG B-LOC
] O
Nandy B-PER
[ O
TZ B-LOC
] O
JoeBoy B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
- O
Winner O
Otile B-PER
Brown I-PER
[ O
KE B-LOC
] O
Kizz B-PER
Daniel I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Teni B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Mayorkun B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Rayvanny B-PER
[ O

TZ B-LOC
] O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
BlaqBonez B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Falz B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
KHALIGRAPH B-PER
Jones I-PER
( O
KE B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Kwesta B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Medikal B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Shinski B-PER
( O
KE B-LOC
) O
Sarkodie B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Reminisce B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Ricky B-PER
Rick I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Zakwe B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Black B-PER
Motion I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Blaq B-PER
diamond I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
DopeNation B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Ethic B-PER
( O
KE B-LOC
) O
Show B-PER
Dem I-PER
Camp I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Toofan B-PER
( O
TG B-LOC
) O
Cracker B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Prince B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Jay B-PER
Synth I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Kel B-PER
P I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
MOG B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Ozedikus B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

Na O
elections O
season O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
and O
we O
go O
start O
with O
Ghana B-LOC
wey O
go O
hold O
dia O
presidential O
elections O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

For O
2017 B-DATE
, O
when O
dem O
hold O
dia O
last O
presidential O
election O
, O
na O
14 O
, O
000 O
clan O
delegates O
pick O
dia O
lawmakers O
wey O
later O
pick O
dia O
president O
. O

Anoda O
sports O
competition O
wey O
go O
grab O
pipo O
attention O
na O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
wey O
go O
also O
happun O
for O
April B-DATE
. O

From O
Rihanna B-PER
to O
Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
, O
to O
Stonebwoy B-PER
, O
many O
albums O
dey O
drop O
hopefully O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

For O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
President O
Buhari B-PER
promise O
to O
complete O
road O
projects O
, O
build O
houses O
among O
odas O
for O
2020 B-DATE
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
President O
promise O
to O
deal O
with O
separatists O
wey O
refuse O
to O
drop O
dia O
arms O
, O
say O
new O
Cameroon B-LOC
wey O
go O
adapt O
to O
present O
times O
reality O
with O
eye O
for O
di O
future O
dey O
take O
shape O
. O

American O
- O
Senegalese O
musician O
Akon B-PER
, O
dey O
one O
step O
closer O
to O
achieve O
im O
ogbonge O
'Akon B-LOC
City' I-LOC
for O
Senegal B-LOC
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
city O
go O
be O
five B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
drive O
from O
di O
kontri O
new O
international O
airport O
. O

Dis O
no O
go O
be O
di O
only O
project O
wey O
Akon B-PER
don O
run O
for O
Africa B-LOC
, O
for O
2007 B-DATE
, O
he O
join O
hand O
to O
form O
di O
Konfidence B-ORG
Foundation I-ORG
, O
wey O
be O
health O
and O
education O
charity O
for O
pikin O
dem O
wey O
no O
too O
get O
for O
West B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
America B-LOC
. O

Di O
chief O
magistrate O
Tajudeen B-PER
Elias I-PER
na O
im O
troway O
di O
mata O
dis B-DATE
morning I-DATE
. O

On O
top O
why O
di O
singer O
no O
appear O
for O
court O
, O
di O
lawyer O
say O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
presently O
dey O
out O
of O
di O
kontri O
na O
im O
make O
am O
. O

Dem O
go O
come O
give O
di O
money O
to O
di O
poor O
pipo O
di O
next O
day O
- O
on O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
. O

Today B-DATE
, O
those O
boxes O
no O
popular O
like O
before O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Eternals O
go O
introduce O
Marvel B-ORG
movie O
first O
gay O
character O
. O

Reports O
don O
dey O
spread O
since O
2019 B-DATE
say O
Phase O
4 O
of O
di O
MCU O
, O
dat O
na O
di O
feems O
afta O
di O
Avengers O
Infinity O
saga O
- O
go O
feature O
transgender O
character O
. O

For O
July B-DATE
last I-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
one O
tori O
pipo O
, O
Geeks B-ORG
Worldwide I-ORG
suggest O
say O
Marvel B-ORG
dey O
look O
for O
trans O
woman O
for O
one O
project O
wey O
dem O
wan O
feem O
for O
2020 B-DATE
. O

Although O
di O
picture O
wey O
she O
put O
no O
show O
di O
face O
of O
her O
fiancé O
, O
she O
use O
di O
# O
MrsEkpataLoading O
to O
take O
announce O
her O
engagement O
. O

Mollie B-PER
na O
actress O
, O
movie O
director O
and O
producer O
wey O
don O
get O
some O
small O
small O
roles O
for O
film O
. O

Dis O
na O
as O
several O
oda O
pipo O
for O
social O
media O
don O
dey O
hala O
say O
, O
dis O
move O
don O
start O
World O
War O
III O
. O

Dis O
go O
be O
di O
fourth O
edition O
of O
di O
music O
awards O
wey O
get O
both O
viting O
and O
non O
- O
voting O
categories O
. O

For O
dia O
2019 B-DATE
show O
, O
di O
event O
trend O
afta O
di O
mama O
of O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
comot O
to O
collect O
her O
pikin O
award O
. O

Kainama B-PER
- O
Harmonize B-PER
x O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Killin O
Dem O
- O
Burna B-PER
Box I-PER
x O
Zlatan B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Kpo O
K3K3 O
- O
Stonebwoy B-PER
x O
Medikal B-PER
x O
Kelvynboy B-PER
x O
Kwesi B-PER
Arthur I-PER
x O
Darkovibes B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Oil O
& O
Gas O
- O
Olamide B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
VIEWERS' O
CHOICE O
49 O
- O
99 O
- O
Tiwa B-PER
Savage I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Able O
God O
- O
Chinko B-PER
Ekun I-PER
x O
Lil B-PER
Kesh I-PER
x O
Zlatan B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Banomoya B-PER
- O
DJ B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
x O
Busisiwa B-PER
x O
TNS B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
My O
Level O
- O
Shatta B-PER
Wale I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
On O
The O
Low O
- O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Soapy O
- O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O

Na O
im O
lead O
to O
di O
long O
music O
break O
afta O
we O
VIP O
platform O
fall O
down O
. O
"""" O

Elba B-PER
bin O
act O
as O
Nelson B-PER
Mandela I-PER
for O
di O
feem O
Long O
Walk O
to O
Freedom O
, O
but O
im O
blow O
afta O
im O
act O
for O
HBO B-ORG
series O
The O
Wire O
, O
for O
di O
feem O
im O
act O
as O
drug O
capone O
for O
Stringer O
Bell O
. O

South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
beauty O
queen O
Zozibini B-PER
Tunzi I-PER
na O
di O
2019 B-DATE
Miss O
Universe O
winner O
. O

See O
some O
of O
dia O
Tweets O

Di O
Met B-ORG
Police I-ORG
say O
dem O
neva O
arrest O
anybody O
. O

Met O
police O
say O
dem O
call O
officers O
make O
dem O
come O
dia O
house O
for O
Palace B-LOC
Green I-LOC
, O
Kensington B-LOC
, O
shortly O
after O
23 B-DATE
: I-DATE
00 I-DATE
GMT I-DATE
. O

For O
di O
statement O
wen O
oga O
Orlando B-PER
carry O
come O
out O
, O
e O
say O
dem O
arrest O
Duncan B-PER
Mighty I-PER
afta O
one O
upcoming O
rapper O
, O
M2 B-PER
write O
complain O
against O
am O
say O
e O
collect O
money O
and O
no O
gree O
do O
work O
wey O
dem O
pay O
am O
to O
do O
. O

Some O
fans O
no O
too O
gbadu O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
part O
for O
Davido B-PER
new O
album O
"""" O
A O
Good O
Time O
"""" O
wey O
just O
drop O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
di O
event O
happun O
for O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
commercial O
centre O
and O
di O
organiser O
say O
dem O
do O
di O
event O
to O
showcase O
di O
"""" O
best O
and O
unique O
modern O
art O
from O
Africa B-LOC
and O
for O
abroad O
"""" O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
ART O
X O
Prize O
- O
di O
ogbonge O
prize O
of O
di O
fair O
- O
go O
to O
Etinosa B-PER
Yvonne I-PER
wey O
be O
documentary O
photographer O
for O
Lagos B-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
she O
teach O
herself O
di O
work O
. O

Game O
of O
Thrones O
na O
HBO B-ORG
most O
popular O
series O
. O

Dia O
reason O
na O
say O
di O
feem O
dem O
bin O
show O
am O
for O
theatre O
for O
October B-DATE
1967 I-DATE
, O
wey O
disqualify O
for O
di O
1968 B-DATE
season I-DATE
. O

To O
make O
matters O
work O
worse O
, O
13 B-DATE
Hours I-DATE
lost O
to O
Mel B-PER
Gibson's I-PER
World O
War O
Two O
drama O
Hacksaw O
Ridge O
. O

Las O
- O
las O
everything O
fit O
end O
man O
. O
"""" O

Ghanaians O
eye O
get O
over O
news O
say O
American O
Grammy O
- O
winning O
rapper O
Cardi B-PER
B I-PER
dey O
drop O
de O
motherland O
dis O
December B-DATE
for O
music O
festival O
. O

Last B-DATE
month I-DATE
, O
di O
Academy O
announce O
say O
93 O
kontris O
submit O
dia O
films O
for O
di O
category O
and O
ten O
of O
di O
films O
come O
from O
Africa B-LOC
. O

Jesus B-PER
na O
di O
main O
figure O
of O
di O
Christian O
religion O
and O
many O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
follow O
di O
religion O
believe O
say O
im O
be O
di O
son O
of O
God O
wey O
die O
for O
di O
sins O
of O
di O
world O
over O
2000 B-DATE
years I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

Also O
, O
actress O
Nancy B-PER
Isime I-PER
and O
rapper O
Reminisce B-PER
na O
who O
dey O
follow O
host O
di O
event O
. O

Some O
fashionistas O
don O
already O
start O
to O
dey O
pepper O
red O
carpet O
. O

2 O
. O
Him O
get O
him O
stage O
name O
from O
late O
reggae O
icon O
Bob B-PER
Marley I-PER
wey O
he O
consider O
him O
inspiration O
. O

3 O
. O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
tok O
say O
him O
be O
di O
pioneer O
of O
AfroBaashment O
- O
sound O
wey O
be O
fusion O
of O
afrobeat O
with O
Jamaican O
and O
British O
influences O
. O

6 O
. O
He O
blast O
Simi B-PER
afta O
she O
condemn O
yahoo O
yahoo O
for O
social O
media O
. O

He O
tell O
am O
say O
make O
she O
siddon O
pray O
for O
yahoo O
boys O
. O

8 O
. O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
management O
don O
release O
statement O
say O
he O
no O
be O
yahoo O
boy O
and O
dem O
add O
say O
him O
lawyers O
dey O
work O
to O
prove O
him O
innocence O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
di O
Headies O
2019 B-DATE
awards O
honour O
some O
of O
Nigeria B-LOC
ogbonge O
musicians O
like O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
, O
Teni B-PER
, O
Falz B-PER
, O
Chinko B-PER
Ekun I-PER
and O
many O
more O
. O

Di O
Headies O
na O
one O
of O
di O
ogbonge O
awards O
wey O
dem O
torchlight O
Nigerian O
performers O
and O
plenti O
pipo O
dey O
always O
look O
forward O
to O
am O
every O
year O
. O

However O
, O
many O
of O
di O
pipo O
wey O
watch O
di O
event O
from O
dia O
house O
tok O
say O
di O
two O
of O
dem O
no O
gel O
togeda O
, O
wetin O
oyibo O
pipo O
dey O
call O
'chemistry' O
, O
as O
dem O
no O
feel O
say O
di O
two O
of O
dem O
connect O
well O
. O

Still O
, O
pipo O
no O
like O
how O
winners O
on O
di O
night B-DATE
no O
show O
to O
collect O
dia O
award O
. O

. O
Sam B-PER
Faiers I-PER
, O
28 B-DATE
, O
( O
£ O
6 O
. O
3m O
) O
23 O
. O
Joey B-PER
Essex I-PER
, O
29 B-DATE
, O
( O
£ O
6 O
. O
3m O
) O
24 O
. O
Tommy B-PER
Mallet I-PER
, O
27 B-DATE
, O
( O
£ O
5 O
. O
2m O
) O
- O
new O
entry O
25 O
. O
Maisie B-PER
Williams I-PER
, O
22 B-DATE
, O
( O
£ O
4 O
. O
5m O
) O
- O
new O
entry O
26 O
. O
George B-PER
Ezra I-PER
, O
26 B-DATE
, O
( O
£ O
4 O
. O
4m O
) O
- O
new O
entry O
27 O
. O
Jess B-PER
Glynne I-PER
, O
30 B-DATE
, O
£ O
4 O
. O
4m O
- O
new O
entry O
28 O
. O
Olivia B-PER
and O
Alex B-PER
Bowen I-PER
, O
25 B-DATE
and O
28 B-DATE
, O
( O
£ O
4 O
. O
3m O
- O
joint O
) O
- O
new O
entry O
29 O
. O
Billie B-PER
Faiers I-PER
, O
29 B-DATE
, O
( O
£ O
3 O
. O
6m O
) O
- O
new O
entry O
30 O
. O
Tom B-PER
Holland I-PER
, O
23 B-DATE
, O
( O
£ O
3 O
. O
5m O
) O
- O

Some O
of O
di O
issues O
wey O
di O
panel O
go O
discuss O
na O
tins O
wey O
already O
dey O
cause O
tok O
tok O
for O
di O
kontri O
. O

Wen O
di O
fight O
start O
Whittaker B-PER
bin O
get O
upper O
hand O
as O
im O
carry O
heavy O
punch O
dey O
blow O
Adesanya B-PER
for O
head O
but O
as O
di O
fight O
dey O
go O
on O
, O
Adesanya B-PER
come O
do O
im O
own O
back O
and O
beat O
Whittaker B-PER
. O

Di O
way O
Israel B-PER
Adesanya I-PER
dey O
popular O
all O
ova O
di O
world O
surprise O
pipo O
, O
im O
explode O
enta O
di O
global O
MMA B-ORG
scene O
only O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
afta O
e O
come O
di O
UFC B-ORG
wit O
undefeated O
11 O
- O
0 O
record O
. O

E O
come O
still O
continue O
to O
get O
six O
successive O
wins O
inside O
di O
fighting O
cage O
, O
togeda O
with O
im O
win O
over O
Kelvin B-PER
Gastelum I-PER
for O
UFC B-ORG
236 O
in O
April B-DATE
wey O
make O
am O
get O
di O
interim O
middleweight O
title O
for O
di O
Fight O
of O
di O
Year O
contender O
inside O
Atlanta B-LOC
. O

Even O
though O
most O
of O
di O
fans O
of O
di O
show O
dey O
use O
dia O
money O
vote O
for O
dia O
favourite O
contestant O
, O
some O
of O
dem O
dey O
go O
further O
to O
spend O
dia O
money O
in O
support O
of O
dia O
favourite O
contestants O
. O

For O
one O
of O
her O
Instagram O
post O
, O
she O
reveal O
say O
she O
send O
Tacha B-PER
money O
afta O
dem O
disqualify O
am O
. O

For O
di O
video O
, O
she O
dey O
sing O
to O
"""" O
Ready O
or O
Not O
"""" O
by O
di O
Fugees B-ORG
and O
na O
for O
dia O
kasala O
burst O
. O

Still O
, O
pipo O
no O
accept O
her O
apology O
. O

No O
be O
today B-DATE
dis O
tok O
ontop O
Gina B-PER
Rodriguez I-PER
mata O
start O
. O

"""" O
Well O
, O
first O
of O
all O
I O
don O
dream O
of O
to O
own O
my O
own O
record O
store O
. O
. O
. O

I O
dey O
always O
collect O
music O
wen O
I O
be O
small O
boy O
. O

"""" O
I O
see O
am O
as O
natural O
way O
to O
go O
afta O
I O
leave O
school O
to O
continue O
di O
hobby O
of O
my O
childhood O
, O
"""" O
na O
so O
Tejuoso B-PER
tok O
. O

Nowadays O
, O
for O
time O
wen O
Afrobeats O
dey O
enjoy O
airplays O
for O
radio O
and O
for O
nightclubs O
, O
Di B-ORG
Jazzhole I-ORG
position O
imself O
as O
custodian O
of O
a O
different O
type O
of O
music O
. O

