Mixed B-ORG
Martial I-ORG
Arts I-ORG
joinbodi O
, O
Ultimate B-ORG
Fighting I-ORG
Championship I-ORG
, O
UFC B-ORG
don O
decide O
say O
dem O
go O
enta O
back O
di O
octagon O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
, I-DATE
9 I-DATE
May I-DATE
, O
for O
Jacksonville B-LOC
, O
Florida B-LOC
. O

Di O
Florida B-ORG
State I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
say O
dem O
dey O
collabo O
with O
di O
UFC B-ORG
to O
make O
sure O
say O
health O
and O
safety O
protocols O
dey O
ground O
to O
ensure O
say O
evri O
pesin O
wey O
attend O
di O
event O
day O
safe O
. O

On O
di O
first O
day O
, O
di O
number O
one O
lightweight O
fighter O
Tony B-PER
Ferguson I-PER
go O
face O
number O
four O
Justin B-PER
Gaethje I-PER
, O
for O
di O
UFC B-ORG
banterweight O
Championship O
wia O
Henry B-PER
Cejudo I-PER
dey O
look O
to O
flog O
multiple O
- O
time O
title O
holder O
Dominick B-PER
Cruz I-PER
. O

Cooking O
burns O
, O
dog O
bites O
na O
some O
of O
di O
injury O
dem O
wey O
some O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
players O
don O
get O
during O
di O
coronavirus O
lockdown O
. O

United B-ORG
doctor O
Steve B-PER
McNally I-PER
say O
even O
though O
say O
di O
break O
don O
give O
di O
players O
time O
to O
recover O
, O
dem O
dey O
see O
increase O
for O
some O
kain O
funny O
- O
funny O
injuries O
. O

"""" O
Fortunately O
, O
most O
of O
di O
boys O
dey O
well O
and O
we O
no O
get O
any O
real O
issues O
at O
all O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
di O
McNally B-PER
tok O
for O
di O
club O
official O
app O
. O

If O
dem O
win O
, O
Dortmund B-ORG
go O
close O
reduce O
to O
one O
point O
di O
gap O
wey O
Bayern B-ORG
dey O
give O
dem O
. O

In O
fact O
, O
di O
only O
kontris O
for O
Africa B-LOC
wey O
StarTimes B-ORG
no O
cover O
na O
Algeria B-LOC
, O
Morocco B-LOC
, O
Libya B-LOC
and O
Tunisia B-LOC
Meanwhile O
BetWay B-ORG
wey O
be O
sports O
betting O
website O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
tweet O
say O
all O
dia O
customers O
fit O
watch O
di O
matches O
live O
ontop O
dia O
website O
. O

SATURDAY B-DATE
16TH I-DATE
MAY I-DATE
2020 I-DATE
B B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Schalke B-ORG
Augsburg I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Wolfsburg B-ORG
Düsseldorf I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Paderborn B-ORG
RB I-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Freiburg B-ORG
Hoffenheim I-ORG
14 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
Hertha B-ORG
Berlin I-ORG
Frankfurt I-ORG
17 B-DATE
: I-DATE
30 I-DATE
B B-ORG
Mgladbach I-ORG

Conditions O
Di O
Premier O
League O
, O
wey O
be O
di O
league O
wey O
football O
fans O
dey O
watch O
pass O
for O
di O
world O
no O
go O
resume O
anytime O
before O
1 B-DATE
June I-DATE
, O
afta O
di O
British O
goment O
on O
Monday B-DATE
comot O
to O
say O
no O
sport O
event O
fit O
hold O
in O
di O
kontri O
before O
dis O
date O
. O

Conditions O
Spain B-LOC
top O
league O
and O
working O
place O
of O
Lionel B-PER
Messi I-PER
dey O
torchlight O
June B-DATE
12 I-DATE
as O
di O
date O
when O
dem O
go O
resume O
di O
season O
. O

Dis O
don O
vex O
some O
clubs O
wey O
dey O
bottom O
and O
di O
mata O
don O
even O
turn O
to O
court O
mata O
. O

Bjornsson B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
powerlifter O
play O
di O
role O
of O
Ser O
Gregor O
"""" O
Di O
Mountain O
"""" O
Clegane O
for O
di O
HBO B-ORG
series O
, O
break O
di O
record O
for O
Im O
own O
gym O
for O
Im O
hometown O
, O
Iceland B-LOC
. O

Na O
sports O
broadcaster O
ESPN B-ORG
stream O
di O
event O
and O
dem O
film O
am O
for O
Bjornsson's B-PER
YouTube O
channel O
. O

so O
many O
pipo O
don O
tok O
say O
, O
'501kg O
no O
go O
ever O
go O
up' O
. O
. O
. O

I O
just O
dey O
speechless O
, O
even O
though O
I O
dey O
talk O
too O
much O
now O
, O
But O
I O
dey O
happy O
- O
Dis O
na O
big O
deal O
for O
me O
Na O
Eddie B-PER
Hall I-PER
, O
one O
British O
man O
who O
become O
di O
first O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
and O
Nigerian O
striker O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
dey O
among O
di O
richest O
players O
wey O
dey O
30 B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
below O
. O

Joshua B-PER
worth O
£ O
107m O
according O
to O
Sunday B-ORG
Times I-ORG
and O
e O
make O
majority O
of O
im O
money O
from O
di O
two O
fights O
against O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jnr I-PER
. O

Top O
of O
di O
list O
of O
sports O
stars O
wey O
dey O
30 B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
below O
na O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
player O
, O
Gareth B-PER
Bale I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
valued O
at O
£ O
114m O
. O

Aside O
Ighalo B-PER
, O
four O
other O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
players O
including O
: O
Paul B-PER
Pogba I-PER
, O
Davide B-PER
de I-PER
Gea I-PER
, O
Anthony B-PER
Martial I-PER
and O
Luke B-PER
Shaw I-PER
make O
di O
18 O
- O
man O
list O
. O

We O
neva O
know O
weda O
Ligue B-ORG
de I-ORG
Football I-ORG
Professional I-ORG
( O
LFP B-ORG
) O
go O
choose O
to O
abandon O
di O
season O
without O
promotion O
or O
relegation O
and O
no O
champions O
or O
dem O
go O
base O
di O
outcome O
of O
di O
campaign O
on O
current O
standings O
. O

"""" O
E O
go O
dey O
possible O
, O
on O
sunny O
days O
, O
to O
practice O
individual O
sporting O
activity O
outdoors O
, O
as O
dem O
go O
respect O
di O
rules O
of O
social O
distancing O
. O

Di O
head O
of O
di O
Dutch B-ORG
FA I-ORG
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
say O
im O
tink O
say O
e O
dey O
"""" O
very O
doubtful O
"""" O
say O
Premier O
League O
go O
fit O
complete O
di O
2019 B-DATE
- I-DATE
20 I-DATE
campaign O
. O

Uefa B-ORG
don O
tok O
say O
dem O
go O
use O
on O
- O
field O
performance O
to O
determine O
which O
clubs O
go O
make O
up O
di O
next O
season O
European O
club O
competitions O
. O

Na O
30 O
match O
balls O
, O
each O
of O
dem O
, O
ball O
boys O
go O
disinfect O
am O
and O
keep O
for O
special O
spots O
rather O
than O
handing O
am O
over O
to O
players O
. O

On O
Saturday B-DATE
, O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
players O
run O
to O
go O
celebrate O
in O
front O
of O
di O
empty O
South O
Bank O
RB B-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG
striker O
Yussuf B-PER
Poulsen I-PER
na O
from O
a O
safe O
distance O
fit O
stay O
interview O
am O
sake O
of O
corona O
. O

European O
football O
governing O
body O
go O
hold O
video O
conference O
meetings O
to O
discuss O
dia O
response O
to O
di O
coronavirus O
outbreak O
. O

Euro O
2020 B-DATE
suppose O
take O
place O
from O
12 B-DATE
June I-DATE
- I-DATE
12 I-DATE
July I-DATE
for O
venues O
all O
ova O
Europe B-LOC
. O

Japan's B-LOC
Prime O
Minister O
Shinzo B-PER
Abe I-PER
say O
di O
International B-ORG
Olympic I-ORG
Committee I-ORG
don O
agree O
to O
di O
delay O
. O

"""" O
I O
proposed O
to O
postpone O
for O
one B-DATE
year I-DATE
and O
[ O
IOC B-ORG
] O
president O
Thomas B-PER
Bach I-PER
don O
give O
100 O
% O
support O
, O
"""" O
Im O
tok O
. O

Di O
one B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
delay O
go O
also O
apply O
to O
di O
Tokyo B-LOC
Paralympic O
Games O
. O

Di O
agreement O
come O
as O
di O
British B-ORG
Olympic I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
BOA B-ORG
) O
dey O
meet O
for O
Tuesday B-DATE
to O
discuss O
di O
matter O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
international O
striker O
Ifeanyi B-PER
George I-PER
don O
die O
for O
motor O
accident O
at O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
26 I-DATE
. O

George B-PER
, O
wey O
get O
two O
caps O
for O
di O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
, O
dey O
involved O
for O
one O
accident O
wey O
happun O
for O
Benin B-LOC
- I-LOC
Agbor I-LOC
road I-LOC
wen O
im O
dey O
travel O
to O
Lagos B-LOC
on O
Sunday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
. O

Joshua B-PER
neva O
fight O
since O
December B-DATE
wen O
im O
win O
di O
fight O
against O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jr I-PER
for O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
to O
collect O
back O
im O
belts O
wey O
di O
Mexican O
- O
American O
bin O
collect O
for O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
wen O
dem O
first O
fight O
for O
June B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
. O

Im O
bin O
suppose O
fight O
Joshua B-PER
for O
October B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
but O
n O
fit O
do O
am O
because O
of O
sholder O
injury O
. O

But O
e O
never O
fit O
help O
di O
Gunners B-ORG
to O
win O
anything O
during O
im O
time O
for O
the O
club O
, O
except O
for O
runners O
- O
up O
medals O
for O
Carabao O
Cup O
and O
Europa O
League O
. O

Dem O
sack O
am O
afta O
e O
finish O
second O
for O
di O
league O
in O
2010 B-DATE
- I-DATE
11 I-DATE
. O

Israel B-PER
Adesanya I-PER
wey O
im O
nickname O
na O
Stylebender B-PER
, O
dey O
represent O
New B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC
wey O
be O
di O
kontri O
im O
parents O
migrate O
to O
. O

Joshua B-PER
win O
im O
belts O
back O
with O
points O
victory O
over O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jr I-PER
. O
for O
December B-DATE
. O

Dis O
go O
be O
Joshua B-PER
first O
fight O
for O
UK B-LOC
since O
im O
beat O
Alexander B-PER
Povetkin I-PER
for O
Wembley B-LOC
for O
September B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
. O

Last B-DATE
week I-DATE
, O
Joshua B-PER
promoter O
Eddie B-PER
Hearn I-PER
tok O
say O
tok O
- O
tok O
dey O
go O
on O
for O
di O
all O
- O
British O
unification O
fight O
between O
Joshua B-PER
and O
Tyson B-PER
Fury I-PER
. O

Fury B-PER
beat O
Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
to O
collect O
di O
WBC O
title O
last B-DATE
month I-DATE
, O
e O
mean O
say O
na O
British O
heavyweights O
hold O
all O
di O
belts O
dem O
for O
di O
division O
. O

Di O
family O
of O
di O
football O
star O
Kazeem B-PER
Tiamiyu I-PER
wey O
die O
for O
Sagamu B-LOC
- O
Ogun B-LOC
state I-LOC
South I-LOC
West I-LOC
Nigeria I-LOC
, O
don O
tok O
about O
wetin O
dem O
remember O
am O
for O
, O
and O
how O
di O
loss O
go O
forever O
affect O
dem O
. O

Tiamiyu B-PER
na O
rising O
footballer O
with O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
club I-ORG
wey O
im O
life O
cut O
short O
afta O
one O
unfortunate O
incident O
wey O
involve O
police O
, O
but O
for O
di O
family O
and O
friends O
wey O
im O
leave O
behind O
, O
di O
memory O
of O
dia O
love O
one O
still O
fresh O
for O
mind O
. O

Tiamiyu B-PER
Fasasi I-PER
, O
wey O
bi O
Kazeem B-PER
papa O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Yoruba I-ORG
say O
e O
never O
reach O
like O
two B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
wen O
im O
pikin O
tell O
am O
say O
im O
get O
invitation O
to O
go O
play O
[ O
football O
] O
trial O
for O
Sweden B-LOC
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
very O
caring O
, O
e O
never O
fight O
anybodi O
before O
, O
and O
na O
pikin O
wey O
like O
to O
give O
. O

Im O
coach O
Daniel B-PER
Ogunmodede I-PER
, O
say O
na O
Kazeem B-PER
good O
behaviour O
make O
am O
promote O
Kazeem B-PER
to O
assistant O
captain O
, O
even O
though O
na O
four B-DATE
months I-DATE
ago I-DATE
im O
join O
dem O
. O

Tori O
break O
ontop O
social O
media O
afta O
Remo B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
football O
club O
release O
statement O
say O
SARS B-ORG
Police O
harass O
dia O
player O
Kazeem B-PER
wey O
lead O
to O
im O
death O
for O
Sagamu B-LOC
, O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
22 I-DATE
February I-DATE
. O

Dem O
say O
SARS B-ORG
bin O
claim O
Kazeem B-PER
na O
mago O
- O
mago O
pesin O
, O
even O
afta O
dia O
player O
show O
dem O
im O
ID O
card O
. O

And O
na O
during O
dis O
gbege O
with O
SARS B-ORG
anoda O
car O
hit O
and O
kill O
Kazeem B-PER
. O

I O
want O
fair O
and O
true O
justice O
from O
di O
federal O
goment O
and O
even O
from O
di O
police O
demsef O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Kazeem B-PER
papa O
say O
im O
want O
now O
. O

City B-ORG
go O
play O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
for O
di O
last O
16 O
of O
Champions O
League O
, O
di O
first O
leg O
go O
happun O
for O
Spain B-LOC
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

But O
I O
go O
say O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
na O
fantastic O
club O
. O
"""" O

Di O
American O
, O
34 B-DATE
, O
say O
im O
costume O
heavy O
so O
tey O
"""" O
legs O
weak O
am O
"""" O
for O
di O
fight O
. O

Fury B-PER
from O
Britain B-LOC
use O
ogbonge O
fight O
to O
win O
di O
title O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
after O
Wilder B-PER
pipo O
ask O
say O
make O
referee O
end O
di O
match O
for O
seventh O
round O
. O

Wilder B-PER
say O
di O
costume O
, O
wey O
dem O
sew O
plenty O
tins O
ontop O
am O
, O
also O
come O
wit O
mask O
and O
crown O
, O
weigh O
at O
least O
18 O
. O
1kg O
and O
na O
tribute O
to O
Black B-DATE
History I-DATE
Month I-DATE
. O

Fury B-PER
on O
di O
oda O
hand O
no O
use O
im O
leg O
waka O
enta O
ring O
as O
im O
sidon O
ontop O
throne O
wey O
four O
pipo O
carri O
. O

Although O
dem O
carri O
Wilder B-PER
go O
hospital O
after O
di O
fight O
, O
e O
say O
im O
no O
get O
concussion O
, O
say O
im O
ear O
drum O
no O
bust O
or O
im O
jaw O
break O
, O
like O
di O
way O
pipo O
dey O
tok O
. O

Former O
Brazil B-LOC
forward O
Ronaldinho B-PER
dey O
police O
custody O
for O
Paraguay B-LOC
ontop O
accuse O
say O
im O
use O
fake O
passport O
enta O
di O
kontri O
, O
according O
to O
authorities O
. O

Police O
search O
di O
hotel O
for O
di O
capital O
, O
Asuncion B-LOC
, O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
, O
wia O
im O
dey O
stay O
wit O
im O
brother O
. O

E O
also O
add O
say O
dem O
go O
investigate O
dia O
own O
customers O
authorities O
join O
. O

Ronaldinho B-PER
dey O
Paraguay B-LOC
to O
promote O
one O
book O
and O
do O
campaign O
for O
underprivileged O
pikin O
dem O
. O

One O
former O
rugby O
league O
player O
, O
im O
wife O
and O
dia O
three O
children O
die O
inside O
fire O
for O
di O
Australian O
city O
of O
Brisbane B-LOC
. O

"""" O
Dis O
na O
horrific O
scene O
, O
"""" O
Det O
Insp O
Mark B-PER
Thompson I-PER
tel O
tori O
pipo O
: O
"""" O
We O
still O
dey O
investigate O
di O
mata O
, O
but O
wen O
police O
reach O
di O
crime O
scene O
di O
car O
dey O
burn O
. O

Rowan B-PER
Baxter I-PER
bin O
dey O
for O
di O
front O
passenger O
seat O
and O
Hannah B-PER
Baxter I-PER
bin O
dey O
drive O
di O
car O
, O
police O
tok O
. O

Pipo O
wey O
dey O
live O
for O
di O
area O
tell O
Australian O
tori O
pipo O
say O
dem O
see O
madam O
Baxter B-PER
, O
31 B-DATE
, O
jump O
comot O
from O
di O
car O
wen O
she O
dey O
on O
fire O
. O

But O
dem O
confam O
am O
say O
she O
later O
die O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
. O

Tickets O
for O
dia O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
fights O
dey O
go O
for O
thousands O
of O
dollars O
, O
already O
di O
fighters O
dey O
badmouth O
each O
oda O
ahead O
of O
di O
fight O
. O

Dis O
na O
everything O
you O
need O
to O
know O
about O
di O
fight O
. O

In O
terms O
of O
money O
for O
di O
two O
men O
dia O
money O
fit O
reach O
eight O
- O
figure O
for O
dat O
night B-DATE
alone O
. O

"""" O
I O
don O
dey O
here O
for O
25 B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
I O
neva O
see O
dis O
kind O
investment O
for O
pay O
- O
per O
- O
view O
fight O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
boxing O
correspondent O
Mike B-PER
Costello I-PER
tok O
. O

Costello B-PER
add O
say O
: O
I O
feel O
say O
Wilder B-PER
don O
learn O
from O
im O
first O
fight O
and O
e O
go O
dey O
better O
dis O
time O
to O
close O
di O
space O
dem O
. O

And O
yes O
, O
e O
go O
dey O
controversial O
. O
"""" O

Sabi O
pipo O
and O
betting O
pipo O
dey O
divided O
. O

"""" O
Dis O
na O
di O
moment O
we O
don O
dey O
wait O
for O
tey O
- O
tey O
, O
"""" O
dat O
na O
wetin O
Wilder B-PER
tok O
dis B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

Fury B-PER
get O
new O
cuts O
man O
- O
in O
case O
di O
wound O
wey O
need O
47 O
stitches O
after O
im O
September B-DATE
win O
over O
Otto B-PER
Wallin I-PER
open O
again O
- O
and O
im O
also O
hire O
di O
chef O
wey O
UFC B-ORG
star O
Conor B-PER
McGregor I-PER
dey O
use O
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
go O
host O
CHAN O
2020 B-DATE
from O
4 B-DATE
- I-DATE
25 I-DATE
April I-DATE
and O
na O
one O
of O
de O
kontris O
for O
announce O
say O
two O
pipo O
don O
test O
positive O
for O
coronavirus O
recently O
. O

One O
player O
chop O
five B-DATE
years I-DATE
suspension O
for O
France B-LOC
sake O
of O
say O
im O
bite O
im O
opponent O
penis O
for O
fight O
wey O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
. O

Di O
incident O
happun O
afta O
dia O
match O
for O
di O
stadium O
car O
park O
. O

Saling B-PER
say O
because O
di O
'case O
dey O
quite O
original' O
, O
di O
disciplinary O
committee O
call O
expert O
witness O
before O
dem O
decide O
to O
suspend O
di O
Soetrich B-ORG
player O
for O
five B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

Afta O
Fury B-PER
win O
e O
come O
begin O
dey O
bounce O
around O
with O
di O
WBC O
world O
heavyweight O
belt O
wey O
dey O
on O
top O
im O
shoulder O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
box O
out O
of O
im O
skin O
and O
I O
no O
know O
say O
e O
fit O
do O
dis O
. O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
new O
signing O
Odion B-PER
Ighalo I-PER
dey O
train O
separate O
from O
wia O
oda O
players O
of O
di O
club O
dey O
train O
. O

United B-ORG
say O
na O
step O
wey O
dem O
take O
becos O
of O
di O
risk O
of O
Coronavirus O
as O
Ighalo B-PER
dey O
come O
from O
China B-LOC
wia O
di O
virus O
don O
kill O
more O
dan O
1000 O
pipo O
. O

BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
understand O
say O
Ighalo B-PER
don O
dey O
train O
with O
support O
from O
di O
club O
as O
im O
dey O
use O
personalised O
fitness O
programme O
to O
ready O
am O
for O
di O
Chelsea B-ORG
Premier O
League O
game O
. O

Na O
for O
di O
National B-ORG
Taekwondo I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
wey O
dey O
close O
to O
Etihad B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
and O
wia O
im O
don O
dey O
stay O
dem O
dey O
use O
since O
e O
land O
from O
China B-LOC
11 B-DATE
days I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

Ighalo B-PER
join O
United B-ORG
on O
loan O
for O
di O
rest O
of O
di O
season O
from O
China B-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
club O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
. O

Yobo B-PER
wey O
play O
for O
six O
Nations O
Cup O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
as O
defender O
go O
replace O
Imama B-PER
Amapakabo I-PER
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
technical O
crew O
. O

Di O
defender O
play O
for O
three O
World O
Cups O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
bin O
be O
di O
captain O
of O
di O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
wen O
dem O
win O
di O
2013 B-DATE
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

Yobo B-PER
wey O
play O
100 O
matches O
for O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
also O
play O
for O
Everton B-ORG
, O
Fenerbahce B-ORG
, O
Marseille B-ORG
, O
Standard B-ORG
Liege I-ORG
and O
Norwich B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

Dem O
don O
kick O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
comot O
from O
Champions O
League O
until O
2022 B-DATE
. O

City B-ORG
dey O
vex O
, O
dem O
claim O
say O
na O
di O
court O
no O
follow O
law O
to O
find O
dem O
guilty O
and O
dem O
promise O
say O
di O
fight O
neva O
finish O
. O

Wetin O
go O
determine O
di O
future O
of O
Guardiola B-PER
for O
Man B-ORG
City I-ORG
na O
if O
di O
club O
dey O
succesful O
for O
dia O
appeal O
against O
UEFA B-ORG
. O

We O
alreadi O
know O
say O
veteran O
midfielder O
David B-PER
Silva I-PER
go O
comot O
for O
end O
of O
dis O
season O
. O

But O
di O
number O
of O
players O
wey O
dia O
contracts O
go O
expire O
before O
City B-ORG
go O
return O
back O
to O
Champions O
League O
na O
mata O
wey O
dey O
worry O
. O

Leroy B-PER
Sane I-PER
deal O
go O
ends O
at O
the O
same O
time O
. O

And O
what O
about O
di O
stars O
wey O
dia O
contract O
dey O
go O
pass O
2022 B-DATE
, O
like O
Kevin B-PER
de I-PER
Bruyne I-PER
, O
Ederson B-PER
, O
Bernardo B-PER
Silva I-PER
, O
Raheem B-PER
Sterling I-PER
, O
Bernardo B-PER
Silva I-PER
and O
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
? O

"""" O
'My O
agent O
want O
to O
speak O
to O
you O
, O
United B-ORG
dey O
come O
for O
me O
, O
you O
need O
to O
make O
dis O
happun' O
. O
"""" O

I O
want O
to O
come O
here' O
, O
"""" O
Ighalo B-PER
add O
. O

"""" O
I O
come O
reply O
say O
: O
'I O
no O
care O
oh O
. O

I O
want O
to O
go O
join O
United B-ORG
. O

I O
no O
care O
how O
much O
be O
di O
pay O
- O
cut O
, O
I O
know O
dat O
, O
make O
e O
just O
happun' O
. O
"""" O

Ighalo B-PER
say O
e O
don O
tey O
wey O
im O
na O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
fan O
, O
na O
since O
wen O
im O
be O
small O
boy O
and O
e O
dey O
happy O
say O
im O
dream O
to O
play O
for O
di O
Old B-LOC
Trafford I-LOC
club O
don O
come O
through O
. O

Di O
Nigerian O
striker O
fly O
from O
China B-LOC
come O
Manchester B-LOC
last B-DATE
weekend I-DATE
afta O
di O
club O
sign O
am O
on O
loan O
from O
Shanghai B-ORG
Shenhua I-ORG
. O

"""" O
But O
di O
risk O
[ O
of O
border O
restrictions O
wey O
don O
tight O
now O
] O
sake O
of O
di O
coronavirus O
we O
know O
want O
take O
chances O
. O
"""" O

Tori O
be O
say O
United B-ORG
go O
return O
back O
on O
Friday B-DATE
before O
dia O
Premier O
League O
game O
against O
Chelsea B-ORG
for O
Stamford B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
on O
Monday B-DATE
, I-DATE
17 I-DATE
February I-DATE
. O

Most O
importantly O
him O
na O
correct O
human O
being O
wit O
a O
great O
personality O
and O
im O
leadership O
qualities O
dey O
clear O
for O
all O
to O
see O
. O

United B-ORG
go O
pay O
initial O
fee O
of O
around O
55m O
euros O
( O
£ O
47m O
) O
for O
di O
25 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
plus O
oda O
add O
- O
ons O
wey O
fit O
increase O
di O
overall O
cost O
to O
80m O
euros O
( O
£ O
67 O
. O
6m O
) O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
two O
clubs O
don O
dey O
negotiate O
throughout O
di O
transfer O
window O
until O
Tuesday B-DATE
wey O
dem O
get O
breakthrough O
afta O
reports O
begin O
fly O
up O
and O
down O
say O
Barcelona B-ORG
sef O
dey O
interested O
. O

Di O
negotiation O
between O
di O
club O
dey O
good O
and O
we O
know O
say O
from O
time O
, O
dis O
two O
clubs O
don O
dey O
good O
to O
each O
oda O
. O

Fernandes B-PER
join O
Sporting B-ORG
from O
Sampdoria B-ORG
for O
£ O
7 O
. O
2m O
for O
2017 B-DATE
but O
before O
den O
, O
im O
no O
really O
dey O
popular O
for O
im O
homeland O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Pipo O
for O
media O
dey O
ask O
why O
Benfica B-ORG
, O
Sporting B-ORG
or O
Porto B-ORG
no O
go O
for O
Fernandes B-PER
because O
im O
be O
fantastic O
player O
. O
"""" O

For O
Italy B-LOC
, O
im O
do O
well O
. O

Di O
wife O
of O
late O
Kobe B-PER
Bryant I-PER
, O
Vanessa B-PER
share O
foto O
of O
her O
daughter O
Gianna B-PER
"""" I-PER
Gigi I-PER
"""" I-PER
Bryant I-PER
, O
for O
social O
media O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

Di O
post O
don O
already O
get O
ova O
2 O
. O
3m O
likes O
. O

"""" O
Na O
correct O
pesin O
in O
be O
and O
im O
dey O
very O
professional O
, O
im O
go O
make O
use O
of O
im O
time O
here O
well O
. O
"""" O

United B-ORG
na O
one O
of O
di O
most O
popular O
clubs O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
and O
as O
soon O
as O
fans O
hear O
di O
tori O
about O
Ighalo B-PER
move O
dem O
begin O
chook O
mouth O
ontop O
di O
mata O
for O
social O
media O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
fourth O
edition O
of O
di O
marathon O
wey O
start O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
commercial O
capital O
city O
for O
2016 B-DATE
. O

Di B-ORG
Hammers I-ORG
last O
defeat O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
don O
carri O
dem O
down O
to O
17th O
position O
for O
di O
relegation O
zone O
of O
Premier O
League O
. O

Na O
just O
40 B-DATE
seconds I-DATE
McGregor B-PER
use O
defeat O
am O
. O

But O
referee O
Herb B-PER
Dean I-PER
step O
inside O
and O
wave O
say O
di O
contest O
contest O
don O
end O
afta O
blow O
afta O
blow O
land O
ontop O
'Cowbow' B-PER
"""" O
I O
make O
history O
tonight B-DATE
. O

"""" O
I O
like O
dis O
weight O
division O
. O

I O
feel O
really O
good O
. O

I O
still O
work O
to O
do O
to O
return O
to O
how O
I O
be O
before O
. O
"""" O

Mohamed B-PER
Salah I-PER
( O
Egypt B-LOC
& O
Liverpool B-ORG
) O
Riyad B-PER
Mahrez I-PER
( O
Algeria B-LOC
& O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
) O
Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
( O
Senegal B-LOC
& O
Liverpool B-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Ajara B-PER
Nchout I-PER
( O
Cameroon B-LOC
& O
Valerenga B-ORG
) O
Asisat B-PER
Oshoala I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Barcelona B-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Thembi B-PER
Kgatlana I-PER
( O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
& O
Beijing B-ORG
Phoenix I-ORG
FC I-ORG
) O
Anice B-PER
Badri I-PER
( O
Tunisia B-LOC
& O
Esperance B-ORG
) O
Tarek B-PER
Hamed I-PER
( O
Egypt B-LOC
& O
Zamalek B-ORG
) O
Youcef B-PER
Belaïli I-PER
( O
Algeria B-LOC
& O
Esperance B-ORG
/ O
Ahli B-ORG
Jeddah I-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Achraf B-PER
Hakimi I-PER
( O
Morocco B-LOC
& O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
) O
- O
Winner O
Samuel B-PER
Chukwueze I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Villarreal B-ORG
) O
Victor B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
( O
Nigeria B-LOC
& O
Lille B-ORG
) O
Aliou B-PER
Cisse I-PER
( O
Senegal B-LOC
- O
Senegal B-LOC
) O
Djamel B-PER

Di O
decade O
also O
end O
wit O
di O
2019 B-DATE
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
wey O
hold O
for O
June B-DATE
and O
July B-DATE
for O
di O
first O
time O
instead O
of O
di O
usual O
January B-DATE
to O
February B-DATE
calendar O
. O

Im O
go O
on O
to O
keep O
11 O
consecutive O
clean O
sheets O
while O
with O
Lille B-ORG
and O
bin O
dey O
115 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
away O
from O
beating O
Ligue O
1 O
all O
- O
time O
record O
of O
minutes O
- O
of O
- O
clean O
- O
sheets O
set O
by O
Gaetan B-PER
Huard I-PER
for O
1993 B-DATE
wia O
e O
play O
1 B-DATE
, I-DATE
176 I-DATE
minutes I-DATE
without O
conceding O
one O
goal O
. O

Di O
former O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
captain O
bin O
be O
key O
member O
of O
di O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
side O
wey O
win O
di O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
for O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Di O
Cameroonian O
peak O
for O
Tottenham B-ORG
for O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
and O
na O
one O
of O
di O
best O
left O
backs O
for O
Premier O
League O
under O
Harry B-PER
Redknapp I-PER
. O

Unfortunately O
for O
Assou B-PER
- I-PER
Ekotto I-PER
, O
knee O
surgery O
mean O
say O
im O
career O
go O
pay O
di O
price O
but O
e O
be O
pesin O
wey O
pass O
expectations O
and O
become O
di O
best O
African O
left O
- O
back O
for O
Premier O
League O
. O

Benatia B-PER
bin O
be O
big O
influence O
for O
Italian O
Serie O
A O
side O
Udinese B-ORG
, O
but O
na O
for O
AS B-ORG
Roma I-ORG
wia O
di O
world O
take O
notice O
of O
am O
. O

Di O
only O
reason O
e O
still O
dey O
Napoli B-ORG
na O
say O
di O
club O
owner O
turn O
down O
many O
offers O
from O
top O
European O
outfits O
so O
far O
. O

Essien B-PER
prowess O
begin O
to O
die O
down O
just O
for O
di O
turn O
of O
di O
decade O
with O
injuries O
taking O
dia O
toll O
but O
e O
bin O
still O
dey O
important O
for O
Ghana B-LOC
as O
dem O
qualify O
for O
di O
World O
Cup O
for O
2014 B-DATE
and O
- O
e O
insists O
say O
im O
deserve O
place O
for O
e O
team O
of O
di O
decade O
! O

Yaya B-PER
don O
win O
di O
Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
African I-ORG
Football I-ORG
( O
Caf B-ORG
) O
African O
Player O
of O
the O
Year O
award O
four O
times O
in O
di O
last O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

E O
also O
score O
79 O
goals O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
di O
most O
by O
any O
midfielder O
for O
di O
club O
during O
dat O
period O
. O

E O
also O
captain O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
to O
dia O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
crown O
for O
2015 B-DATE
. O

Salah B-PER
don O
exceed O
expectations O
for O
Liverpool B-ORG
wia O
e O
win O
di O
Premier O
League O
Golden O
Boot O
for O
di O
two B-DATE
seasons I-DATE
with O
di O
club O
so O
far O
. O

For O
di O
beginning O
of O
di O
decade O
Drogba B-PER
reach O
im O
career O
high O
of O
37 O
goals O
to O
help O
Chelsea B-ORG
win O
domestic O
Cup O
double O
and O
also O
win O
e O
second O
Premier O
League O
Golden O
Boot O
. O

E O
trophy O
winning O
continue O
afta O
e O
leave O
Chelsea B-ORG
with O
three O
more O
for O
Turkey B-LOC
as O
e O
help O
Galatasaray B-ORG
win O
di O
league O
, O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
and O
Super O
Cup O
. O

Im O
move O
to O
England B-LOC
for O
di O
end O
of O
e O
career O
, O
and O
even O
though O
e O
no O
shine O
at O
dat O
point O
e O
still O
manage O
one O
memorable O
hat O
- O
trick O
for O
Chelsea B-ORG
against O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
. O

"""" O
I O
no O
go O
fit O
continue O
to O
play O
like O
dat O
"""" O
dis O
na O
wetin O
Seven O
time O
champion O
Serena B-PER
Williams I-PER
tok O
afta O
she O
crash O
comot O
from O
Australian O
Open O
on O
Friday B-DATE
morning I-DATE
and O
lose O
6 O
- O
4 O
6 O
- O
7 O
( O
2 O
- O
7 O
) O
7 O
- O
5 O
to O
Wang B-PER
Qiang I-PER
from O
China B-LOC
for O
third O
round O
. O

E O
dey O
unprofessional O
. O

Wang B-PER
bin O
dey O
serve O
for O
di O
match O
when O
di O
game O
dey O
5 O
- O
4 O
but O
Williams B-PER
broke O
her O
for O
di O
first O
time O
come O
win O
di O
tie O
- O
break O
to O
level O
di O
game O
. O

Di O
28 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
Wang B-PER
wey O
be O
number O
27th O
seed O
for O
world O
tennis O
ranking O
, O
recover O
come O
seal O
victory O
for O
her O
third O
match O
point O
. O

Dis O
na O
Williams B-PER
23rd B-DATE
year I-DATE
as O
professional O
tennis O
player O
and O
she O
still O
dey O
eye O
Margaret B-PER
Court I-PER
record O
of O
24 O
grand O
slam O
singles O
titles O
. O

Di O
last O
time O
wey O
38 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
Serena B-PER
win O
grand O
slam O
na O
2017 B-DATE
when O
she O
beat O
her O
sister O
for O
Australian O
Open O
final O
to O
win O
her O
23rd O
title O
and O
na O
di O
same B-DATE
year I-DATE
she O
born O
her O
daughter O
too O
. O

Leicester B-ORG
manage O
to O
match O
brake O
for O
di O
ginger O
wey O
Brentford B-ORG
carri O
come O
for O
second O
half O
of O
dem O
two O
FA B-ORG
Cup O
fourth O
round O
match O
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
very O
important O
as O
one O
team O
and O
as O
one O
group O
of O
players O
. O

Ogbonge O
football O
fans O
dey O
get O
one O
kain O
deep O
level O
of O
physical O
stress O
wen O
dem O
dey O
watch O
dia O
team O
dey O
play O
and O
dem O
fit O
give O
diasef O
heart O
attack O
, O
na O
so O
research O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Fans O
wey O
too O
join O
togeda O
emotionally O
with O
dia O
team O
, O
wey O
get O
strong O
sense O
say O
dem O
be O
one O
with O
dia O
team O
dey O
experience O
di O
greatest O
psychological O
stress O
response O
wen O
dem O
dey O
watch O
match O
"""" O
, O
Dr O
Martha B-PER
Newson I-PER
, O
researcher O
for O
di O
Centre B-ORG
for I-ORG
di I-ORG
Study I-ORG
of I-ORG
Social I-ORG
Cohesion I-ORG
for O
Oxford B-ORG
tok O
. O

"""" O
Fans O
wey O
be O
casual O
supporters O
dey O
also O
experience O
stress O
but O
e O
no O
dey O
serious O
like O
dat O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
Clubs O
fit O
dey O
do O
heart O
screening O
or O
oda O
health O
measures O
for O
dia O
fans O
wey O
dey O
committed O
because O
na O
dem O
dey O
at O
risk O
to O
experience O
stress O
during O
di O
game O
, O
"""" O
she O
add O
. O

As O
di O
day O
waka O
dey O
go O
, O
unconfam O
reports O
of O
shooting O
, O
wey O
involve O
Togo B-LOC
national O
team O
, O
start O
to O
fly O
evriwia O
. O

Players O
bin O
just O
dey O
laugh O
and O
joking O
amongst O
demselves O
for O
di O
bus O
. O

Angola B-LOC
security O
forces O
join O
dem O
for O
di O
border O
and O
suppose O
escort O
dem O
through O
di O
forest O
- O
wey O
be O
di O
base O
of O
one O
groups O
wey O
dey O
call O
for O
independence O
from O
Angola B-LOC
- O
to O
Cabinda B-LOC
city I-LOC
. O

I O
remember O
afta O
15 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
wey O
we O
don O
dey O
drive O
we O
hear O
gunshot O
for O
di O
forest O
- O
we O
all O
laugh O
, O
make O
joke O
. O

Di O
first O
casualty O
happen O
before O
anybody O
even O
know O
wetin O
dey O
go O
on O
. O

Dem O
shoot O
kill O
am O
. O

Im O
life O
change O
for O
just O
few O
seconds O
, O
as O
e O
realise O
say O
dem O
don O
shoot O
am O
too O
. O

"""" O
Dat O
na O
wen O
I O
see O
myself O
- O
both O
my O
belle O
and O
my O
back O
begin O
bleed O
. O

I O
no O
wan O
die O
here O
. O
' O
"""" O

E O
remember O
one O
team O
- O
mate O
wey O
get O
military O
training O
call O
for O
weapon O
, O
so O
dat O
e O
go O
fit O
fight O
back O
. O

Memories O
of O
how O
long O
e O
last O
dey O
different O
, O
but O
everyone O
agree O
say O
na O
at O
least O
30 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
e O
last O
. O

Our O
bus O
bin O
don O
stop O
and O
pipo O
bin O
don O
dey O
shoot O
our O
bus O
for O
30 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
. O

Maybe O
na O
my O
dead O
body O
you O
fit O
dey O
tok O
to O
. O
"""" O

Accounts O
of O
how O
e O
all O
end O
different O
- O
Adebayor B-PER
describe O
one O
fleet O
of O
4x4 O
vehicles O
arrive O
to O
take O
di O
squad O
away O
even O
as O
dem O
still O
dey O
shoot O
from O
di O
forest O
, O
while O
Senaya B-PER
remember O
silence O
. O

Throughout O
di O
meal O
, O
evriwia O
bin O
dey O
silent O
. O

Anoda O
question O
lie O
for O
di O
presence O
Angolan O
security O
wey O
travel O
with O
di O
team O
. O

And O
na O
di O
militarised O
escort O
cause O
di O
attack O
? O

None O
of O
dis O
questions O
get O
clear O
answers O
, O
even O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
on O
- O
and O
at O
di O
time O
di O
most O
immediate O
issue O
for O
di O
players O
na O
to O
absorb O
wetin O
don O
happen O
to O
dem O
and O
decide O
wetin O
to O
do O
next O
. O

Rumours O
suggest O
say O
split O
bin O
dey O
between O
those O
for O
camp O
wey O
want O
continue O
wit O
di O
tournament O
and O
those O
wey O
want O
go O
home O
. O

Two O
pipo O
bin O
die O
and O
a O
number O
of O
odas O
seriously O
wound O
- O
di O
worst O
na O
di O
goalkeeper O
, O
Obilale B-PER
. O

Dat O
no O
dey O
true O
, O
but O
e O
suffer O
serious O
damage O
to O
im O
spine O
, O
intestines O
, O
liver O
and O
bladder O
, O
and O
dem O
transfer O
am O
go O
hospital O
for O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
, O
to O
begin O
e O
recovery O
. O

I O
go O
back O
to O
school O
, O
take O
exams O
, O
work O
and O
write O
book O
, O
"""" O
im O
tok O
. O

For O
long O
time O
im O
work O
wit O
children O
with O
special O
needs O
, O
as O
e O
help O
dem O
through O
di O
medium O
of O
football O
, O
and O
e O
don O
set O
up O
e O
own O
organisation O
to O
continue O
dat O
work O
. O

Obilale B-PER
lose O
e O
livelihood O
- O
and O
almost O
e O
life O
- O
for O
Cabinda B-LOC
and O
e O
dey O
striking O
say O
im O
tok O
say O
na O
since O
only O
di O
change O
in O
leadership O
for O
di O
Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
African I-ORG
Football I-ORG
for O
2017 B-DATE
, O
wen O
current O
president O
Ahmad B-PER
comot O
Issa B-PER
Hayatou I-PER
, O
na O
im O
e O
don O
get O
any O
meaningful O
contact O
wit O
di O
continental O
governing O
body O
. O

Odas O
na O
e O
former O
captain O
Adebayor B-PER
and O
Ghana B-LOC
Ayew B-PER
brothers O
- O
Andre B-PER
Ayew I-PER
and O
e O
brother O
Rahim B-PER
bin O
dey O
part O
of O
di O
Black B-ORG
Stars I-ORG
squad O
wey O
play O
for O
Cabinda B-LOC
for O
2010 B-DATE
. O

"""" O
I O
really O
no O
fit O
recover O
. O
. O
. O

But O
no O
one O
fit O
deny O
di O
human O
cost O
of O
dat O
short O
bus O
trip O
for O
Cabinda B-LOC
, O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Super B-ORG
Falcons I-ORG
captain O
, O
Asisat B-PER
Oshoala I-PER
say O
she O
want O
'create O
her O
own O
history' O
afta O
she O
win O
di O
2019 B-DATE
Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
African I-ORG
Football I-ORG
( O
Caf B-ORG
) O
Women O
Player O
of O
di O
Year O
award O
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

"""" O
E O
dey O
keep O
me O
going O
but O
of O
course O
work O
still O
dey O
to O
do O
, O
I O
want O
to O
create O
my O
own O
history O
and O
not O
just O
equal O
someone O
else O
record O
- O
I O
go O
give O
my O
best O
to O
create O
my O
own O
. O
"""" O

She O
say O
she O
no O
dey O
take O
di O
fourth O
win O
for O
granted O
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
actually O
tense O
about O
dis O
, O
but O
na O
historical O
night B-DATE
for O
me O
, O
"""" O
she O
tok O
Nkwocha B-PER
, O
wey O
be O
five O
- O
time O
Women O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
winner O
, O
claim O
di O
award O
back O
- O
to O
- O
back O
for O
2004 B-DATE
and O
2005 B-DATE
and O
again O
for O
2010 B-DATE
and O
2011 B-DATE
. O

Im O
tok O
join O
: O
"""" O
Fans O
, O
pipo O
, O
no O
get O
sense O
again O
like O
dem O
get O
before O
. O
"""" O

For O
2020 B-DATE
, O
2025 B-DATE
we O
go O
get O
young O
pikin O
dem O
wey O
don O
grow O
- O
wetin O
we O
go O
come O
do O
? O

Im O
go O
replace O
Unai B-PER
Emery I-PER
wey O
Arsenal B-ORG
sack O
for O
early B-DATE
November I-DATE
but O
dem O
neva O
announce O
im O
coaching O
team O
yet O
. O

"""" O
We O
need O
to O
dey O
compete O
for O
di O
top O
trophies O
for O
di O
game O
, O
"""" O
na O
wetin O
Arteta B-PER
tok O
"""" O
Dat O
one O
dey O
very O
clear O
to O
me O
, O
when O
I O
discuss O
with O
di O
[ O
owners O
] O
Stan B-PER
and O
Josh B-PER
Kroenke I-PER
and O
senior O
pipo O
from O
di O
club O
. O
"""" O

Arsenal B-ORG
dey O
siddon O
for O
number O
10 O
position O
for O
Premier O
League O
table O
with O
22 O
points O
. O

Di O
37 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
na O
former O
Arsenal B-ORG
club O
captain O
, O
wey O
play O
five O
seasons O
for O
di O
club O
, O
from O
2011 B-DATE
to O
2016 B-DATE
. O

As O
player O
for O
di O
club O
im O
win O
two O
FA B-ORG
Cups O
titles O
. O

Before O
im O
join O
Arsenal B-ORG
as O
dia O
new O
manager O
im O
bin O
dey O
part O
of O
Pep B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
coaching O
staff O
for O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O

Kamaru B-PER
kpo O
- O
kpo O
Covington B-PER
patapata O
for O
di O
last O
round O
, O
and O
put O
am O
for O
ground O
two O
times O
with O
two O
big O
punch O
, O
e O
come O
begin O
dey O
punch O
am O
, O
punch O
am O
before O
referee O
Marc B-PER
Goddard I-PER
come O
dey O
force O
to O
shout O
say O
di O
fight O
don O
do O
oh O
! O

Covington B-PER
even O
insult O
Kamaru B-PER
say O
im O
dey O
claim O
to O
be O
"""" O
di O
first O
Nigerian O
- O
born O
, O
African O
champion O
, O
whereas O
dem O
born O
am O
for O
Dallas B-LOC
. O
"""" O

I O
get O
di O
responsibility O
to O
go O
inside O
dia O
and O
teach O
am O
lesson O
. O
"""" O

E O
return O
to O
English O
football O
eight B-DATE
and I-DATE
a I-DATE
half I-DATE
years I-DATE
afta O
Chelsea B-ORG
sack O
am O
. O

Everton B-ORG
announce O
Ancelotti B-PER
arrival O
on O
Saturday B-DATE
before O
di O
home O
Premier O
League O
game O
against O
Arsenal B-ORG
, O
wey O
appoint O
former O
Gunners B-ORG
and O
Toffees B-ORG
midfielder O
Mikel B-PER
Arteta I-PER
as O
dia O
head O
coach O
on O
Friday B-DATE
. O

Ancelotti B-PER
wey O
be O
60 B-DATE
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
go O
officially O
take O
ova O
Sunday B-DATE
and O
im O
first O
match O
in O
charge O
go O
be O
di O
home O
game O
against O
Burnley B-ORG
on O
26 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

Ancelotti B-PER
don O
win O
15 O
major O
trophies O
during O
im O
career O
and O
im O
na O
one O
of O
only O
three O
managers O
to O
win O
three O
European O
Cups O
/ O
Champions O
Leagues O
- O
along O
with O
Liverpool B-ORG
legend O
Bob B-PER
Paisley I-PER
and O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
boss O
Zinedine B-PER
Zidane I-PER
. O

Everton B-ORG
director O
of O
football O
, O
Marcel B-PER
Brands I-PER
tok O
say O
Ancelotti B-PER
na O
"""" O
one O
of O
di O
finest O
managers O
for O
di O
world O
football O
"""" O
and O
na O
"""" O
proven O
winner O
"""" O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Welterweight O
champion O
Kamaru B-PER
Usman I-PER
, O
go O
fight O
Colby B-PER
Covington I-PER
for O
UFC B-ORG
245 O
inside O
octagon O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
, O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
on O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
na O
three O
title O
fights O
go O
happun O
but O
na O
Kamuru B-PER
fight O
na O
im O
be O
di O
main O
event O
of O
di O
night B-DATE
, O
sake O
of O
say O
di O
two O
fighters O
don O
dey O
eye O
each O
oda O
since O
. O

Di O
Nigerian O
neva O
lose O
for O
im O
last O
14 O
fights O
for O
UFC B-ORG
. O

Usman B-PER
get O
six O
career O
knockout O
win O
and O
one O
submission O
victory O
. O

Di O
American O
neva O
lose O
for O
im O
last O
seven O
fight O
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
real O
. O

Plenti O
fighters O
dey O
fear O
to O
fall O
. O
Me O
I O
know O
dey O
fear O
to O
fall O
becos O
I O
know O
say O
I O
be O
winner O
and O
I O
go O
continue O
to O
win O
. O
"""" O

Tori O
be O
say O
Usman B-PER
and O
Covington B-PER
go O
make O
$ O
500 O
, O
000 O
each O
for O
dis O
dia O
fight O
. O

Oda O
Boxing O
Day O
matches O
see O
Chelsea B-ORG
surprisingly O
lose O
2 O
- O
0 O
to O
Southampton B-ORG
for O
Stamford B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
while O
Tottenham B-ORG
come O
from O
behind O
to O
beat O
Brighton B-ORG
2 O
- O
1 O
. O

Carlo B-PER
Ancelotti I-PER
begin O
life O
as O
new O
coach O
of O
Everton B-ORG
with O
1 O
- O
0 O
win O
ova O
Burnley B-ORG
for O
Goodison B-LOC
Park I-LOC
. O

Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
sama O
Newcastle B-ORG
4 O
- O
1 O
for O
Old B-LOC
Trafford I-LOC
. O

Wilder B-PER
say O
na O
since O
like O
June B-DATE
na O
im O
dem O
don O
sign O
agreement O
for O
rematch O
, O
but O
say O
e O
go O
be O
afta O
im O
first O
fight O
Luis B-PER
Ortiz I-PER
from O
Cuba B-LOC
, O
wey O
im O
defeat O
for O
MGM B-LOC
Grand I-LOC
for O
November B-DATE
. O

No O
fighter O
don O
ever O
carry O
all O
four O
major O
world O
titles O
for O
di O
heavyweight O
division O
. O

Aboudi B-PER
Onguéné I-PER
Gabrielle I-PER
, O
captain O
for O
Cameroon B-LOC
women O
national O
team O
, O
president O
for O
"""" O
Terre B-ORG
Promise' I-ORG
association I-ORG
, O
say O
e O
wan O
komot O
women O
football O
from O
'darkness' O
. O

Di O
Russian O
champion O
for O
2019 B-DATE
with O
CSKA B-ORG
Mosco I-ORG
make O
de O
statement O
for O
'GO7 O
Awards' O
prize O
award O
weh O
e O
organise O
for O
compensate O
de O
pipo O
weh O
deh O
work O
hard O
for O
2018 B-DATE
football O
season O
. O

Na O
de O
first O
prize O
award O
weh O
player O
weh O
e O
still O
bi O
active O
wit O
national O
team O
don O
organise O
for O
encourage O
women O
football O
. O

"""" O
We O
wan O
komot O
football O
from O
darkness O
, O
na O
why O
we O
organise O
de O
awards O
. O

Cameroon B-LOC
women O
football O
shine O
for O
world O
stage O
for O
2015 B-DATE
wen O
Lionesses O
go O
World O
Cup O
for O
de O
first O
taim O
wit O
players O
laik O
Aboudi B-PER
weh O
deh O
take O
de O
team O
for O
knock O
out O
stage O
. O

Aboudi B-PER
, O
striker O
for O
national O
team O
, O
football O
for O
yi O
na O
gift O
, O
and O
as O
player O
weh O
e O
start O
for O
young O
age O
di O
play O
wit O
boys O
dem O
, O
say O
na O
e O
own O
small O
contribution O
for O
komot O
women O
football O
from O
darkness O
. O

"""" O
We O
no O
bi O
know O
say O
woman O
football O
dey O
and O
plenti O
of O
we O
start O
play O
wit O
boys O
, O
na O
so O
ah O
develop O
, O
but O
as O
model O
for O
some O
players O
now O
ah O
wan O
motivate O
dem O
"""" O
, O
Aboudi B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
. O

"""" O
Ah O
glad O
as O
Aboudi B-PER
weh O
e O
don O
always O
encourage O
me O
don O
start O
dis O
award O
, O
na O
big O
push O
for O
woman O
dem O
"""" O
, O
de O
player O
tok O
. O

"""" O
Di O
referee O
need O
monitor O
to O
check O
if O
im O
dey O
right O
or O
wrong O
. O
. O
. O
For O
me O
, O
dis O
na O
di O
most O
important O
worry O
, O
"""" O
Wenger B-PER
tok O
. O

Liverpool B-ORG
midfielder O
James B-PER
Milner I-PER
no O
dey O
hide O
am O
say O
im O
no O
like O
VAR O
at O
all O
. O

Former O
players O
sef O
don O
chook O
mouth O
for O
di O
mata O
. O

For O
November B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
, O
Chelsea B-ORG
coach O
and O
former O
midfielder O
, O
Frank B-PER
Lampard I-PER
draw O
ear O
give O
anybody O
wey O
wan O
hear O
am O
say O
VAR O
fit O
dey O
"""" O
dangerous O
"""" O
for O
di O
Premier O
League O
. O

Premier O
League O
legends O
like O
Alan B-PER
Shearer I-PER
, O
Robbie B-PER
Fowler I-PER
and O
Phil B-PER
Neville I-PER
no O
happy O
at O
all O
wit O
di O
way O
tins O
dey O
go O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
true O
story O
, O
"""" O
Wenger B-PER
tok O
. O

I O
not O
fit O
ansa O
and O
by O
cool O
way O
I O
call O
am O
back O
. O

"""" O
Him O
bein O
dey O
inside O
him O
car O
dey O
go O
for O
di O
game O
against O
Olympiakos B-ORG
. O

We O
tok O
for O
four B-DATE
to O
five B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
maximum O
and O
he O
tell O
me O
say O
dem O
don O
assign O
[ O
Hans B-PER
- I-PER
Dieter I-PER
] O
Flick B-PER
to O
be O
be O
coach O
- O
him O
go O
manage O
di O
next O
two O
games O
. O

However O
, O
dem O
get O
a O
perfect O
record O
inside O
di O
Champions O
League O
and O
dia O
2 O
- O
0 O
win O
over O
Olympiakos B-ORG
inside O
Flick B-PER
first O
game O
wey O
dey O
in O
charge O
for O
di O
meantime O
, O
make O
am O
dia O
numebr O
four O
win O
in O
four O
group O
games O
. O

For O
di O
start O
of O
October B-DATE
, O
Bayern B-ORG
, O
still O
managed O
by O
Kovac B-PER
, O
thrash O
Tottenham B-ORG
7 O
- O
2 O
for O
away O
Champions O
League O
game O
in O
London B-LOC
. O

Dis O
tin O
fit O
make O
am O
better O
pesin O
, O
better O
fighter O
or O
e O
fit O
just O
destroy O
am O
"""" O
. O

Former O
world O
heavyweight O
champion O
Mike B-PER
Tyson I-PER
know O
how O
big O
Saturday B-DATE
night I-DATE
go O
be O
for O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
. O

Six B-DATE
months I-DATE
afta O
Joshua B-PER
lose O
to O
Andy B-PER
Ruiz I-PER
Jr I-PER
for O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
im O
get O
second O
chance O
to O
prove O
to O
imself O
. O

Muhammad B-PER
Ali I-PER
: O
On O
February B-DATE
15 I-DATE
, I-DATE
1978 I-DATE
Ali B-PER
lose O
im O
title O
to O
Leon B-PER
Spinks I-PER
for O
15 O
round O
split O
decision O
. O

Seven B-DATE
months I-DATE
later O
Ali B-PER
defeat O
Spinks B-PER
for O
15 O
rounds O
afta O
all O
di O
judges O
give O
am O
di O
victory O
. O

But O
Rahman B-PER
lose O
im O
rematch O
fight O
seven B-DATE
months I-DATE
later O
with O
Lewis B-PER
, O
as O
di O
Britain O
finish O
am O
with O
knockout O
for O
round O
four O
for O
Las B-LOC
Vegas I-LOC
. O

Foreman B-PER
win O
di O
fight O
on O
knockout O
afta O
im O
land O
Moorer B-PER
heavy O
blow O
for O
im O
chin O
. O

On O
November B-DATE
11 I-DATE
, I-DATE
1997 I-DATE
, O
Holyfield B-PER
and O
Moorer B-PER
meet O
again O
for O
rematch O
. O

Di O
big O
fight O
wey O
evri O
dey O
wait O
for O
dem O
title O
am O
unification O
rematch O
, O
and O
e O
go O
takes O
place O
on O
Dec B-DATE
. I-DATE
7 I-DATE
for O
Diriyah B-LOC
Arena I-LOC
- O
custom O
- O
built O
15 O
, O
000 O
- O
seater O
venue O
inside O
Diriyah B-LOC
, O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
. O

"""" O
I O
dey O
here O
to O
win O
, O
I O
no O
get O
fear O
for O
mind O
. O
. O
. O
, O
I O
don O
say O
my O
prayers O
and O
take O
time O
to O
embrace O
wetin O
go O
happun O
on O
for O
Saturday B-DATE
"""" O
Na O
wetin O
Joshua B-PER
tok O
. O

I O
know O
say O
im O
lost O
weight O
. O
. O
. O

Joshua B-PER
- O
Ruiz B-PER
Jr I-PER
Nationality O
: O
British O
- O
American O
/ O
Mexican O
Age O
: O
30 B-DATE
- O
30 B-DATE
Height O
: O
6ft O
6 O
- O
6ft O
2 O
Stance O
: O
Orthodox O
- O
Orthodox O
Reach O
: O
82 O
in O
- O
74 O
in O
Record O
: O
22 O
- O
1 O
- O
0 O
- O
33 O
- O
1 O
- O
0 O
KOs O
: O
21 O
- O
22 O
Rounds O
: O
91 O
- O
151 O
Debut O
: O
5 B-DATE
/ I-DATE
10 I-DATE
/ I-DATE
2013 I-DATE
- O
28 B-DATE
/ I-DATE
03 I-DATE
/ I-DATE
2009 I-DATE
Nickname O
: O
AJ B-PER
- O
Destroyer B-PER
Tori O
be O
say O
Joshua B-PER
dey O
set O
for O
one O
of O
di O
biggest O
ever O
paydays O
in O
boxing O
history O
. O

You O
fit O
watch O
di O
match O
here O
: O
Na O
Sky B-ORG
Sports I-ORG
and O
DAZN B-ORG
USA I-ORG
be O
di O
major O
tori O
pipo O
wey O
go O
show O
di O
fight O
. O

Deontay B-PER
Wilder I-PER
knockout O
Luis B-PER
Ortiz I-PER
to O
defend O
im O
WBC O
world O
heavyweight O
title O
for O
di O
10th O
time O
. O

Na O
only O
Tommy B-PER
Burns I-PER
( O
11 O
) O
, O
Vitali B-PER
Klitschko I-PER
( O
11 O
) O
, O
Wladimir B-PER
Klitschko I-PER
( O
18 O
) O
, O
Larry B-PER
Holmes I-PER
( O
20 O
) O
and O
Joe B-PER
Louis I-PER
( O
25 O
) O
don O
manage O
to O
defend O
dia O
heavyweight O
crown O
more O
times O
straight O
without O
defeat O
. O

Meanwhile O
plenti O
pipo O
for O
inside O
social O
media O
follow O
to O
jollificate O
with O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
afta O
im O
win O
. O

Some O
pipo O
even O
start O
dey O
learn O
moral O
lesson O
from O
di O
victory O
. O

Minister O
of O
Youths O
and O
Sports O
Development O
, O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
Sunday B-PER
Dare I-PER
, O
say O
Africa B-LOC
richest O
man O
Aliko B-PER
Dangote I-PER
godo O
collabo O
wit O
goment O
to O
repair O
di O
Moshood B-LOC
Abiola I-LOC
National I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
for O
Abuja B-LOC
, O
di O
kontri O
capital O
. O

Di O
$ O
360m O
stadium O
wey O
be O
di O
official O
home O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
national O
sport O
teams O
don O
turn O
to O
something O
else O
, O
16 B-DATE
years I-DATE
afta O
dem O
launch O
am O
for O
2003 B-DATE
. O

But O
today B-DATE
, O
na O
di O
opposite O
. O

Many O
of O
di O
stadiums O
for O
di O
kontri O
, O
like O
many O
goment O
structures O
, O
no O
dey O
get O
regular O
maintenance O
and O
dis O
na O
wetin O
fit O
don O
make O
di O
stadium O
bad O
well O
well O
. O

"""" O
If O
e O
happun O
to O
anyone O
of O
us O
, O
e O
happun O
to O
all O
of O
us O
, O
"""" O
Abraham B-PER
bin O
tok O
. O

Uefa B-ORG
bin O
order O
say O
make O
dem O
no O
fully O
open O
di O
Bulgaria B-LOC
national I-LOC
stadium I-LOC
afta O
racist O
behaviour O
wey O
dia O
fans O
show O
for O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
qualifying O
games O
against O
di O
Czech B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
and O
Kosovo B-LOC
for O
June B-DATE
. O

"""" O
If O
e O
happun O
and O
warning O
don O
sound O
comot O
for O
di O
stadium O
, O
and O
e O
come O
happun O
again O
, O
we O
go O
need O
to O
decide O
as O
one O
team O
and O
wit O
di O
staff O
, O
"""" O
Abraham B-PER
bin O
tok O
. O

Di O
president O
of O
di O
Bulgaria B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Union I-ORG
( O
BFU B-ORG
) O
, O
Borislav B-PER
Mihaylov I-PER
, O
don O
resign O
. O

Bulgaria B-LOC
Prime O
Minister O
Boyko B-PER
Borissov I-PER
ask O
am O
to O
carry O
im O
load O
waka O
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
afta O
di O
racist O
abuse O
of O
England B-LOC
players O
inside O
di O
Euro O
2020 B-DATE
qualifier O
for O
Sofia B-LOC
. O

Meanwhile O
di O
Bulgaria B-LOC
national O
team O
coach O
Krasimir B-PER
Balakov I-PER
say O
im O
no O
hear O
any O
of O
di O
racist O
chant O
on O
Monday B-DATE
. O

"""" O
E O
go O
pain O
me O
if O
e O
happun O
say O
na O
true O
. O
. O
. O
Me O
personally O
, O
I O
no O
hear O
di O
chanting O
, O
"""" O
Balakov B-PER
bin O
tok O
. O

Dis O
na O
afta O
Ivelin B-PER
Popov I-PER
bin O
go O
meet O
supporters O
for O
stadium O
to O
encourage O
dem O
to O
stop O
di O
racist O
behaviour O
. O

Earlier O
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
, O
di O
Bulgaria B-LOC
prime O
minister O
"""" O
strongly O
condemn O
"""" O
di O
behaviour O
of O
di O
fans O
and O
ask O
Mihalov B-PER
to O
resign O
"""" O
immediately O
"""" O
. O

Dis O
na O
di O
third O
time O
wey O
di O
African O
champions O
no O
go O
qualify O
for O
major O
sporting O
event O
wey O
dey O
happun O
everi O
four B-DATE
- I-DATE
four I-DATE
years I-DATE
: O
For O
2012 B-DATE
( O
London B-LOC
) O
and O
2016 B-DATE
( O
Rio B-LOC
de I-LOC
Janeiro I-LOC
) O
. O

Les B-ORG
Elephantes I-ORG
and O
Super B-ORG
Falcons I-ORG
bin O
play O
0 O
- O
0 O
draw O
for O
Abidjan B-LOC
four B-DATE
days I-DATE
earlier I-DATE
, O
and O
Nigeria B-LOC
be O
di O
favourite O
to O
win O
am O
for O
Agege B-LOC
, O
but O
coach O
Clementine B-PER
Toure I-PER
and O
her O
girls O
decide O
say O
dem O
go O
change O
am O
for O
dem O
. O

Dem O
carry O
Day B-PER
from O
di O
ring O
wit O
stretcher O
. O

La O
Liga O
dey O
reason O
am O
to O
carri O
di O
Spanish B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
( O
RFEF B-ORG
) O
go O
court O
ontop O
say O
dem O
postponed O
El O
Clasico O
between O
Barcelona B-ORG
and O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
to O
18 B-DATE
December I-DATE
. O

Di O
first O
round O
of O
Copa O
del O
Rey O
competition O
go O
begin O
on O
dat O
same O
date O
too O
. O

"""" O
La O
Liga O
no O
gree O
wit O
di O
competition O
committee O
decision O
to O
select O
18 B-DATE
December I-DATE
- O
afta O
dem O
reach O
agreement O
wit O
Barcelona B-ORG
and O
Real B-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
, O
even O
though O
Liga O
say O
dem O
no O
want O
am O
- O
as O
di O
date O
wey O
di O
postponed O
Clasico O
go O
now O
happun O
, O
"""" O
La O
Liga O
tok O
for O
statement O
. O

"""" O
We O
dey O
study O
di O
document O
. O
. O
. O
in O
order O
to O
torchlight O
how O
we O
take O
carri O
di O
mata O
go O
court O
. O
"""" O

Spain B-ORG
Constitutional I-ORG
Court I-ORG
don O
declare O
di O
referendum O
illegal O
. O

Senegal B-LOC
make O
sure O
say O
Brazil B-LOC
no O
win O
for O
Neymar B-PER
100th O
match O
as O
both O
kontris O
play O
1 O
- O
1 O
for O
international O
friendly O
for O
Singapore B-LOC
. O

Brazil B-LOC
go O
now O
face O
Nigeria B-LOC
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
on O
Sunday B-DATE
for O
di O
same O
venue O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
. O

Etienne B-PER
Eto'o I-PER
say O
e O
bi O
na O
big O
blow O
for O
know O
say O
dis O
decree O
go O
komot O
dem O
for O
World O
Cup O
, O
and O
wit O
de O
five O
Europe B-LOC
players O
encourage O
we O
selves O
and O
we O
don O
turn O
new O
page O
for O
life O
, O
Eto'o B-PER
e O
pikin O
tok O
. O

Coach O
Libiih B-PER
Thomas I-PER
, O
former O
Cameroon B-LOC
international O
weh O
e O
play O
1990 B-DATE
World O
Cup O
bin O
write O
for O
federation O
make O
deh O
tell O
e O
weti O
about O
dis O
decree O
for O
do O
before O
e O
give O
e O
finals O
list O
for O
Fifa B-ORG
. O

Casimero B-PER
for O
score O
anoda O
goal O
during O
di O
match O
but O
im O
head O
di O
ball O
go O
hit O
bar O
. O

Top O
star O
Neymar B-PER
play O
only O
12 B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
for O
di O
match O
sake O
of O
Injury O
, O
but O
oda O
ogbonge O
stars O
like O
Philipe B-PER
Coutinho I-PER
, O
Gabriel B-PER
Jesus I-PER
, O
Roberto B-PER
Firmino I-PER
and O
veteran O
Dani B-PER
Alves I-PER
show O
wella O
for O
di O
Brazil B-LOC
team O
. O

Di O
Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
bin O
loose O
3 O
- O
0 O
to O
Brazil B-LOC
for O
dia O
last O
meeting O
for O
National B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
Abuja I-LOC
. O

Super B-ORG
Eagles I-ORG
coach O
, O
Gernot B-PER
Rohr I-PER
plan O
use O
today B-DATE
match O
take O
prepare O
im O
team O
for O
dia O
Africa B-LOC
Cup O
of O
Nations O
. O

Senegal B-LOC
International O
player O
Sadio B-PER
Mane I-PER
score O
di O
first O
goal O
for O
di O
defending O
champions O
. O

Osimhen B-PER
dey O
form O
Victor B-PER
Osimhen I-PER
score O
for O
Lille B-ORG
but O
den O
lose O
2 O
- O
1 O
for O
house O
to O
Chelsea B-ORG
. O

Di O
Nigerian O
striker O
now O
don O
score O
seven O
goals O
for O
in O
last O
10 O
games O
for O
im O
French O
club O
for O
all O
competitions O
. O
Ziyech B-PER
score O
from O
25 O
yards O
Morocco B-LOC
international O
player O
Hakim B-PER
Ziyech I-PER
score O
fine O
goal O
as O
Ajax B-ORG
continue O
dis O
fine O
form O
for O
Champions O
League O
. O

Pepe B-PER
enter O
as O
substitute O
for O
di O
second O
half O
and O
come O
later O
score O
two O
free O
- O
kicks O
to O
show O
Arsenal B-ORG
fans O
say O
im O
fit O
provide O
di O
pepper O
dia O
season O
need O
. O

Before O
Thursday B-DATE
night I-DATE
game O
, O
Pepe B-PER
bin O
don O
score O
only O
one O
goal O
in O
11 O
appearance O
for O
di O
gunners B-ORG
since O
im O
£ O
72m O
summer B-DATE
signing O
from O
Lyon B-ORG
. O

Afta O
di O
game O
Arsenal B-ORG
coach O
Unai B-PER
Emery I-PER
call O
Pepe B-PER
match O
- O
winning O
performance O
as O
"""" O
perfect O
"""" O
. O

Emery B-PER
say O
: O
"""" O
Every O
player O
usually O
need O
time O
to O
adapt O
. O

"""" O
Im O
dey O
kontinu O
im O
adaptation O
process O
and O
as O
soon O
as O
e O
adapt O
finish O
, O
e O
go O
dey O
better O
for O
us O
. O
"""" O

Goals O
from O
Norwich B-ORG
top O
scorer O
Teemu B-PER
Pukki I-PER
, O
Todd B-PER
Cantwell I-PER
and O
Kenny B-PER
McLean I-PER
na O
im O
help O
di O
newly O
promoted O
side O
beat O
di O
reigning O
league O
champions O
. O

Di O
last O
time O
wey O
Manchester B-ORG
City I-ORG
lose O
for O
Premier O
League O
na O
for O
January B-DATE
29 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2019 I-DATE
wen O
Newcastle B-ORG
bin O
beat O
dem O
2 O
- O
1 O
. O

Di O
Jamaican O
run O
her O
fastest O
race O
in O
six B-DATE
years I-DATE
wit O
time O
of O
10 B-DATE
. I-DATE
71 I-DATE
seconds I-DATE
to O
win O
her O
eight O
world O
title O
. O

Afta O
she O
win O
she O
say O
; O
"""" O
My O
son O
Zyon B-PER
, O
my O
family O
na O
my O
strength O
. O

Na O
about O
who O
you O
be O
and O
why O
you O
start O
"""" O
. O

Fraser B-PER
- I-PER
Pryce I-PER
, O
wey O
be O
32 B-DATE
- I-DATE
years I-DATE
don O
become O
di O
oldest O
woman O
to O
win O
Olympic O
or O
world O
100m O
title O
, O
two B-DATE
years I-DATE
afta O
she O
born O
her O
pikin O
, O
Zyon B-PER
. O

"""" O
Di O
police O
say O
e O
dey O
difficult O
to O
track O
dis O
kidnappers O
dem O
, O
but O
wetin O
dey O
make O
me O
worry O
na O
say O
my O
mama O
dey O
very O
sick O
, O
"""" O
Siasia B-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Sport I-ORG
. O

"""" O
For O
pesin O
wey O
no O
well O
, O
to O
come O
comot O
freedom O
from O
dat O
pesin O
life O
, O
dis O
one O
pass O
bad O
, O
e O
dey O
heartbreaking O
and O
sad O
. O

"""" O
So O
di O
only O
tin O
wey O
I O
fit O
do O
na O
to O
just O
beg O
dis O
guys O
to O
free O
my O
mama O
. O

I O
go O
like O
make O
di O
goment O
or O
whoever O
dey O
capable O
to O
help O
me O
bring O
my O
mama O
back O
. O
"""" O

"""" O
For O
three B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
I O
never O
get O
work O
and O
wit O
dis O
Fifa B-ORG
ban O
appeal O
and O
to O
come O
get O
my O
sick O
mama O
for O
di O
hands O
of O
kidnappers O
, O
my O
tire O
pass O
tire O
. O
"""" O

Di O
match O
go O
take O
place O
for O
di O
Singapore B-LOC
National I-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
on O
October B-DATE
13 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2019 I-DATE
. O

Goalkeepers O
: O
Francis B-PER
Uzoho I-PER
( O
Omonia B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Cyprus B-LOC
) O
; O
Ikechukwu B-PER
Ezenwa I-PER
( O
Heartland B-ORG
FC I-ORG
) O
; O
Emil B-PER
Maduka I-PER
Okoye I-PER
( O
Fortuna B-ORG
Dusseldorf I-ORG
, O
Germany B-LOC
) O
. O

Defenders O
: O
Olaoluwa B-PER
Aina I-PER
( O
Torino B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Italy B-LOC
) O
; O
Abdullahi B-PER
Shehu I-PER
( O
Bursaspor B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Turkey B-LOC
) O
; O
Chidozie B-PER
Awaziem I-PER
( O
CD B-ORG
Leganes I-ORG
, O
Spain B-LOC
) O
; O
William B-PER
Ekong I-PER
( O
Udinese B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Italy B-LOC
) O
; O
Kenneth B-PER
Omeruo I-PER
( O
CD B-ORG
Leganes I-ORG
, O
Spain B-LOC
) O
; O
Jamilu B-PER
Collins I-PER
( O
SC B-ORG
Padeborn I-ORG
07 I-ORG
, O
Germany B-LOC
) O
; O
Oluwasemilogo B-PER
Ajayi I-PER
( O
West B-ORG
Bromwich I-ORG
Albion I-ORG
, O
England B-LOC
) O
. O

Midfielders O
: O
Alexander B-PER
Iwobi I-PER
( O
Everton B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
England B-LOC
) O
; O
Anderson B-PER
Esiti I-PER
( O
PAOK B-ORG
Salonica I-ORG
, O
Greece B-LOC
) O
; O
Oghenekaro B-PER
Etebo I-PER
( O
Stoke B-ORG
City I-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
England B-LOC
) O
; O
Wilfred B-PER
Ndidi I-PER
( O
Leicester B-ORG
City I-ORG
, O
England B-LOC
) O
; O
Joseph B-PER
Ayodele I-PER
- I-PER
Aribo I-PER
( O
Glasgow B-ORG
Rangers I-ORG
, O
Scotland B-LOC
) O
; O
Ramon B-PER
Azeez I-PER
( O
Granada B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
Spain B-LOC
) O
. O

"""" O
We O
dey O
look O
at O
how O
woman O
go O
fit O
fight O
as O
part O
of O
di O
undercard O
, O
"""" O
im O
tell O
BBC B-ORG
5 O
Live O
Boxing O
. O

Some O
pipo O
don O
criticize O
di O
event O
wen O
di O
tori O
comot O
say O
na O
for O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
e O
go O
happun O
. O

For O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
, O
freedom O
of O
expression O
and O
women O
rights O
get O
k O
- O
leg O
and O
di O
international O
community O
don O
also O
raise O
di O
issue O
of O
death O
penalty O
for O
offence O
wey O
international O
law O
no O
recognise O
to O
be O
crime O
. O

Japan B-LOC
sef O
bin O
get O
second O
wave O
for O
di O
north O
of O
di O
kontri O
for O
Haikkaido B-LOC
city I-LOC
. O

Dis O
na O
as O
plenti O
kontris O
dey O
look O
into O
mass O
testing O
as O
way O
to O
avoid O
second O
wave O
. O

Factories O
for O
di O
textile O
industries O
don O
open O
plenti O
last B-DATE
week I-DATE
of I-DATE
April I-DATE
even O
as O
di O
lockdown O
still O
dey O
go O
on O
till O
di O
middle B-DATE
of I-DATE
May I-DATE
. O

Bangladesh B-LOC
wey O
be O
di O
second O
largest O
explorer O
of O
clothes O
for O
world O
dem O
don O
dey O
suffer O
on O
top O
cancellation O
of O
orders O
from O
Europe B-LOC
and O
South B-LOC
America I-LOC
. O

Di O
whole O
supply O
chain O
from O
who O
dey O
farm O
, O
to O
di O
finisihed O
product O
don O
dey O
face O
palava O
, O
'e O
. O
g O
India B-LOC
we O
don O
lose O
dia O
fist O
harvest O
of O
tea O
leaves O
cause O
no O
bodi O
dey O
to O
pick O
and O
go O
fit O
lose O
dia O
second O
harvest O
join O
and O
na O
why O
dem O
economies O
wey O
dey O
depend O
on O
crops O
dey O
press O
so O
dat O
food O
no O
go O
waste O
. O

Dem O
dey O
do O
temperature O
check O
for O
Vietnam B-LOC
schools O
and O
different O
time O
for O
drop O
off O
and O
pick O
up O
of O
pikin O
for O
Norway B-LOC
schools O
. O

Many O
kontris O
no O
wan O
reduce O
lockdown O
restriction O
for O
restaurants O
, O
pubs O
and O
theatres O
, O
For O
Thailand B-LOC
, O
na O
cubicle O
pipo O
don O
dey O
eat O
inside O
as O
dem O
restaurants O
don O
dey O
get O
protective O
barriers O
and O
oda O
kontris O
don O
dey O
tink O
di O
same O
way O
. O

For O
public O
transport O
wia O
social O
distancing O
go O
turn O
wahala O
, O
cities O
dem O
get O
oda O
plans O
. O

Even O
sef O
dem O
cancel O
di O
Buddist B-DATE
New I-DATE
Year I-DATE
for O
South B-LOC
Asia I-LOC
. O

But O
kontris O
dey O
wey O
dey O
try O
normalise O
di O
attendance O
for O
religious O
events O
. O

Many O
religious O
groups O
don O
carry O
dia O
faith O
enter O
internet O
as O
dem O
dey O
stuck O
for O
house O
with O
streaming O
and O
sabi O
pipo O
tok O
say O
dis O
practice O
fit O
no O
end O
any O
time O
soon O
. O

Dis O
na O
one O
of O
di O
biggest O
events O
of O
di O
year O
, O
e O
dey O
mark O
di O
birth O
of O
di O
founder O
of O
di O
nation O
. O

Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
last O
appear O
for O
state O
media O
on O
12 B-DATE
April I-DATE
as O
im O
"""" O
inspect O
pursuit O
assault O
plane O
group O
"""" O
for O
one O
handout O
wey O
no O
get O
date O
. O

We O
know O
say O
im O
chair O
one O
key O
political O
meeting O
di O
day O
before O
, O
from O
state O
media O
despatches O
. O

But O
dem O
never O
see O
am O
since O
. O

But O
later O
one O
sensational O
headline O
for O
US B-LOC
media O
comot O
say O
di O
North O
Korean O
leader O
dey O
in O
critical O
condition O
after O
heart O
surgery O
. O

E O
dey O
important O
to O
note O
say O
nobody O
don O
deny O
say O
Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
undergo O
heart O
surgery O
. O

State O
media O
dat O
time O
admit O
say O
im O
bin O
dey O
suffer O
from O
"""" O
uncomfortable O
physical O
condition O
"""" O
, O
but O
dem O
no O
address O
rumours O
say O
im O
dey O
suffer O
from O
gout O
. O

Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
- I-PER
un I-PER
papa O
prepare O
am O
to O
lead O
di O
kontri O
for O
many O
years O
. O

Di O
Kim B-PER
dynasty O
look O
secure O
. O

Dis O
dey O
account O
for O
over O
85 O
percent O
of O
cases O
for O
wey O
Ashanti B-LOC
den O
Eastern B-LOC
region I-LOC
dey O
follow O
. O

Dis O
be O
after O
17 O
new O
people O
recover O
after O
de O
last O
declaration O
by O
Ghana B-ORG
Health I-ORG
Service I-ORG
. O

Social O
- O
distancing O
measures O
dey O
in O
place O
for O
Netherlands B-LOC
since O
23 B-DATE
March I-DATE
, O
wen O
goment O
impose O
wetin O
dem O
call O
"""" O
intelligent O
"""" O
or O
"""" O
targeted O
"""" O
lockdown O
. O

"""" O
Discuss O
how O
best O
to O
do O
am O
togeda O
, O
"""" O
di O
RIVM B-ORG
guidance O
tok O
. O

On O
Monday B-DATE
, O
di O
Netherlands B-LOC
begin O
dia O
first O
stage O
of O
five O
- O
phase O
lockdown O
exit O
plan O
. O

I O
no O
know O
if O
my O
friends O
suspect O
anytin O
. O

Evritin O
look O
great O
from O
di O
outside O
: O
smiling O
faces O
, O
friends O
, O
plenti O
moni O
, O
happiness O
and O
confidence O
. O

Na O
recently O
I O
sabi O
say O
my O
ex O
- O
wife O
dey O
rape O
me O
for O
10 B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

Inside O
one O
day O
, O
I O
lose O
evritin O
. O

I O
bin O
need O
to O
go O
overseas O
on O
long O
business O
trip O
. O

She O
go O
scratch O
my O
skin O
wit O
her O
fingernails O
till O
I O
start O
to O
dey O
bleed O
, O
she O
go O
punch O
me O
. O

I O
try O
rent O
anoda O
room O
for O
mysef O
for O
hotel O
once O
but O
I O
no O
dey O
speak O
dia O
language O
so O
dem O
no O
understand O
me O
for O
exception O
. O

I O
don O
count O
wen O
we O
go O
leave O
Ukraine B-LOC
. O

But O
my O
try O
to O
comot O
for O
di O
relationship O
drag O
for O
years O
. O

We O
go O
fight O
, O
I O
go O
turn O
off O
my O
phone O
and O
even O
block O
her O
for O
evriwia O
; O
I O
go O
hide O
but O
she O
go O
come O
siddon O
for O
door O
side O
. O

And O
I O
go O
go O
back O
to O
her O
evri O
time O
. O

Wia O
eva O
I O
go O
, O
I O
need O
to O
always O
call O
her O
. O

I O
go O
dey O
tell O
her O
. O

She O
no O
fit O
go O
anywhere O
without O
me O
- O
I O
be O
play O
toy O
wey O
need O
to O
entertain O
her O
all O
di O
time O
. O

Ira B-PER
no O
get O
job O
- O
I O
provide O
for O
us O
, O
cook O
and O
even O
clean O
. O

Na O
once O
a O
day O
dis O
kind O
tin O
dey O
happun O
or O
even O
evri O
oda O
day O
. O

Anytin O
wey O
dey O
happun O
- O
she O
go O
blame O
me O
. O

I O
dey O
powerless O
and O
I O
dey O
do O
evritin O
she O
want O
so O
she O
no O
go O
vex O
. O

Wen O
I O
reach O
house O
, O
she O
say O
she O
dey O
sorry O
but O
she O
no O
fit O
stop O
. O

So O
evritin O
go O
start O
again O
di O
next B-DATE
day I-DATE
. O

I O
no O
dey O
perfect O
. O

You O
no O
go O
see O
di O
way O
out O
and O
you O
no O
go O
hear O
wen O
you O
dey O
situation O
like O
dat O
, O
you O
no O
dey O
know O
wetin O
dey O
happun O
to O
you O
. O

You O
no O
dey O
see O
di O
way O
out O
and O
you O
no O
dey O
hear O
from O
anyone O
. O

You O
no O
even O
dey O
tink O
say O
you O
get O
time O
to O
escape O
, O
e O
just O
dey O
hopeless O
. O

Sita B-PER
Tyasutami I-PER
and O
her O
mama O
Maria B-PER
Darmaningsih I-PER
bin O
get O
all O
di O
symptoms O
of O
coronovirus O
and O
bin O
dey O
chill O
for O
hospital O
bed O
dey O
wait O
for O
di O
result O
of O
dia O
test O
. O

Tyasutami B-PER
tok O
say O
, O
"""" O
we O
bin O
ask O
make O
dem O
to O
test O
us O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
but O
hospital O
say O
na O
sake O
of O
say O
dem O
bin O
no O
get O
di O
equipment O
. O
"""" O

Tyasutami B-PER
and O
Darmaningsih B-PER
bin O
expect O
say O
doctor O
go O
tell O
dem O
dia O
result O
instead O
of O
Presido O
Widod B-PER
wey O
broadcast O
am O
give O
kontri O
pipo O
for O
2 B-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

Tyasutami B-PER
tok O
say O
before O
dia O
diagonosis O
she O
bin O
get O
like O
2 O
, O
000 O
followers O
for O
Instagram O
and O
no O
hate O
speech O
but O
now O
she O
don O
dey O
get O
hate O
speech O
steady O
from O
her O
10 O
, O
000 O
followers O
wey O
dey O
target O
di O
pictures O
wey O
she O
wear O
sexy O
clothes O
. O

But O
pipo O
start O
to O
dey O
tok O
again O
. O

Dem O
test O
every O
pesin O
for O
her O
house O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
and O
na O
wia O
dem O
find O
out O
say O
her O
older O
sister O
, O
33 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
artist O
manager O
wey O
dey O
stay O
for O
Vienna B-LOC
, O
Anindyajati B-PER
go O
need O
join O
dem O
for O
isolation O
for O
hospital O
. O

Di O
experience O
don O
change O
dia O
life O
forever O
. O

Additional O
reporting O
by O
Resty B-PER
Woro I-PER
Yuniar I-PER
of O
BBC B-ORG
Indonesia I-ORG

Di O
World B-ORG
Health I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
( O
WHO B-ORG
) O
don O
sama O
warning O
say O
coronavirus O
fit O
no O
comot O
for O
di O
world O
again O
. O

WHO B-ORG
Emergencies O
Director O
, O
Dr O
Mike B-PER
Ryan I-PER
wey O
tok O
dis O
one O
for O
one O
virtual O
press O
briefing O
say O
, O
e O
dey O
important O
for O
pipo O
to O
know O
say O
dis O
virus O
fit O
become O
anoda O
common O
virus O
for O
di O
world O
just O
like O
HIV O
. O

He O
say O
many O
oda O
sicknesses O
, O
like O
measles O
still O
dey O
even O
afta O
vaccine O
dey O
to O
treat O
am O
. O

He O
warn O
say O
assurance O
no O
dey O
if O
di O
virus O
no O
go O
come O
again O
as O
kontris O
reduce O
lockdown O
small O
. O

Di O
dancer O
dey O
for O
di O
musician O
hit O
music O
video O
WO O
! O
! O

Allen B-PER
na O
di O
drummer O
, O
musical O
director O
and O
leader O
of O
Fela B-PER
Kuti I-PER
famous O
band O
Africa B-ORG
'70 I-ORG
for O
1960 B-DATE
- I-DATE
70s I-DATE
. O

He O
once O
tok O
say O
"""" O
without O
Tony B-PER
Allen I-PER
, O
afrobeat O
no O
go O
exist O
"""" O
. O

UK B-LOC
musician O
Brian B-PER
Eno I-PER
wen O
im O
dey O
tok O
about O
Allen B-PER
say O
im O
"""" O
reason O
am O
to O
be O
di O
greatest O
drummer O
wey O
don O
ever O
live O
"""" O
. O

Allen B-PER
career O
and O
life O
tori O
dey O
documented O
inside O
im O
2013 B-DATE
autobiography O
Tony B-PER
Allen I-PER
: O
Master O
Drummer O
of O
Afrobeat O
. O

Allen B-PER
bin O
first O
meet O
Fela B-PER
for O
1964 B-DATE
, O
and O
dem O
form O
partnership O
wey O
produce O
plenty O
albums O
during O
di O
era O
of O
Africa B-ORG
'70 I-ORG
band O
, O
including O
Gentleman O
and O
Zombie O
. O

Oda O
celebrities O
wey O
go O
show O
face O
for O
di O
18 B-DATE
April I-DATE
concert O
na O
David B-PER
Beckham I-PER
, O
Kerry B-PER
Washington I-PER
, O
Priyanka B-PER
Chopra I-PER
Jonas I-PER
, O
Idris B-PER
and O
Sabrina B-PER
Elba I-PER
, O
wey O
both O
test O
positive O
for O
Covid O
- O
19 O
. O

Two B-DATE
months I-DATE
afta O
im O
tok O
about O
im O
sickness O
for O
public O
, O
im O
write O
open O
letter O
about O
im O
experience O
with O
di O
cancer O
treatment O
, O
im O
tok O
about O
di O
"""" O
intensity O
"""" O
of O
im O
pain O
and O
di O
"""" O
uncertainty O
"""" O
of O
life O
. O

You O
go O
dey O
sweat O
. O

I O
come O
give O
her O
tonnes O
of O
tissue O
paper O
wey O
later O
turn O
to O
brown O
! O
"""" O

Di O
couple O
enta O
gbege O
afta O
one O
viral O
video O
wey O
show O
dem O
dey O
party O
for O
house O
with O
more O
dan O
20 O
pipo O
for O
di O
house O
Di O
couple O
go O
also O
pay O
100 O
, O
000 O
naira O
each O
and O
go O
observe O
di O
isolation O
for O
place O
wia O
nobody O
go O
know O
by O
di O
Lagos B-LOC
state O
goment O
to O
determine O
dia O
Covid O
- O
19 O
status O
. O

Dem O
must O
also O
submit O
di O
names O
and O
phone O
numbers O
of O
every O
pesin O
wey O
attend O
di O
party O
. O

Di O
coronavirus O
palava O
no O
be O
like O
wetin O
wan O
stop O
soon O
as O
more O
and O
more O
pipo O
and O
kontries O
dey O
confam O
cases O
. O

Apart O
from O
oga O
Idris B-PER
, O
oda O
celebs O
too O
don O
also O
announce O
say O
dem O
get O
di O
virus O
. O

Ogbonge O
Oscar O
- O
winner O
actor O
Tom B-PER
Hanks I-PER
tell O
world O
pipo O
say O
im O
and O
im O
wife O
Rita B-PER
Wilson I-PER
don O
test O
positive O
for O
di O
coronavirus O
for O
Australia B-LOC
. O

Fever O
and O
tireness O
na O
my O
main O
symptoms O
. O

Kristofer B-PER
Hivju I-PER
, O
wey O
don O
also O
act O
for O
films O
like O
'Fast O
& O
Furious O
8' O
, O
'Downhill' O
, O
'The O
Last O
King' O
say O
: O
"""" O
My O
familiy O
and O
I O
dey O
self O
- O
isolate O
for O
house O
for O
as O
long O
as O
e O
take O
. O

Rachel B-PER
Matthews I-PER
, O
wey O
dey O
popular O
for O
her O
role O
in O
'Happy O
Death O
Day' O
and O
also O
voiced O
di O
character O
of O
Honeymaren O
for O
Frozen O
2 O
, O
announce O
for O
her O
Instagram O
Stories O
say O
she O
don O
test O
positive O
for O
COVID O
- O
19 O
. O

She O
say O
: O
"""" O
I O
no O
dey O
sure O
of O
my O
next O
step O
but O
i O
go O
remain O
in O
quarantine O
until O
dem O
tell O
me O
to O
do O
otherwise O
. O
. O
. O
"""" O
Kim B-PER
Kardashian I-PER
, O
Naomi B-PER
Campbell I-PER
, O
Arnold B-PER
Schwarzenegger I-PER
, O
Taylor B-PER
Swift I-PER
, O
Ariana B-PER
Grande I-PER
, O
Lizzo B-PER
and O
oda O
celebrities O
don O
come O
out O
for O
social O
media O
to O
share O
tips O
wey O
go O
help O
stop O
di O
spread O
of O
di O
virus O
. O

She O
tok O
say O
, O
"""" O
DJ B-PER
Obi I-PER
party O
bin O
get O
plenti O
celebs O
with O
oda O
pipo O
join O
and O
dey O
very O
interesting O
. O

We O
dey O
pretend O
say O
we O
dey O
for O
inside O
club O
and O
for O
di O
chat O
we O
, O
go O
dey O
do O
like O
na O
real O
party O
, O
dey O
chyke O
babe O
, O
dey O
bounce O
pipo O
comot O
and O
like O
say O
pesin O
dey O
order O
bottles O
. O
"""" O

Anoda O
pesin O
wey O
be O
music O
artiste O
, O
LSMK B-PER
wey O
im O
real O
name O
na O
Olisa B-PER
Ogbolu I-PER
also O
tok O
how O
im O
host O
listening O
party O
for O
im O
Instagram O
page O
, O
for O
im O
music O
wey O
im O
neva O
release O
yet O
. O

Infact O
, O
Helen B-PER
Ifeonye I-PER
, O
tell O
us O
say O
she O
dey O
use O
am O
to O
attend O
game O
parties O
wey O
dem O
dey O
do O
. O

She O
say O
, O
"""" O
E O
dey O
very O
wild O
and O
fun O
say O
random O
pipo O
go O
fit O
just O
join O
your O
room O
without O
warning O
and O
you O
go O
just O
dey O
look O
new O
pesin O
. O
"""" O

Anoda O
pesin O
, O
Moses B-PER
Imodu I-PER
describe O
di O
House O
Party O
App O
say O
, O
"""" O
na O
like O
combination O
of O
Whatsapp O
, O
Snapchat O
an O
Skype O
as O
you O
fit O
video O
chat O
with O
up O
to O
eight O
pipo O
and O
also O
fit O
play O
online O
games O
. O
"""" O

Henshaw B-PER
make O
dis O
demand O
wen O
she O
follow O
BBC B-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
tok O
on O
top O
di O
matter O
. O

She O
say O
she O
go O
"""" O
like O
make O
di O
executive O
give O
us O
criteria O
wey O
dem O
tak O
choose O
our O
patron O
. O

Dem O
go O
also O
need O
give O
us O
history O
of O
person O
wey O
dem O
appoint O
. O

We O
get O
women O
for O
di O
guild O
and O
we O
no O
want O
make O
person O
slap O
us O
! O
! O
"""" O

When O
she O
follow O
our O
correspondent O
tok O
, O
she O
still O
put O
hand O
for O
chest O
say O
she O
tok O
wetin O
she O
tok O
. O

Rollas B-PER
say O
im O
no O
see O
way O
Henshaw B-PER
and O
di O
rest O
pipo O
dey O
vex O
. O

Di O
president O
even O
say O
na O
Senator O
Abbo B-PER
holy O
pass O
. O

As O
di O
palava O
dey O
hot O
for O
social O
media O
, O
BBC B-ORG
pidgin I-ORG
try O
tok O
to O
di O
senator O
wey O
dey O
di O
eyes O
of O
di O
storm O
but O
im O
no O
reply O
message O
wey O
our O
correspondent O
send O
give O
am O
. O

For O
2013 B-DATE
, O
e O
enta O
di O
Country O
Music O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
and O
even O
for O
dat O
year O
e O
perform O
"""" O
The O
Gambler O
"""" O
twice O
for O
Glastonbury O
on O
top O
how O
pipo O
gbadun O
di O
song O
. O

E O
bin O
marry O
five O
times O
and O
get O
five O
pikin O
. O

Di O
feem O
follow O
win O
for O
Best O
Sound O
Editor O
, O
Best O
Cinematographer O
, O
Best O
Soundtrack O
, O
Best O
Writers O
, O
Best O
Movie O
for O
West B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
Best O
Overall O
Movie O
. O

Pipo O
for O
social O
media O
don O
dey O
tok O
dia O
mind O
on O
top O
di O
movie O
. O

You O
fit O
find O
oda O
winners O
of O
di O
night O
here O
: O

According O
to O
Uganda B-LOC
tori O
pipo O
, O
dem O
diagnose O
Nikita B-PER
Pearl I-PER
Waligwa I-PER
with O
brain O
tumour O
. O

Di O
film O
wey O
she O
do O
for O
2016 B-DATE
na O
true O
life O
story O
of O
Phiona B-PER
Mutesi I-PER
, O
wey O
begin O
play O
chess O
for O
di O
age B-DATE
of I-DATE
nine I-DATE
even O
though O
say O
e O
no O
go O
school O
and O
e O
carry O
di O
game O
go O
anoda O
level O
as O
im O
begin O
compete O
for O
international O
tournaments O
. O

Di O
film O
feature O
actress O
Lupita B-PER
Nyong'o I-PER
as O
her O
mama O
and O
David B-PER
Oyelowo I-PER
as O
her O
chess O
teacher O
. O

Waligwa B-PER
play O
di O
role O
of O
Gloria B-PER
, O
friend O
of O
Phiona B-PER
who O
explained O
how O
dem O
take O
dey O
play O
chess O
to O
her O
. O

For O
2017 B-DATE
, O
dem O
say O
she O
don O
recover O
but O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
dem O
find O
anoda O
tumor O
. O

Dem O
dey O
call O
am O
"""" O
music O
biggest O
night O
"""" O
, O
di O
ceremony O
na O
like O
di O
"""" O
music O
longest O
day O
"""" O
- O
wit O
different O
festivities O
wey O
dey O
start O
wit O
lunchtime O
for O
LA B-LOC
and O
e O
dey O
enta O
night O
time O
. O

Dem O
dey O
advise O
make O
pesin O
wear O
shoe O
wey O
go O
dey O
comfortable O
. O

All O
dem O
three O
dey O
represent O
di O
new O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
lead O
di O
way O
for O
pop O
music O
and O
pipo O
wey O
no O
dey O
follow O
old O
ways O
wey O
dem O
dey O
use O
do O
things O
But O
, O
as O
Snoop B-PER
Dogg I-PER
sabi O
wella O
nominations O
no O
mean O
say O
you O
go O
win O
, O
im O
don O
go O
house O
17 O
times O
wey O
im O
no O
collect O
trophy O
afta O
dem O
nominate O
. O

We O
no O
go O
fit O
predict O
pipo O
wey O
go O
win O
di O
award O
sake O
of O
dis O
reason O
but O
dis O
na O
some O
of O
di O
seven O
moments O
wey O
you O
go O
watch O
out O
for O
today B-DATE
. O

Ten B-DATE
days I-DATE
before O
di O
Grammys O
, O
di O
Recording O
Academy O
drop O
bombshell O
say O
dem O
dey O
suspend O
dia O
chief O
executive O
Deborah B-PER
Dugan I-PER
with O
immediate O
effect O
. O

Dugan B-PER
respond O
as O
she O
file O
discrimination O
complaint O
wia O
she O
suggest O
say O
di O
voting O
process O
for O
di O
Grammys O
get O
mago O
- O
mago O
inside O
. O

Some O
of O
her O
claims O
dey O
confam O
wetin O
evribodi O
dey O
suspect O
say O
e O
dey O
happun O
say O
dem O
dey O
treat O
pipo O
wey O
perform O
dat O
night O
beta O
pass O
oda O
pipo O
. O

Afta O
e O
die O
, O
di O
Los B-ORG
Angeles I-ORG
Police I-ORG
Department I-ORG
hail O
am O
as O
a O
"""" O
peacemaker O
"""" O
. O

Sir O
Elton B-PER
look O
like O
e O
bin O
dey O
cry O
as O
im O
put O
head O
for O
im O
piano O
and O
shake O
im O
head O
. O

Di O
audience O
give O
am O
ogbonge O
applause O
as O
plenti O
attendants O
help O
am O
comot O
stage O
. O

Walking O
pneumonia O
na O
type O
of O
lung O
infection O
wey O
bacteria O
or O
virus O
dey O
cause O
and O
e O
no O
dey O
serious O
like O
oda O
type O
of O
pneumonia O
and O
some O
of O
im O
victims O
no O
even O
need O
go O
hospital O
. O

E O
no O
too O
tay O
afta O
im O
comot O
stage O
wey O
, O
Sir O
Elton B-PER
tok O
sorry O
give O
im O
fans O
for O
Instagram O
post O
. O

Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
don O
tok O
say O
di O
way O
e O
bin O
dey O
take O
drugs O
wen O
im O
bin O
dey O
young O
na O
sometin O
wey O
dey O
"""" O
legit O
crazy O
scary O
"""" O
. O

E O
tok O
dis O
one O
for O
di O
latest O
episode O
of O
im O
YouTube O
series O
"""" O
Justin O
Bieber O
Seasons O
"""" O
, O
di O
singer O
tok O
say O
e O
bin O
dey O
addicted O
to O
drugs O
and O
cannabis O
wen O
e O
be O
13 B-DATE
years I-DATE
old I-DATE
. O

E O
say O
, O
"""" O
Pipo O
no O
sabi O
how O
serious O
e O
bin O
dey O
. O

I O
bin O
dey O
wake O
up O
for O
morning O
and O
di O
first O
tin O
I O
go O
do O
na O
to O
take O
drugs O
, O
smoke O
joint O
come O
start O
my O
day O
. O
"""" O

Di O
25 B-DATE
year I-DATE
old I-DATE
pop O
star O
don O
tok O
about O
im O
drug O
abuse O
and O
abusing O
im O
relationship O
before O
, O
but O
dis O
latest O
video O
na O
di O
first O
time O
e O
dey O
tok O
about O
am O
for O
camera O
. O

Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
tok O
about O
times O
wey O
e O
go O
do O
ecstasy O
and O
mushrooms O
wey O
dey O
turn O
brain O
sotay O
, O
im O
security O
team O
go O
dey O
check O
im O
pulse O
for O
night O
to O
make O
sure O
say O
e O
still O
dey O
breathe O
. O

Di O
series O
also O
show O
di O
star O
dey O
use O
oxygen O
mask O
to O
reduce O
im O
stress O
, O
anxiety O
and O
depression O
and O
how O
e O
dey O
work O
with O
brain O
disorder O
sabi O
person O
. O

Di O
statement O
say O
, O
"""" O
we O
dey O
happy O
to O
tell O
di O
public O
say O
di O
feem O
, O
Sugar O
Rush O
don O
dey O
classified O
and O
don O
collect O
final O
approval O
for O
public O
screening O
. O
"""" O

Di O
director O
of O
di O
feem O
, O
Kayode B-PER
Kasum I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
Pidgin I-ORG
say O
, O
"""" O
I O
dey O
happy O
say O
di O
movie O
dey O
back O
so O
pipo O
go O
fit O
see O
am O
because O
e O
be O
something O
wey O
dey O
very O
different O
wey O
I O
feel O
say O
Nigerians O
go O
dey O
proud O
of O
. O
"""" O

E O
also O
tok O
say O
di O
movie O
as O
e O
no O
dey O
cinema O
na O
"""" O
big O
blow O
because O
di O
movie O
bin O
dey O
climb O
for O
di O
money O
e O
dey O
make O
at O
very O
high O
rate O
. O
"""" O

Last B-DATE
week I-DATE
, O
pipo O
shock O
well O
- O
well O
afta O
some O
of O
di O
feem O
cast O
like O
Banky B-PER
W I-PER
announce O
say O
di O
movie O
, O
wey O
dem O
release O
for O
25 B-DATE
December I-DATE
last I-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
don O
comot O
from O
cinema O
. O

Shabalala B-PER
die O
for O
hospital O
inside O
Pretoria B-LOC
, O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
, O
di O
band O
manager O
tok O
. O

Mr O
Shabalala B-PER
die O
dis B-DATE
morning I-DATE
, O
"""" O
Xolani B-PER
Majozi I-PER
tell O
tori O
pipo O
South B-ORG
Africa I-ORG
Times I-ORG
. O

( O
Rest O
in O
peace O
, O
fada O
, O
your O
race O
don O
complete O
. O
) O

E O
begin O
work O
for O
di O
family O
farm O
and O
later O
, O
for O
one O
local O
factory O
. O

Shabalala B-PER
come O
finally O
become O
di O
leader O
and O
main O
composer O
for O
di O
choir O
, O
e O
mix O
indigenous O
Zulu O
songs O
and O
dances O
with O
South O
African O
isicathamiya O
singing O
style O
- O
dat O
na O
acapella O
tradition O
wey O
involve O
soft O
, O
shuffling O
style O
of O
dance O
. O

Dem O
re O
- O
christened O
di O
group O
name O
to O
Ladysmith B-ORG
Black I-ORG
Mambazo I-ORG
- O
Ladysmith B-LOC
represent O
dia O
hometown O
, O
Black O
refer O
to O
di O
black O
oxen O
wey O
be O
di O
strongest O
for O
di O
farm O
, O
and O
Mambazo O
na O
Zulu O
word O
for O
axe O
, O
wey O
symbolize O
di O
group O
ability O
to O
cut O
down O
competition O
. O

Di O
band O
join O
Simon B-PER
for O
im O
world O
tour O
and O
in O
return O
, O
Simon B-PER
produce O
dia O
next O
three O
albums O
- O
with O
1987 B-DATE
Shaka O
Zulu O
wey O
win O
Grammy O
for O
best O
traditional O
folk O
recording O
. O

Shabalala B-PER
retire O
from O
active O
performance O
for O
2014 B-DATE
shortly O
afta O
im O
perform O
for O
one O
memorial O
concert O
for O
Nelson B-PER
Mandela I-PER
. O

"""" O
My O
friend O
, O
wey O
be O
giant O
humble O
man O
, O
Joseph B-PER
Shabalala I-PER
, O
don O
pass O
away O
dis B-DATE
morning I-DATE
, O
"""" O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
Singer O
, O
Sipho B-PER
"""" I-PER
Hotstix I-PER
"""" I-PER
Mabuse I-PER
write O
for O
twitter B-ORG
. O

Chairmo O
for O
Kannywood B-ORG
Artistes I-ORG
Council I-ORG
Alhassan B-PER
Kwalle I-PER
tell O
BBC B-ORG
say O
nude O
video O
of O
actress O
Maryam B-PER
Booth I-PER
wey O
don O
go O
viral O
for O
social O
media O
for O
di O
last O
few O
days O
no O
go O
make O
dem O
ban O
her O
from O
acting O
. O

"""" O
For O
di O
video O
she O
dey O
even O
try O
seize O
di O
phone O
from O
pesin O
wey O
dey O
record O
wey O
show O
say O
she O
no O
gree O
make O
di O
recording O
happun O
. O

She O
just O
comot O
from O
bathroom O
and O
dey O
try O
change O
cloth O
wen O
di O
pesin O
record O
her O
. O
"""" O

Our O
council O
go O
give O
her O
all O
necessary O
support O
and O
she O
fit O
act O
film O
anytime O
. O
"""" O

Di O
actress O
Maryam B-PER
, O
bin O
release O
statement O
on O
Friday B-DATE
wia O
she O
accuse O
her O
former O
boyfriend O
Deezel B-PER
wey O
be O
musician O
say O
na O
im O
release O
di O
video O
wen O
dem O
bin O
dey O
date O
3 B-DATE
years I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

But O
Deezel B-PER
also O
release O
im O
own O
statement O
say O
no O
be O
im O
release O
di O
video O
and O
e O
no O
get O
anything O
to O
gain O
by O
doing O
dat O
. O

Di O
three B-DATE
seconds I-DATE
video O
wey O
go O
viral O
on O
Friday B-DATE
don O
make O
many O
pipo O
to O
comment O
on O
social O
media O
on O
weda O
na O
her O
friend O
or O
boyfriend O
record O
am O
. O

No O
think O
am O
too O
much O
, O
16 O
young O
pipo O
don O
decide O
to O
take O
di O
challenge O
to O
live O
inside O
one O
house O
for O
two B-DATE
months I-DATE
with O
di O
hope O
to O
find O
dia O
true O
love O
for O
one O
new O
reality O
TV O
show O
wey O
dem O
call O
di O
Ultimate O
Love O
. O

She O
say O
she O
don O
propose O
to O
man O
before O
but O
her O
papa O
no O
gree O
afta O
im O
realise O
say O
her O
bobo O
too O
old O
for O
her O
. O

Im O
shock O
evribodi O
for O
di O
launch O
show O
wen O
im O
disclose O
say O
im O
be O
former O
refugee O
from O
Sierra B-LOC
- I-LOC
Leone I-LOC
wia O
im O
mama O
from O
come O
before O
im O
find O
im O
way O
to O
im O
papa O
kontri O
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

Im O
longest O
relationship O
last O
for O
four B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
na O
with O
im O
high O
school O
sweetheart O
. O

Bolanle B-PER
na O
very O
bubbly O
woman O
from O
Ondo B-LOC
state I-LOC
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
. O

For O
di O
35 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
, O
public O
proposal O
na O
big O
no O
- O
no O
. O

23 B-DATE
- I-DATE
year I-DATE
- I-DATE
old I-DATE
accountant O
from O
Brass B-LOC
, O
Bayelsa B-LOC
State I-LOC
. O

Im O
dey O
hope O
to O
find O
pesin O
wey O
dey O
caring O
. O

Obichukwu B-PER
just O
dey O
find O
woman O
wey O
go O
give O
am O
peace O
. O

Many O
Nigerians O
neva O
still O
believe O
dia O
eyes O
say O
di O
sexiest O
man O
alive' O
for O
2019 B-DATE
, O
( O
according O
to O
Peoples B-ORG
Magazine I-ORG
) O
show O
face O
for O
Lagos B-LOC
. O

Some O
Nigerians O
for O
social O
media O
don O
begin O
dey O
react O
and O
wonder O
wia O
dem O
dey O
wen O
America B-LOC
singer O
, O
John B-PER
Legend I-PER
come O
perform O
for O
Lagos B-LOC
. O

Ghanaian O
rapper O
, O
Sarkodie B-PER
and O
Nigerian O
singer O
Yemi B-PER
Alade I-PER
don O
begin O
dey O
patch O
dia O
relationship O
afta O
afta O
tins O
fall O
apart O
between O
dem O
two B-DATE
years I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

Yesterday B-DATE
, O
Sarkodie B-PER
tweet O
say O
make O
Yemi B-PER
Alade I-PER
follow O
am O
back O
on O
Twitter B-ORG
and O
di O
Nigeria B-LOC
singer O
agree O
. O

Alade B-PER
come O
para O
and O
accuse O
Sarkodie B-PER
say O
im O
dey O
unprofessional O
and O
since O
den O
di O
two O
of O
dem O
no O
too O
dey O
yarn O
with O
each O
oda O
until O
now O
. O

Di O
artists O
coming O
back O
togeda O
as O
friends O
lead O
to O
happiness O
for O
many O
of O
dia O
fans O
as O
dem O
begin O
tweet O
concerning O
dis O
. O

Di O
77th O
Golden O
Globe O
Awards O
dey O
happun O
for O
Los B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC
, O
California B-LOC
for O
Sunday B-DATE
evening I-DATE
. O

Here O
na O
di O
full O
list O
of O
nominees O
: O
Best O
motion O
picture O
- O
drama O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
for O
motion O
picture O
- O
drama O
Best O
actor O
for O
motion O
picture O
- O
drama O
Best O
motion O
picture O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
for O
motion O
picture O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
motion O
picture O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
motion O
picture O
- O
animated O
Best O
motion O
picture O
- O
foreign O
language O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
wey O
dey O
supporting O
role O
for O
any O
motion O
picture O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
wey O
dey O
supporting O
role O
for O
any O
motion O
picture O
Best O
director O
for O
motion O
picture O
Best O
screenplay O
- O
motion O
picture O
Best O
original O
score O
Best O
original O
song O
- O
motion O
picture O
Best O
Television O
series O
- O
drama O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
for O
drama O
series O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
drama O
series O
Best O
television O
series O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O

actress O
for O
television O
series O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
television O
series O
- O
musical O
or O
comedy O
Best O
television O
limited O
series O
or O
motion O
picture O
wey O
dem O
do O
for O
television O
Best O
actress O
for O
limited O
series O
or O
TV O
movie O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
limited O
series O
or O
motion O
picture O
wey O
dem O
make O
for O
television O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actress O
for O
supporting O
role O
in O
a O
series O
, O
limited O
series O
or O
a O
motion O
picture O
wey O
dem O
make O
for O
television O
Best O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
for O
supporting O
role O
for O
series O
, O
limited O
series O
or O
motion O
picture O
wey O
dem O
make O
for O
television O

British O
born O
actress O
, O
singer O
and O
songwriter O
Cynthia B-PER
Erivo I-PER
don O
collect O
nomination O
for O
di O
Best O
Actress O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Oscars O
awards O
. O

Dem O
born O
Erivo B-PER
to O
Nigerian O
parents O
for O
Stockwell B-LOC
, O
London B-LOC
for O
1987 B-DATE
. O

Di O
'Harriet' O
actress O
collect O
nomination O
for O
best O
actress O
and O
also O
best O
original O
song O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Academy O
Awards O
. O

Di O
actress O
and O
singer O
gbab O
nomination O
for O
her O
role O
as O
Harriet B-PER
Tubman I-PER
inside O
Harriet B-PER
and O
best O
original O
song O
say O
she O
follow O
write O
and O
perform O
di O
feem O
song O
"""" O
Stand O
Up O
"""" O
for O
di O
92nd O
Annual O
Academy O
Awards O
. O

If O
Erivo B-PER
win O
one O
of O
di O
categories O
, O
she O
go O
become O
di O
16th O
person O
to O
win O
Emmy O
, O
Grammy O
, O
Oscar O
and O
Tony O
Award O
. O

Erivo B-PER
bin O
win O
Grammy O
for O
2017 B-DATE
for O
di O
best O
musical O
theatre O
album O
category O
. O

Meanwhile O
di O
feem O
Joker O
dey O
lead O
all O
oda O
feems O
with O
a O
total O
of O
11 O
nominations O
. O

Di O
comic O
book O
original O
story O
dey O
up O
for O
best O
picture O
, O
best O
director O
and O
best O
actor O
for O
Joaquin B-PER
Phoenix I-PER
, O
plus O
eight O
oda O
awards O
. O

See O
di O
full O
list O
of O
nominees O
Best O
picture O
1917 B-DATE
Best O
actor O
Best O
actress O
Best O
director O
Best O
supporting O
actress O
Best O
supporting O
actor O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
film O
editing O
Best O
animated O
short O
Best O
live O
action O
short O
Best O
sound O
editing O
Best O
sound O
mixing O
Best O
adapted O
screenplay O
Best O
original O
screenplay O
Best O
foreign O
language O
film O
Best O
original O
song O
Best O
original O
score O
Best O
animated O
feature O
Best O
documentary O
feature O
Best O
cinematography O
Best O
costume O
design O
Best O
make O
- O
up O
and O
hairstyling O
Best O
production O
design O
Best O
visual O
effects O

Di O
title O
of O
im O
11th O
studio O
album O
na O
Music O
to O
Be O
Murdered O
By O
, O
wit O
20 O
songs O
inside O
wey O
feature O
artistes O
like O
Ed B-PER
Sheeran I-PER
, O
Black B-PER
Thought I-PER
, O
Q B-PER
- I-PER
Tip I-PER
and O
odas O
. O

Grammy O
nominated O
singer O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
win O
three O
awards O
including O
Africa B-LOC
Artiste O
of O
di O
year O
for O
di O
2020 B-DATE
Soundcity B-ORG
MVP O
Awards O
. O

FireBoy B-PER
DML I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
JoeBoy B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Marioo B-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Rema B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Simmy B-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Wendy B-PER
Shay I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Blow O
My O
Mind O
- O
Davido B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Daz O
How O
Star O
Do O
- O
Skibii B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Gugulethu O
- O
Prince B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
[ O
SA B-LOC
] O
- O
Winner O
Jama B-PER
- O
DJ B-PER
Mic I-PER
Smith I-PER
[ O
GH B-LOC
] O
Killin O
Dem O
- O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Inama B-PER
- O
Diamond B-PER
PlatNumz I-PER
[ O
TZ B-LOC
] O
Innos B-PER
B I-PER
[ O
CG B-LOC
] O
Nandy B-PER
[ O
TZ B-LOC
] O
JoeBoy B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
- O
Winner O
Otile B-PER
Brown I-PER
[ O
KE B-LOC
] O
Kizz B-PER
Daniel I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Teni B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Mayorkun B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Rayvanny B-PER
[ O

SA B-LOC
) O
Cassper B-PER
Nyovest I-PER
[ O
SA B-LOC
] O
Davido B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
- O
Winner O
Diamond B-PER
Platnumz I-PER
[ O
TZ B-LOC
] O
Kizz B-PER
Daniel I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Mr B-PER
Eazi I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Yemi B-PER
Alade I-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Wizkid B-PER
[ O
NG B-LOC
] O
Baby O
- O
JoeBoy B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Dumebi O
- O
Rema B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Fetch O
your O
Life O
- O
Prince B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Jealous O
- O
Fireboy B-PER
DML I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Jama B-PER
- O
DJ B-PER
Mic I-PER
Smith I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Kainama B-PER
- O
Harmonize B-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Killin O
Dem O
- O
BurnaBoy B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Kpo O
K3K3 O
- O
StoneBwoy B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Oil O
& O
Gas O
- O
Olamide B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
49 O
- O
99 O
- O
Tiwa B-PER

Savage I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Able O
God O
- O
Chinko B-PER
Ekun I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Banomoya B-PER
- O
Prince B-PER
Kaybee I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
My O
Level O
- O
Shatta B-PER
Wale I-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
On O
The O
Low O
- O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Soapy O
- O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Tetema O
- O
Rayvanny B-PER
( O
TZ B-LOC
) O
Zanku O
( O
Legwork O
) O
- O
Zlatan B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
49 O
- O
99 O
- O
Tiwa B-PER
Savage I-PER
by O
Meji B-PER
Alabi I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
- O
Winner O
Dangote B-PER
- O
Burna B-PER
Boy I-PER
by O
Clarence B-PER
Peters I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Jericho O
- O
Simi B-PER
by O
Adasa B-PER
Cookey I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Ngwa O
- O
Blick O
Bassy O
by O
Tebego B-PER
Malope I-PER
( O
SA B-LOC
) O
Ohema B-PER
- O
Kuami B-PER
Eugene I-PER
by O
Rex B-PER
( O
GH B-LOC
) O
Jealous O

NG B-LOC
) O
Wizkid B-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Yemi B-PER
Alade I-PER
( O
NG B-LOC
) O
Excellence O
in O
Philanthropy O
: O
DJ B-PER
Cuppy I-PER
- O
Winner O
Excellence O
in O
Sports O
: O
Anthony B-PER
Joshua I-PER
- O
Winner O
Excellence O
in O
Social O
Entrepreneurship O
and O
Digital O
Influence O
: O
Bright B-PER
Jaja I-PER
- O
Winner O
Community O
and O
Socio O
- O
Political O
Development O
: O
Adebola B-PER
Williams I-PER
& O
Jude B-PER
Jideonwo I-PER
- O
Winner O
Excellence O
in O
Music O
: O
Innocent B-PER
Idibia I-PER
( O
2Baba B-PER
) O
- O
Winner O

From O
politics O
to O
sports O
enta O
entertainment O
sef O
, O
from O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
Cameroon B-LOC
, O
Ghana B-LOC
and O
di O
rest O
of O
di O
world O
, O
dis O
na O
some O
of O
di O
tins O
to O
look O
out O
for O
in O
di O
year O
2020 B-DATE
. O

America B-LOC
don O
see O
some O
very O
interesting O
times O
since O
dem O
elect O
Donald B-PER
Trump I-PER
to O
become O
dia O
president O
for O
2016 B-DATE
. O

E O
remain O
for O
us O
to O
see O
if O
im O
go O
get O
second O
term O
for O
di O
White B-LOC
house I-LOC
. O

Anoda O
big O
thing O
na O
Britain B-LOC
wey O
wan O
comot O
from O
di O
European B-ORG
Union I-ORG
. O

Di O
journey O
na O
upandan O
since O
dem O
agree O
through O
yes O
or O
no O
vote O
for O
2016 B-DATE
say O
dem O
wan O
comot O
. O

Dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
every O
suppose O
click O
especially O
after O
Prime O
Minister O
Boris B-PER
Johnson I-PER
win O
during O
di O
last O
general O
elections O
. O

From O
Rihanna B-PER
to O
Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
, O
to O
Stonebwoy B-PER
, O
many O
albums O
dey O
drop O
hopefully O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

Meanwhile O
, O
Rihanna B-PER
don O
dey O
already O
tease O
new O
music O
, O
for O
now O
eh O
, O
di O
codeword O
you O
suppose O
know O
na O
R9 O
. O

PS5 O
, O
according O
to O
tori O
, O
di O
gaming O
console O
dey O
drop O
for O
di O
end O
of O
di O
year O
. O

With O
No O
Time O
To O
Die O
( O
James B-PER
bond I-PER
feem O
) O
, O
Coming O
to O
America B-LOC
, O
Bad O
Boys O
For O
Life O
with O
some O
ogbonge O
, O
correct O
superhero O
movies O
like O
Black O
Widow O
wey O
dey O
drop O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
cinema O
go O
just O
dey O
hungry O
you O
to O
go O
. O

But O
as O
some O
dey O
go O
odas O
dey O
come O
, O
and O
drum O
roll O
please O
. O
. O
. O
Indian O
soap O
opera O
station O
, O
Zee O
World O
announce O
say O
dem O
go O
add O
two O
new O
shows O
for O
dia O
line O
up O
. O

For O
now O
, O
e O
never O
clear O
wen O
e O
go O
happun O
. O

Ghana B-LOC
follow O
show O
interest O
for O
dis O
mata O
because O
West B-LOC
African I-LOC
kontris I-LOC
bin O
don O
dey O
tok O
single O
currency O
to O
helep O
trade O
. O

Nigeria B-LOC
Presido O
Muhammadu B-PER
Buhari I-PER
announce O
last B-DATE
year I-DATE
say O
e O
go O
dey O
let O
African O
pipo O
enta O
di O
kontri O
and O
get O
visa O
on O
arrival O
to O
allow O
for O
trade O
runs O
. O

Since O
den O
, O
more O
explanations O
as O
to O
how O
dis O
parole O
go O
run O
don O
comeout O
but O
pio O
dey O
wait O
to O
see O
how O
tins O
go O
play O
out O
. O

From O
online O
shopping O
tax O
, O
to O
transfer O
of O
money O
tax O
, O
many O
Nigerians O
dey O
look O
with O
corner O
eye O
wetin O
go O
happun O
with O
all O
dis O
policies O
wey O
suppose O
begin O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
. O

Plenti O
goments O
across O
di O
world O
for O
dia O
new B-DATE
year I-DATE
messages O
don O
promise O
wetin O
dem O
go O
do O
dis B-DATE
year I-DATE
to O
boost O
dia O
kontries O
. O

President O
Nana B-PER
Akufo I-PER
- I-PER
Addo I-PER
vision O
na O
say O
Ghana B-LOC
go O
reach O
higher O
heights O
for O
2020 B-DATE
. O

Citizens O
across O
dis O
kontries O
and O
di O
world O
, O
go O
dey O
chook O
eye O
to O
see O
wetin O
go O
play O
at O
di O
end O
of O
di O
day O
with O
all O
these O
visions O
and O
promises O
. O

Now O
, O
di O
council O
say O
di O
Art B-LOC
and I-LOC
Craft I-LOC
Village I-LOC
wey O
worth O
N9 O
. O
8 O
billion O
don O
become O
wia O
robbers O
dey O
hide O
plus O
wia O
dem O
dey O
sell O
bad O
drugs O
. O

"""" O
Di O
Art B-LOC
and I-LOC
Craft I-LOC
village I-LOC
( O
wey O
dey O
opposite O
Abuja B-ORG
Sheraton I-ORG
Hotels I-ORG
) O
with O
value O
of O
N9 O
. O
8 O
billion O
( O
27 O
, O
03 O
US B-LOC
Dollars O
) O
, O
na O
di O
reason O
behind O
why O
some O
pipo O
wey O
dey O
vex O
for O
me O
want O
make O
dem O
put O
me O
for O
prison O
and O
remove O
me O
from O
office O
because O
I O
I O
no O
gree O
do O
wetin O
dem O
want O
"""" O
Na O
so O
Otunba O
Olusegun B-PER
Runsewe I-PER
, O
Director O
- O
General O
of O
NCAC B-ORG
- O
wey O
be O
parastatal O
of O
di O
Federal B-ORG
Ministry I-ORG
of I-ORG
Information I-ORG
and I-ORG
Culture I-ORG
, O
tell O
tori O
pipo O
for O
Abuja B-LOC
. O

For O
im O
case O
, O
Ummakalif B-ORG
Limited I-ORG
say O
di O
sealing O
of O
di O
village O
dey O
against O
di O
contract O
agreemment O
for O
him O
to O
develop O
part O
of O
di O
village O
. O

According O
to O
Ummakalif B-PER
, O
dat O
order O
mean O
say O
make O
nobody O
do O
anytin O
wey O
go O
close O
di O
place O
down O
. O

Tori O
be O
say O
di O
city O
go O
be O
five B-DATE
minutes I-DATE
drive O
from O
di O
kontri O
new O
international O
airport O
. O

E O
tok O
say O
im O
dey O
get O
"""" O
di O
right O
treatment O
"""" O
wey O
go O
help O
treat O
dis O
disease O
wey O
no O
get O
cure O
, O
and O
im O
go O
reveal O
more O
for O
di O
documentary O
series O
about O
im O
life O
wey O
go O
dey O
YouTube O
soon O
. O

"""" O
You O
fit O
learn O
all O
wetin O
I O
don O
dey O
battle O
wit O
and O
overcome O
. O
"""" O

Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
wife O
, O
model O
Hailey B-PER
Bieber I-PER
, O
defend O
her O
husband O
against O
criticism O
from O
those O
wey O
dey O
try O
to O
make O
di O
Lyme O
disease O
look O
common O
. O

On O
top O
why O
di O
singer O
no O
appear O
for O
court O
, O
di O
lawyer O
say O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
presently O
dey O
out O
of O
di O
kontri O
na O
im O
make O
am O
. O

Di O
pesin O
wey O
drag O
Naira B-PER
Marley I-PER
go O
court O
, O
Ademola B-PER
Adelekan I-PER
claim O
say O
di O
singer O
assault O
and O
damage O
im O
car O
but O
im O
go O
drop O
di O
charges O
because O
di O
singer O
don O
meet O
up O
with O
im O
demands O
. O

Di O
servants O
go O
also O
den O
go O
home O
on O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
to O
give O
Christmas B-DATE
boxes O
to O
dia O
families O
. O

Di O
day O
also O
get O
religious O
connections O
and O
dem O
dey O
celebrate O
am O
as O
Saint B-DATE
Stephen's I-DATE
Day I-DATE
for O
Ireland B-LOC
and O
DI O
Catalonia B-LOC
region I-LOC
of O
Spain B-LOC
. O

Dem O
go O
come O
give O
di O
money O
to O
di O
poor O
pipo O
di O
next O
day O
- O
on O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
. O

Today B-DATE
, O
those O
boxes O
no O
popular O
like O
before O
. O

Na O
also O
public O
holiday O
for O
Nigeria B-LOC
nd O
some O
oda O
kontries O
around O
di O
world O
. O
. O
Wen O
26 B-DATE
December I-DATE
na O
Saturday B-DATE
, O
di O
Boxing B-DATE
Day I-DATE
holiday O
go O
move O
to O
di O
next B-DATE
Monday I-DATE
. O

If O
26 B-DATE
December I-DATE
fall O
on O
Sunday B-DATE
, O
den O
di O
holiday O
na O
di O
following O
Tuesday B-DATE
. O

"""" O
And O
very O
soon O
, O
for O
one O
movie O
wey O
we O
dey O
shoot O
right O
now O
, O
"""" O
Marvel B-ORG
Studio I-ORG
oga O
Kevin B-PER
Fiege I-PER
na O
im O
tok O
dis O
one O
during O
one O
kweshion O
and O
answer O
session O
wey O
dem O
do O
for O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
Film I-ORG
Academy I-ORG
. O
